[
{"question": "Where can I find UAE WiFi by Etisalat?", "answer": ["Service is available in all UAE Emirates, in key leisure and business locations. For a complete list of locations please visit our interactive locations map."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Who can access UAE WiFi by Etisalat?", "answer": ["Service is available to anyone holding UAE mobile number and WiFi enabled device."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Can I log in to multiple WiFi sessions?", "answer": ["Only one WiFi session per mobile number is allowed."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Do I have to register every time I log in to UAE WiFi by Etisalat?", "answer": ["No, you will only need to do it once."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Is there a data limit or time limit during the validity period of the paid package?", "answer": ["No, there is no data or time limit. You can use as much Internet as you want during validity of your paid package."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Is there a data limit or time limit during the validity period of the free package?", "answer": ["No, there is no data limit, but free package time is linked with your mobile data package and will give you between 5 and 30 hours of free WiFi depending on your mobile data package."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Is there a limit to the number of free WiFi packages I can enjoy?", "answer": ["If you have multiple mobile data packages during the same month, then your WiFi allowance will accumulate to up to 60 hours in total."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "What happens to my unused allowance when the validity expires?", "answer": ["Your unused WiFi allowance will not roll over to the next month. For free access a new allowance will be automatically given if you have a valid eligible mobile data package. For paid access, all you need to do is buy another package and continue enjoying the service."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Can I use VOIP, VPN, and P2P?", "answer": ["VOIP, VPN and P2P services are restricted."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "How fast is UAE WiFi by Etisalat service?", "answer": ["We always use the most advanced technologies, so our WiFi access can accommodate traffic up to ultra-fast 300 Mbps speeds. However end result that you will experience depends on many factors including speed of the destination server you are trying to access (ie speed of YouTube page) or limitations of your WiFi chipset in your device."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "What are the type of devices supporting the eWIFI service?", "answer": ["The device is used only for billing purposes, as login/password can be used on any device that iPass application is installed. Currently iPass app is available for iOS (Apple), Android, PC, Mac devices \u2013 it is not available on BlackBerry"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "If I have finished my data bundle (for example: a weekly package for one GB is finished), would it be treated as normal Roaming out of bundle.", "answer": ["No, as iPass service is not using mobile data, but only WiFi hotspots \u2013 so if your access to WiFi hotspots is over, then you cannot login to them anymore unless you buy a new iPass package. However you can of course use his 3G/4G mobile data regardless of his iPass WiFi hotspots access"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Can the I activate  the service through SMS while being abroad already?", "answer": ["Yes"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Does the promo renew automatically?", "answer": ["No, it's simply one free Daily pack per customer (customer needs to send 'ipass promo' to 1010 to get one free Daily pack). All iPass packs are one-time charge based (customer needs to send SMS every time his pack is expired), there is no auto-renewal with any of them"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "How can I know before travelling will know if  the hotspot Coverage is available or not?", "answer": ["In order to use iPass needs to download iPass application first (from our website / app stores), and in that iPass app there is a 'hotspot finder' function which acts as map with all iPass hotspots located. You can also check location of hotspots via iPass website: "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Why do I need to subscribe to the weekly/monthly data plan if I will be using a hotspot wireless data?", "answer": ["Such bundle gives you full freedom, as mobile data roaming packs give you mobility but they are limited with 1GB and speed (so good mainly for websites, email, social media etc.), and WiFi hotspot access gives you unlimited usage with high speed but it's limited coverage (so good for heavy websites, apps download, music, movies, gaming etc.)"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_wifi"},
{"question": "Can I get a website for my personal use? ", "answer": ["Yes. Our web hosting packages is designed to suit everyone's needs whether it's for your business or personal use.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "What is the minimum knowledge I need, to be able to use the web hosting service? ", "answer": ["To use our web hosting service, all you need to know is your Admin user id and password which will be provided to you when you apply for the service. You also need to know how to use the FTP software to upload your web pages to our web hosting servers.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Can you design a website for me?", "answer": ["As an ISP, we only provide web hosting infrastructure to host your web site. We do provide a web site builder, however, to help you build and design your website.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Do you provide assistance on web designing?", "answer": ["At this stage, we do not provide assistance in web designing. However, below are web designing companies that we recommend", "1. Advanced Digital Technology", "2. Al Ghanem Net Computers LLC", "3. Cyber Gear LLC", "4. Avanza Solutions ME-LLC", "5. Structure IT Solutions 6. Era of Technology"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "What server side technologies and web database integration does Etisalat web hosting support?", "answer": ["- Pre-written CGI Scripts", "- FrontPage 2000 Server Extensions", "- Java Servlets", "- JSP", "- Chili Soft ASP", "- Macromedia Flash Generator", "- Macromedia Cold Fusion", "- PHP", "- MySQL Database"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Do you provide statistics for my website?", "answer": ["Yes, we provide full WEBALIZER generated statistics that includes Daily Statistics, Hourly statistics, URLs, Entry pages, Exit pages, Sites, Referrers, Search engines, Countries. Statistics are updated daily (at night) to ensure that you always have the most recent statistics.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "What is the minimum period of subscription?", "answer": ["One calendar month is the minimum subscription period.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "I have applied for the website. How do I know that my site is active? How long will it take to activate it?", "answer": ["Activation usually takes a few minutes, however in some unusual cases it might take longer. To check whether your site is active or not, type your web site address in the Internet browser. If it is active, then it should take you to our default Welcome page.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "In Etisalat everything is normally based on the account number. So, do you provide an account number when I apply for web hosting?", "answer": ["Yes. You can ask the sales person who is processing your application to provide you with the account number. The account number will appear on your monthly bill on the bottom left side.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Can I upgrade my web hosting package?", "answer": ["Yes, you can upgrade your web hosting package and your web storage space. To upgrade from one package to another, visit our nearest Etisalat Business / Service centers and fill out a new application form indicating which package you want to upgrade to. There are setup fees to upgrade your package. NOTE: You need to ensure that you back-up your website data as the upgrade process will delete old data.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Is there a downtime during switching packages?", "answer": ["Yes. If you are switching your package, your website will be temporarily down until you upload your website files again to the new home directory. Please ensure that you backup your web site files before you switch packages\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Can I get additional web storage beyond what is provided in the package?", "answer": ["Yes. You can order additional web storage space. Please visit our web site for more details on the charges and extra add-on components available.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "Do you charge extra for exceeding the data transfer limit? If so, how much?", "answer": ["Yes. There are extra charges per Mb if you exceed the data transfer limit specified for your package.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_web_hosting"},
{"question": "What is a Proxy Server? ", "answer": ["A proxy server is a server that acts as an intermediary between a workstation user and the Internet to ensure security, administrative control, and caching service. A proxy server receives a request for an Internet service (such as a Web page request) from the user. If it passes filtering requirements, the proxy server, assuming it is also a cache server, looks in its local cache of previously downloaded Web pages. If it finds the page, it returns it to the user without needing to forward the request to the Internet. If the page is not in the cache, the proxy server, acting as a client on behalf of the user, uses one of its own IP addresses to request the page from the server out on the Internet. When the page is returned, the proxy server relates it to the original request and forwards it on to the user.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "What is the proxy setting for Internet Explorer? ", "answer": ["1.In the Internet Explorer, click on Tools Internet options", "2. Click on the Connections tab, and in Dial up Settings highlight the dialler and click on Settings", "3. Select Use Automatic Configuration Script and in the address enter http://proxy.emirates.net.ae/proxy.pac,then click OK."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I not able to access secured sites?", "answer": ["Try configuring Manual proxy if Automatic proxy is configured or vice-versa. If the problem is still not resolved, check with the site Administrator to see if they are using any specific port which needs to be opened by us.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why I am getting connected at 115200 when my modem is 56K? ", "answer": ["It is actually showing the baud rate of your communication port which you can change in the modem properties. This is not the speed with which your modem is communicating, but the speed at which your computer's serial port is capable of communicating with a serial device such as a modem.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why is the \"Save Password\" checkbox unavailable? ", "answer": ["Method 1", "1. When you start Windows, do not click Cancel in the logon dialog box. If you do not have a password, create a new one by typing it in the Password box, or create a null password by clicking OK. Method 2 (If the network password screen doesn't appear)", "1. Click Start - Settings - Control Panel, then double-click Network", "2. Click Add - Client and then click Add", "3. In the Manufacturers box, click Microsoft in the Network Clients box", "4. Click either Client for Microsoft Networks or Client for NetWare Networks, and then click OK", "5. Restart the computer and try again"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "My Modem is making noise while dialling, how do I make it silent ?", "answer": ["Click on Start - Settings - Control Panel and click on Modem, select Properties and type 'M0' in Extra Settings.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "How can I delete the History location bar?", "answer": ["In the Internet Explorer go to Tools -Internet Options, then click on Clear History, then click OK.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I not able to use Real player?", "answer": ["You will need to configure the Proxy Server in Real Player as follows:", "1. Click on View Preferences", "2. Highlight Proxy and select Manual Proxy", "3. Select Manual Proxy Server and enter proxy1.emirates.net.ae Port : 8080."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting disconnected? ", "answer": ["Please verify the following", "1. If you have call waiting facility, you should disable it when you want to connect to the Internet. Otherwise, whenever somebody calls you, your Internet will get disconnected. Please dial #43# 2 to disable call waiting feature on your telephone.", "2. Also check whether you have a noisy telephone line. If so, please call Etisalat Customer service at 180 or 181 to report the fault", "3. Check with your modem dealer. May be the modem is faulty and is not a reliable device.", "For any further clarification, you can reach us anytime at 101, Etisalat Customer Care Center."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message \"There is no Dial tone\"? ", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Check the modem is connected to the phone line", "2. Check the phone line is not disconnected", "3. Verify that the fax modem cable is used for connecting the modem to the phone line socket", "4. If the line is through an exchange, use '9' to make a call", "5. Click on Start - Settings - Control Panel, double-click on Modems - Properties. On Connection tab check that the 'Wait for dial tone before dialing' box is clear. For any further clarification, you can reach us anytime at 101, Etisalat Customer Care Center."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message \"verify username & password\"?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify that the username and password has been entered correctly", "2. Check whether the script file is configured in the Dial-Up Scripting tool or the Scripting Option in the properties of dialup networking connection", "3. Check the status of the account by contacting the Customer Care Centre at 101"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the prompt \"Line Busy\"?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Make sure the dialling number is 400 4444 for normal access and 500 5555 for Dial & Surf (\"0\" should be activated on the telephone line for 500 5555 only)", "2. Check that the Area code & Country code is not selected in Dialup Networking", "3. Verify that the username and the password has been entered correctly", "4. From modem properties check that the 'Wait for Dial Tone Before Dialing' box is clear. For any further clarification, you can reach us anytime at 101,", "Etisalat Customer Care Center."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message \"Modem not responding\"?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify that the modem drivers are installed correctly", "2. Check the dialler is not set to a different modem, or in the case of external modems, the cable is connected", "3. Check that the modem is communicating properly", "4. Click on Start - Settings - Control Panel and double-click on Modem, select Properties, click on Modem Com port - Diagnostics then click on 'More Info'.If this indicates that there is no communication between your modem and your computer it is suggested that you reinstall the modem drivers or contact the modem vendor. For any further clarification, you can reach us anytime at 101, Etisalat Customer Care Center."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message \"The computer you are dialling is not answering\"?", "answer": ["This can be due to many reasons, please check the following", "1. Verify that the 'Use country code and area code' field in the properties of the connection dialler box is clear", "2. Verify that theTCP/IP properties of the dialler DNS is configured as follows: Primary DNS: 194.180.1.6 Secondary DNS: 194.180.1.7", "3. Verify that the ISDN or analogue telephone line is working properly", "4. Check that the cable connecting your modem and telephone socket is functioning properly. For any further clarification, you can reach us anytime at 101,", "Etisalat Customer Care Center."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the prompt \"Modem is being used by another program\"?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify that the modem drivers are installed correctly", "2. Check the dialler is not set to a different modem, or in the case of external modems, the cable is connected", "3. Check that the modem is communicating properly", "4. Click on Start - Settings - Control Panel and double-click on Modem, select Properties, click on Modem Com port - Diagnostics then click on 'More Info'.If this indicates that there is no communication between your modem and your computer it is suggested that you reinstall the modem drivers or contact the modem vendor.", "5. Shutdown the computer, restart and try again. For any further clarification, you can reach us anytime at 101,", "Etisalat Customer Care Center."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message \"Dial Up networking could not negotiate a compatible set of network protocol you specified in the server type setting\"?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify in the TCP/IP properties of the dialler, that the DNS is configured as follows: Primary DNS: 194.180.1.6 Secondary DNS: 194.180.1.7.", "2. Try clearing the box 'Enable Software Compression' and 'Use IP Header Compression'", "3. If the problem is not resolved,", "a. Click on Start - Settings - Control Panel - Network", "b. Highlight TCP/IP, click on Properties and configure the following settings:", "IP Address: 'Obtain an IP address automatically', click on DNS configuration: Enable DNS, Selected Host: ns2, Domain: emirates.net.ae, DNS Server Search Order: 194.180.1.6", "c. Click on Add, 194.180.1.7 and OK", "d. Restart the computer and try again. If the problem is still not resolved try making a new dialup connection and by reinstalling TCP/IP. ."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting garbage in the post terminal screen?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify the proper modem drivers are installed", "2. Reduce the speed of the com port on which the modem is installed", "3. From Modem properties, uncheck from use \"Error Control\" and try the Extra Settings: AT&F1&C1."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the error message 680?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify modem is connected to the phone line with fax modem cable", "2. Verify that the phone line is not disconnected", "3. Check the dialler is not set to a different modem", "4. Make sure that no other programs are using your modem eg. Fax software, Supervoice, etc.", "5. Try uninstalling & reinstalling the modem drivers"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the error message 630 or 633?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify that the modem drivers are installed", "2. Check the dialler is not set to a different modem", "3. Click on Start - Settings - Control Panel and double-click on Modem, select Properties, click on Modem Com port - Diagnostics then click on 'More Info'. If this indicates that there is no communication between your modem and your computer it is suggested that you reinstall the modem drivers or contact the modem vendor.", "4. Try uninstalling & reinstalling the modem drivers", "5. Also try reinstalling the dialup Adapter"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the error message 650 or 691?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Verify that you are typing the correct username and password", "2. If this is Windows NT, make sure there is nothing in the Domain field", "3. Verify that \"logon to the network\" is not checked in the dialler properties"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I not able to browse?", "answer": ["Make sure you are connected to the internet and that you have the correct proxy settings configured in the browser as follows: Manual proxy configuration: HTTP proxy:- http://proxy1.emirates.net.ae Port: 8080 OR", "Automatic proxy configuration:", "http://proxy.emirates.net.ae/proxy.pac"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why am I not able to view Arabic pages?", "answer": ["For Mozilla Firefox users", "It supports all character sets - ISO, Windows Arabic and Unicode - it selects an Arabic font automatically, and also avoids the \"period line mangling\" bugs that all other browsers suffer from. However if you are facing a problem with that please visit http://preferential.mozdev.org for more information.", "For Internet Explorer 5.0", "Click on View - Encoding and select Arabic(Windows). If this does not work and if Internet Explorer is downloaded from the internet or installed from the CD (other then the operating system CD) try updating the Arabic text support as follows:", "1. Click on Start - Settings - Control panel", "2. Double-click on Add/Remove programs", "3. Highlight Internet Explorer, click on OK and select Add Components", "4. From Multilanguage Support select Arabic text support."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "Why do I see a blank page & it says 'Document Done'?", "answer": ["Please check the following", "1. Clear the cache memory In Internet Explorer go to Tools Internet Options, click on Delete Temporary Files, then click OK", "2. Try configuring Manual proxy if Automatic proxy is configured or vice-versa"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_dial_up"},
{"question": "What is the software needed for Internet for Home (Al Shamil)?", "answer": ["You need to install the modem drivers on your computer.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Can I use any modem to connect to the Internet service?", "answer": ["Only modems that are sold directly through Etisalat branches or those that have been type-approved by Etisalat may be used. Please visit www.uaelab.ae to check for an up-to-date list of type-approved modems.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Is high-speed cable Internet access the same thing as 'WebTV?'", "answer": ["No. WebTV uses an analogue modem to connect you to the Internet and your television acts as your monitor. WebTV is mainly designed for those who do not own a computer.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What is Internet for Home (Al Shamil) 256kbps Limited Access Package?", "answer": ["Internet for Home (Al Shamil) Limited Access 256Kbps package is designed for home users who wish to have access to high speed broadband connection for a limited number of hours during the month while paying a flat monthly rate. This package gives you Internet access for 15 hours per month while paying a fixed monthly charge of AED 99, with any additional usage charged at AED 2.99 per hour.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What is the difference between normal Internet for Home (Al Shamil) services, the Limited Access service and normal Dial-up service?", "answer": ["The difference between the three services is clarified in below table:"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What type of modem is recommended to be used to connect to Internet for Home (Al Shamil) 256Kbps Limited Access service?", "answer": ["It is recommended that you use a DSL modem that's connected by USB connection to your PC and will switch off when your PC is shutdown. It is advisable to avoid using DSL Router or Gateway as these modems stay connected to Internet even while the PC is switched off. Avoid saving your Internet access password on your PC to avoid auto-connecting and incurring access usage Configure your Internet browser to dial-out only when a network connection is required and set the idle time out on your browser so that the connection disconnects when not in use. Please note that the idle time out will not work if you have any application like messengers, p2p software or antivirus software which constantly accesses the Internet\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Are there any limitations to DSL? ", "answer": ["DSL decreases in performance as the distance from the exchange increases. There are limits on how far your home can be from the nearest Etisalat exchange. We will be able to advise you of any problems\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Can I still use my Analogue 28.8 or 56K Modem if I have a Broadband service? ", "answer": ["You should keep the modem just in case your cable service is not working. But our Broadband service is so much faster than a dial-up service that you will not want to use it unless you have to.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What precautions should I take if I am using a wireless router/gateway to connect to the Internet?", "answer": ["Customers using wireless routers should take the following precautions to avoid unwarranted usage:", "- Always switch off your routers to avoid extra usage as the routers will stay connected to the Net even if the PC is switched off.", "- Configure the idle timeout settings to a comfortable interval (preferable 5 minutes or less) so that the router will disconnect from the Internet, when not in use.", "- Secure the wireless connection using a strong encryption technique so that trespassers cannot initiate a live session on your Internet, if your router is switched on and during idle timeout mode.", "- Once again we stress that the best precaution is to switch off your router when you are not using the Internet."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Will the Limited Access subscriber be notified when he/she reaches their monthly limits of hours?", "answer": ["Yes, an email notification will be sent to the subscriber's EIM email address when his/her usage reaches 80%, 90% and 100% of your monthly limit of 15 hours. Therefore, we highly recommend that you regularly check your EIM email.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "How can I avoid unwarranted extra usage or charges with the Limited Access service? ", "answer": ["- Ensure that you disconnect from the Internet after you have finished using the Net and, for doubly ensuring that you stay disconnected, please switch off your PC whenever possible.", "- Ideally you should use a DSL modem that's connected by USB connection to your PC and switches off when your PC is shut down. If you are not using a USB modem, please ensure that you switch off the DSL Router or Gateway when not in use or you will be charged as your connection will stay live otherwise .", "- Avoid saving your Internet access password on your PC to avoid auto-connecting and incurring access usage.", "- Configure your Internet browser to dial-out only when a network connection is required and set the idle time out on your browser so that the connection disconnects when not in use. Please note that the idle time out will not work if you have any application like Messengers, P2P software or antivirus software which constantly access the Internet."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the error message \"Drivers not loaded\"? ", "answer": ["Firstly, disconnect and reconnect the USB cable linking your computer and the modem. If this does not resolve the problem, click on 'Start - Settings - Control Panel - System - Device Manager', double-click Network, highlight Speed Stream Adapter, click 'Properties - Driver - Update driver'. Now insert the Broadband for Home (Al Shamil) CD to update the modem drivers.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Why does the computer tell me that the modem status is 'disconnected' while the modem LED is also flashing orange & green? ", "answer": ["Make sure modem cable is firmly connected to the wall jack. Reset the modem and see if the problem is still there. If the problem has not gone away, there could be a problem with the DSL connection.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What is the default voicemail box password on the voicemail system?", "answer": ["When you dial into voicemail system (123) for the first time from your home phone, you will need to set a new password."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "How many messages can I store in the Voicemail box?", "answer": ["15 Voice messages"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "What is the length (time) of the new voicemail messages?", "answer": ["30 seconds"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "How long can I save voicemail messages?", "answer": ["You can choose to save for 14 days. System automatically stores only for 3 days."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "Can I check my voicemail messages online or using Etisalat App?", "answer": ["Sorry, this feature is currently not available."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "Will there be notifications for voicemail messages on the home phone?", "answer": ["Sorry. There is no notification for voicemail messages left on the customer\u2019s home phone."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "How do I fast-forward, rewind messages on the new voicemail system?", "answer": ["User can press # to skip the messages and can directly go to the next message."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "Can I retrieve a deleted message from the voicemail box, if so, how?", "answer": ["Sorry. Once you delete a voicemail message, it cannot be retrieved."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "Is it possible to store a message permanently on the new voicemail system?", "answer": ["After retrieving a Voice message from the system, you can save the voice messages for 3 days only."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "I forgot voicemail password. How can I reset it?", "answer": ["Please visit Etisalat Business Center or dial 101 from your home phone to reset the password"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "What happens if my home phone voicemail box is full ?", "answer": ["When your voice mail box is full and a call is redirected to the system, it overwrites the oldest voicemail message"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_voicemail"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message 'Downloading firmware'?", "answer": ["If the modem LED is yellow, new firmware is being downloaded. Wait until the modem LED turns green.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What is eSupport?", "answer": ["eSupport is an automated desktop internet connection that works as your tool to solve technical Internet problems and guides you through what should be done. This service allows computers to become self-repairing devices by having a virtual agent inside your PC, always ready and active to solve your technical issues and directing you to the correct channel of support.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What are the kind of issues that eSupport can help me solve?", "answer": ["eSupport can help with problems such as", "- Overcoming issues related to retrieving your email", "- Scanning your system for common computer problems", "- Finding answers to frequently asked questions", "- Contacting your support provider regarding your applications or service", "- Keeping you updated by sending you alerts", "- Keeping your software always updated by using the latest technology and executing needed support jobs automatically"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "What are the charges associated with eSupport?", "answer": ["This application is absolutely free and can be downloaded online.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Why am I able to send emails but unable to receive them?", "answer": ["Please check the following and if you are still not able to receive emails, please call our Customer Care representative by dialing 101.", "1) Verify that you are entering the correct email password, and that the email client is configured as follows: Incoming mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae, user id:", "2) Check your email forwarding settings from within the web mail interface and make sure that forwarding is not configured", "3) Check your email storage quota. If it has been completely used up, try to free some space by deleting some of the emails stored, or apply for an upgrade to your email storage quota. For further details on upgrading your storage quota, please visit our website at", "www.etisalat.ae/mail"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "Why am I able to receive emails but can not send them?", "answer": ["Please check the following and if you are still not able to send emails, please call our Customer Care representative by dialing 101.", "1) Make sure you are writing your full email address in lowercase letters in the email address field, and that your email client is configured as follows: Outgoing mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae", "2) Make sure you are sending to a valid email address, any mistake in typing the address can cause this problem."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "I have deleted all my emails from Outlook Express but I still get emails saying 'Low quota warning'. What should I do?", "answer": ["Please check the following and if you still continue to get these emails, please call our Customer Care representative by dialing 101.", "1) Delete all messages to the Trash folder", "2) Set your email client settings to permanently remove messages in the Trash folder."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_for_home"},
{"question": "How do I signup for online billing?", "answer": ["It takes only a few minutes and its free! You'll have to provide your email address and account number (from your most recent bill) if you want to manage your account online."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_accounts"},
{"question": "What are the benefits of signing up for an online account?", "answer": ["There are a number of advantages to using an online account, some of which are:\r\n", "\r\n- Checking your recent call costs\r\n", "\r\n- Access to paper-free billing\r\n", "\r\n- Easy and quick bill payment\r\n", "\r\n- Managing your calling features and plans online"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_accounts"},
{"question": "Do I have to sign up to use Etisalat's Online Services?", "answer": ["Yes. You will have to register, giving your details to use Etisalat Online Services."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_accounts"},
{"question": "Can I view my bill online if I receive a paper bill?", "answer": ["Yes, you can, if you are a registered user with Etisalat Online Services.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_accounts"},
{"question": "What is Telephone SMS service?", "answer": ["The Telephone SMS service lets customers with SMS-enabled Telephones send English and Arabic texts up to a maximum of 160 characters for English & 70 characters for Arabic."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_sms"},
{"question": "My telephone instrument is not SMS-enabled. Can I still receive or send texts using my Telephone?", "answer": ["Yes. Text-to-speech technology can convert a text to a voice message when it is sent to non-SMS enabled Telephone. However you cannot send text messages from your ordinary telephone."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_sms"},
{"question": "What is Unlimited IDD?", "answer": ["For the first time in UAE, customers can now make unlimited international calls to the country of choice for a fixed monthly rental. With this plan added on to your home land phone account, the customers can make direct calls to any international number \u2013 mobile or landlines."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Which are the countries I could make UL calls to?", "answer": ["You can choose one country, from the list of 64 countries to make Unlimited international (International Direct Dialing \u2013 IDD) calls. However, there will be no restriction for you to make calls to other domestic and international numbers for which your existing rates will only apply."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "What is the rental for the product?", "answer": ["There is a fixed monthly rental of just AED 150 per account. You only pay extra if calls are made to other countries other than the one selected. You may also get charged if you cross the Fair usage limits that is set for your specific country."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Who all can subscribe?", "answer": ["Any home \u2013 e Life customer (and or Part of 1P, DEL, 2P or 3P) of Etisalat in UAE with a valid and active fixed telephone line can subscribe to this offer. There is no restrictions based on nationality, type of services you currently have or the ARPU profile. Product can be subscribed during any time of the month."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Can the UL IDD product benefits get extended on to my mobile connection?", "answer": ["The Unlimited IDD to once country of your choice is available exclusively for etisalat home phone customers only. It cannot be availed by mobile subscribers."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Which are the countries available?", "answer": ["There are 64 countries available. Customer can select one country as the most preferred from this list. These countries include most of the major destinations to which more than 80% of people in UAE call.\r\n", "\r\nThere are 2 groups: 1st group with 47 countries and the 2nd group with 17 countries. The FUP is 2K Minutes per month to countries in 1st group and 1K minutes a month to countries in 2nd group. The countries list can be accessed ", "."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "What do you mean by Fair Usage Policy (FUP)?", "answer": ["The Unlimited benefit is planned in a way to extend our customers extreme value on their home IDD calls. However, it could be misused or abused by some customers, which is against the spirit of the product. Such irresponsible consumer behavior by (very) few might end up affecting the rich experience that we want our home phone customers to enjoy. In order to avoid such abuses, we have put fair usage limits. There are 2 different fair usage limits depending on the country of choice."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Why is the predefined usage limit considered as Fair?", "answer": ["On an average, the fixed phone customers in UAE speak international for around 60 minutes (1 hour) a month. Fair usage limits are set at 2000 minutes to group 1 countries, which is more than 33 Hours a month (Which is more than 1 hour every day as against today\u2019s 1 hour a month!). Even to group 2 countries, the Fair usage limit is 1000 minutes, which is more than 16 Hours of international calling a month!", "Anyhow, you can call to the selected country at regular standard rate even after crossing FUP."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Will I have to pay full even if I buy the product mid month?", "answer": ["You can buy the product any time on the month. But we ensure you that you are not unnecessarily charged. The charges for the first month will be prorated depending on the day of subscription. For example, if the subscription is on 10th of the month, the customer will be charged only 100 AED instead of AED 150."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Does it (the plan)  have a contract?", "answer": ["The enhanced One country UL IDD product do not have any contracts that binds you down with exit charges. The regular home product policies are only applied. Exiting mid month is possible, but the charges will be retrieved for full month. Therefore, we suggest you to use the product till month end and then exit."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to the product:\r\n", "\r\n(a) Dial 125 from your home phone and subscribe to the product directly. You can select the country of choice by entering the IDD code as per the voice prompt.\r\n", "\r\n(b) Dial 800101 and speak to our customer care agent to subscribe to the plan\r\n", "\r\n(c) Visit any of our Business centers or can get the product subscribed through any of our indirect sales channels."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Can I change the country of choice?", "answer": ["You can change the country of choice, by detaching (exiting) from the current plan and subscribing new to the different country of your choice. It will be considered as a new subscription with rentals charged."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Can the UL IDD product be used along with other value added products on voice?", "answer": ["The enhanced UL IDD product will co-exist with any other VAS and other products as long as it is not having any IDD component. Eg; it will still run on the account along with VAS, F2M Bundles etc. However, the existing IDD products (Eg 1 Fils) will cease to exist if the UL DD product is subscribed."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "How do I know about my usage?", "answer": ["You can dial into 125 and understand about the usage to the selected country of choice. Anyhow, there will be email send to the registered email ID and messages send to the registered mobile number whenever the customer crosses 80%, 90% and 100% of the predefined Fair Usage Limits.", "Therefore, we suggest you to keep your email ID and mobile number updated in our systems and confirm it with our customer care agent to ensure that these messages are delivered properly."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "Will I have to re-subscribe if I upgrade or downgrade my connection in between the month?", "answer": ["The product / pack will auto move into the new product in case you upgrade or downgrade your eLife connection. There will be no extra action required at your end.", "More details about this product are available in our website www.etisalat.ae"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_unlimited_idd"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate Call Forwarding?", "answer": ["To activate Call Forwarding, press *21*, followed by the desired telephone number, and the # key. To deactivate the service, Press #21#."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate Call Waiting?", "answer": ["To activate Call Waiting, press *43#. To deactivate the service, press #43#."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate Call Barring?", "answer": ["To activate Call Barring, press *33*, followed by your 4-digit password, and the # key. To deactivate the service, press #33*, followed by your 4-digit password, and the # key."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate Do Not Disturb?", "answer": ["To activate Call Waiting, press *26#. To deactivate the service, press #26#."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate FollowMe and Call Forwarding?", "answer": ["To activate FollowMe and Call Forwarding, dial 146 and follow the voice prompts."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate Hotline with TimeOut?", "answer": ["To activate Hotline with TimeOut, press *53*, followed by the desired number and the # key. To deactivate the service, press #53#."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to activate and deactivate Hotline without TimeOut?", "answer": ["To activate Hotline, press *53*, followed by the desired number and the # key. To deactivate the service, press #53#."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to setup Conference Call?", "answer": ["To setup a conference call,\r\n", "\r\ni. Call the first party and press the hook or flash button. This puts the current caller on hold, and you will hear a dial tone.\r\n", "\r\nii. Dial the new number and wait for the call to be answered.\r\n", "\r\niii. Press the hook or flash button again and wait to hear the dial tone.\r\n", "\r\niv. Press 3.\r\n", "\r\nv. All three individuals will then be connected in the same conversation"], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "What is Voice Mail (Al Mersal) Messaging Service?", "answer": ["Voice Mail (Al Mersal) Messaging service is an advanced telephone answering service customized to suit unique customer needs especially for those on the move and who spend time out of their homes or offices."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "What are the codes and commands for activation?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "What is Voice Mail (Al-mersal) password?", "answer": ["Password is a secret number that protects the security and privacy of messages and mailbox and allows access to authorized persons only. Whenever users access their mailbox from another telephone the system prompts to enter a password."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "How to create an Al-mersal password?", "answer": ["Initially when the mailbox is being setup, the system will give you the option to create a password from 4 to 6 digits. This has to be remembered and can be changed anytime."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "What if you forget the password?", "answer": ["All Etisalat mobile customers can apply for the issue of a new password by visiting the nearest Etisalat Business / Service centre, with a valid identity. The old password will be deactivated and a new password, with 4 digits only will be provided. This can then be changed to 6 digits through the mailbox set-up menu."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_calling_plans"},
{"question": "What is my email password? ", "answer": ["Your email password is the password you use to retrieve your emails using the Etisalat web mail client or your own email client. This password is given at the time of subscription to the service and can be changed at any time through the Etisalat web mail interface. For any further clarification, please contact Etisalat Contact Center by dialling 101, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I change my email address? ", "answer": ["To change your email address you will need to change the user id of your Etisalat Internet access account. To do so you will have to submit an application for change of Internet user id by visiting our nearest Etisalat Business / Service center and paying the applicable charges.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I get more email storage space? ", "answer": ["To free some space, you can delete any unwanted messages. At any time, you can also apply for extra storage space for your mailbox to increase its capacity, by visiting http://www.etisalat.ae/mail.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I get more than one email address? ", "answer": ["Yes. Etisalat Internet Mail service allows residential / individual customers to have more than one email account. If you are a business / corporate customer you can apply to the Virtual Email service where you can have your email at your company domain (e.g. employeename1@companydomain)\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is my email password? ", "answer": ["Your email password is the password you use to retrieve your emails using the Etisalat web mail client or your own email client. This password is given at the time of subscription to the service and can be changed at any time through the Etisalat web mail interface. For any further clarification, please contact Etisalat Contact Center by dialling 101, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I receiving an email titled \"Warning: Low Quota\"? ", "answer": ["The default email storage space of your mailbox is 50Mb. The system will automatically notify you by an email as soon as 80% of your mailbox capacity is reached. This email is intended to give you a warning prior to your mailbox reaching its full capacity. Try to free some space by deleting some of the emails stored, or apply for an upgrade to your email storage quota. For further details on upgrading your storage quota, please visit our website at www.etisalat.ae/mail\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I get more email storage space?", "answer": ["To free some space, you can delete any unwanted messages. At any time, you can also apply for extra storage space for your mailbox to increase its capacity, by visiting http://www.etisalat.ae/mail.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is the use of the External Mail Option?", "answer": ["(WM)The 'External Mail' option provides you with a facility to access your other email accounts hosted on mail servers other than the Etisalat mail server, configured to use the POP3 protocol. If your account is hosted on any such server then those messages can be downloaded and viewed through the Etisalat web mail.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Before downloading my emails I want to keep a copy of them on the server. How do I do that? ", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t", "1) Using POP3 you can configure your email client to 'Leave messages on server'. OR", "2) Using IMAP you can view your messages directly on the server without the need for downloading them."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat Mail Alias service?", "answer": ["The Etisalat Mail Alias service allows you to change your 8 character Etisalat email name to a more meaningful name. For example, instead of having your Etisalat email account as abc@eim.ae, you can set it to yourfirstname.lastname@eim.ae. You can have up to 3 aliases for your Etisalat Mail account. Once you setup your email aliases, you will be able to receive emails using your original email accounts (e.g. abc@eim.ae) as well as your new alias (e.g. yourfirstname.lastname@eim.ae). To setup your Etisalat Mail Alias, please access our web mail service at www.etisalat.ae/mymail and select the Alias service option.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I check how many emails I have in my 'web mail Inbox'?", "answer": ["Click on the Inbox icon in the left side, which will display information similar to '{ Inbox 40 Messages (31 unread) }' which indicates the number of the messages you have.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I read and reply to a message in web mail? ", "answer": ["Click on the Inbox icon in the left side, then click the preferred message in the list to read it. If you want to reply to one of the messages, then you need to click on the Reply icon at the top. Click 'Sender only' to reply to the sender alone or click 'Reply all' to reply to all others on the current message list.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I forward a message in web mail? ", "answer": ["Open a message and click 'Forward'. Then type the email address you want to forward and click 'Send'.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I add a contact using my Contacts list in web mail? ", "answer": ["Click on the Address Book then click 'Add Contact', fill the boxes then click Save. Or you can use the Quick Add in the bottom of the Address Book page by filling the boxes then click Add.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I delete a contact from my Contacts list in Web mail?", "answer": ["Click on the Address Book and then the ' X ' next to the contact you want to delete.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I edit a contact using my Contacts list in Web mail? ", "answer": ["Click on the Address Book and then the image under the 'Edit' column, next to the contact you want to edit. Edit the information and save it.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to spell check an email in Web mail? ", "answer": ["Click the 'ABC' icon in the top right corner of the message area.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to check my email using Web mail? ", "answer": ["Access beta.eim.ae, using your browser. Login entering your username and password. A list of the received emails will be listed.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I move emails from 'Web mail' folders? ", "answer": ["Select the email you want to move and click 'Move', and then select the folder you want to move the email to.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I receiving someone else's emails? ", "answer": ["It could be that the person concerned is forwarding his / her emails to your email account.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I increase my email quota?", "answer": ["You will have to apply for extra email quota. For more information click 'Upgrade' in the top right corner in the web mail page.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I check if I've exceeded my email quota?", "answer": ["In the top right corner of the email list is indicated your limit and the used quota.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to write an email in web mail? ", "answer": ["Towards the top left of the email list is the Compose icon, to start writing an email.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I send an SMS using web mail? ", "answer": ["Towards the top left corner of the email list, is the SMS Composer icon, to send an SMS using your web mail.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I obtain an email header? ", "answer": ["Click on the Full Headers icon available towards the middle of the email message.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to log out of web mail?", "answer": ["Click Sign Out at the top right corner of the web mail page, to log out of your web mail account.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I protect myself against spam? ", "answer": ["Visit our Anti-spam center to activate the anti-spam service and get more information.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to delete an email message in web mail? ", "answer": ["Select the email you want to delete by ticking the appropriate checkbox on the email list and then click Delete.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to report an email message as spam in web mail? ", "answer": ["Select the email you want to mark as a spam email then click Spam. Or open the email and then move it to the Spam folder.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to send a message to multiple recipients using web mail? ", "answer": ["Within the email composer you either type all the emails in the To field and separate them with commas (,) or you can use the Cc field (recipients listed in this field will be able to view all of the other recipients of this email) or the Bcc field (recipients listed in this field will not be able to view all of the other recipients of this email).\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to attach a file to a message in Web mail? ", "answer": ["Within the email composer, click 'Browse', and choose the file you want to attach. Then click 'Open'.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I logged out of web mail while writing a long email? ", "answer": ["It is possible that the browser session got idle and lost connection to the server after the long time you spent writing the email.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How to remove an attached file from a message in Web mail?", "answer": ["Click the 'Remove' link, displayed next to the attached file\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is the difference between Smart MCN & Voicemail service?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "How many message my smart MCN service can take?", "answer": ["Up to 7 messages. Each one is valid for 7 days only, after that it will be deleted automatically."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Can I have a voice greeting message for the Smart MCN service?", "answer": ["No, your caller will be hearing a fixed announcement."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Is there any charges for activating or deactivating the service?", "answer": ["No, you can activate & deactivate the service at any time for free.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Is there any charges for retrieving the voice-note messages?", "answer": ["No, it is totally free of charge in case you are retrieving from inside UAE, if you are retrieving the messages from outside UAE roaming charges will be applied."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Is this service free of charge?", "answer": ["Yes, totally free of charge."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Will local callers also be notified when I\u2019m back on the network?", "answer": ["No, only the international numbers who called you while you are away will receive the Notify Me SMS."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Can I activate & deactivate the service any time?", "answer": ["Yes, you can manage the service as you like."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Is there any charges for activating or deactivating the service?", "answer": ["No, you can activate & deactivate the service at any time for free."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "If I'm outside UAE (Roaming), will my international callers be notified when I\u2019m back on the network?", "answer": ["Yes, the service will continue to work normally and no charges will apply to you."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "Can I activate & deactivate the service while roaming?", "answer": ["Yes but the USSD code could be blocked by some of the operators or used for their local services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "vas"},
{"question": "What are the standard Telephone plans available?", "answer": ["The standard Telephone plans available are the Postpaid and Prepaid plans."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_getting_a_phone-line"},
{"question": "How can I apply for a standard Telephone?", "answer": ["You can apply for a standard Telephone by visiting our nearest Etisalat Business / Service centre. You can also call 101 for our Customer Care Center."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_getting_a_phone-line"},
{"question": "How can I place an order for an additional telephone line?", "answer": ["You can apply for an additional Telephone online through Etisalat Online Services. You can also order by visiting our nearest Etisalat Business / Service centre or calling 101 for our Customer Care representatives."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_getting_a_phone-line"},
{"question": "Can I use Etisalat's Prepaid Card to make international calls from my Telephone?", "answer": ["Yes. You can use Etisalat's Prepaid Calling Card to make international calls from your Telephone."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_getting_a_phone-line"},
{"question": "Can I apply for a Telephone if I live in shared accommodation?", "answer": ["Yes. You can apply for a Telephone if you provide a 'No Objection' certificate from the person whose name appears in the tenancy contract."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_getting_a_phone-line"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to STAR Services for my telephone?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to one or all of our STAR Services simply by dialing 182 from your telephone, in which case no subscription charges are applied or visiting our nearest Etisalat Business / Service Centre."], "cat": "telephonenew", "sub_cat": "telephone_getting_a_phone-line"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat Wallet?", "answer": ["A new convenient, rewarding and highly secured service from Etisalat that allows you to make purchases, pay utility bills, top-up Etisalat phone and so much more, all using one simple application.\r\n", "\r\nEasy, fast and secure, there\u2019s no need to carry cash on you anymore because your phone is now your wallet.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "How to get the wallet on my phone?", "answer": ["Down \u201cEtisalat Wallet\u201d Application, available on App Store and Google Play.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "How much the service will cost me?", "answer": ["The service is free of charge.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "How to pay for services in the wallet?", "answer": ["You pay through your valid credit/debit card.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "How to link a card to the wallet then?", "answer": ["Download the Mobile Application, manage wallet, then add card.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "How many cards can I add?", "answer": ["You can add up to valid 5 cards.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "How much card add will cost me?", "answer": ["Nothing it\u2019s a free of charge.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "Any specific bank?", "answer": ["No, any Visa, Master Card, Any bank in the UAE or GCC.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "I can see my card has been charged for AED 1, why is that?", "answer": ["This is just to check what card state with your bank, the AED 1 will be reversed to your account in minutes\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "Is it secured?", "answer": ["Yes, secured by 4-6 Digits PIN, all transactions are secured with your bank through one time password OTP.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "What kind of services available in Etisalat Wallet?  ", "answer": ["- Bill Payment for Self and Other\r\n", "\r\n- Airtime Top-Up for Self and Other\r\n", "\r\n- Get rewarded!\r\n", "\r\n- Loyalty points redemption\r\n", "\r\n- Check your Etisalat Rewards Balance\r\n", "\r\n- Pay for Parking Service\r\n", "\r\n- International Credit Transfer to 100+ Countries\r\n", "\r\n- Push notification for new bills\r\n", "\r\n- Low Balance notification for Prepaid customers\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "etisalat_wallet"},
{"question": "What is POP3, IMAP & SMTP Server? ", "answer": ["POP3 (Post Office Protocol 3) is a standard client/server protocol for receiving and storing emails through an Internet server. These emails can be periodically checked and downloaded by you or your client email receiver. An alternative protocol is Internet Message Access Protocol (IMAP). With IMAP, you can view your emails at the server as though it was on your client computer. An email message deleted locally will still be on the server. POP can be thought of as a \"store-and-forward\" service while IMAP can be thought of as a remote file server. POP and IMAP deal with the receiving of email and are not to be confused with the Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP), a protocol for transferring email across the Internet. You send email with SMTP and a mail handler receives it on your recipient's behalf. Then the mail is read using POP or IMAP.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I configure more than one email account in Outlook Express? ", "answer": ["Yes. To configure a new account:", "1) Open Outlook Express, click on Tools Accounts and select Mail", "2) Click on the Add button and choose the Mail option", "3) Follow instructions to configure the new email account with these settings", "Incoming mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae , Outgoing mail server:", "mail.emirates.net.ae, User id: ."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Before downloading my emails I want to keep a copy of them on the server. How do I do that? ", "answer": ["You have two options:", "1) Using POP3 you can configure your email client to 'Leave messages on server' OR", "2) Using IMAP you can view your messages directly on the server without the need for downloading them"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I able to send emails but unable to receive them?", "answer": ["Please check the following and if you are still not able to receive emails, please call our Customer Care representative by dialing 101.", "1) Verify that you are entering the correct email password, and that the email client is configured as follows: Incoming mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae, user id:", "2) Check your email forwarding settings from within the web mail interface and make sure that forwarding is not configured", "3) Check your email storage quota. If it has been completely used up, try to free some space by deleting some of the emails stored, or apply for an upgrade to your email storage quota. For further details on upgrading your storage quota, please visit our website at www.etisalat.ae/mail."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "I have deleted all my emails from Outlook Express but I still get emails saying 'Low quota warning'. What should I do?", "answer": ["Please check the following and if you still continue to get these emails, please call our Customer Care representative by dialing 101.", "1) Delete all messages to the Trash folder", "2) Set your email client settings to permanently remove messages in the Trash folder."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I configure my email client to be able to send Email2SMS messages? ", "answer": ["To be able to send Email2SMS messages from your email client you need to configure it to use SMTP authentication. Depending on which email client software you are using configuration steps may vary. For details on configuring your email client, please follow the steps below. For web mail client at ", " No configuration is required.", "1. From the main tool bar menu, select Tools, then Email Accounts", "2. Select view or change existing email accounts and click Next", "3. Select the name of your EIM Mail account and click Change", "4. Under Server information, enter exmail.emirates.net.ae in the Outgoing mail server (SMTP) field, then click on More Settings.", "5. Select the Outgoing Server tab, and check the box My outgoing server (SMTP) requires authentication", "6. Select Use same settings as my incoming mail server and click OK", "7. Click Next, then click Finish.", "1. From the main tool bar menu select Tools, then Accounts", "2. Under the Mail tab select your EIM Mail account and click Properties", "3. Select the Servers tab and change the Outgoing Mail (SMTP) field to exmail.emirates.net.ae", "4. Check the box My server requires authentication and click on Settings", "5. Select Use same settings as my incoming mail server", "6. Click OK and then Close."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "I am using the Etisalat web mail client to send Email2SMS messages but recipients are receiving messages with empty body text. Why? ", "answer": ["When using the Internet Explorer web browser and the Etisalat web mail to send Email2SMS messages, please make sure that you are composing your message in text mode and not HTML, in order to make sure that the body of your messages are being received.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "When I send Arabic Email2SMS messages using Etisalat web mail the recipients are not able to read the characters properly. Why?", "answer": ["To be able to send both Arabic and English Email2SMS messages using Etisalat web mail, please make sure that you have set your preferred language in your web mail settings to Arabic.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What will happen if I exceed the maximum number of characters allowed in an Email2SMS message? ", "answer": ["In the event that your Email2SMS message exceeds the maximum number of characters allowed (i.e. 560 characters for English and 280 characters for Arabic messages), the message will be truncated to the maximum number of characters allowed before delivery to its intended recipients.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I attach an image to my Email2SMS message? ", "answer": ["Currently, SMS supports only text. If you attach an image to your Email2SMS message, the attachment will be discarded and only the text portion of your message gets delivered.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Is there a possibility of any virus attached when using the Email2SMS service? ", "answer": ["Since SMS is compromised of only static text, there is absolutely no risk of viruses being transferred to mobile phones as a result of using the service. In addition, this service does not support attachments, thus reducing any potential threats.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "When I send an Email2SMS message to a friend, can he/she reply back to me? ", "answer": ["Yes. To reply to an Email2SMS message from your mobile phone:", "1. Enter the sender's e-mail address in the Message field followed by a space", "2. Between brackets enter the subject of the message followed by a space", "3. Add your message text with a maximum of 160 characters (which includes the e-mail address and subject as well)", "4. In the Number field , key in 1234 and press the SEND key"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Do I have to specify the UAE country code every time I need to send an Email2SMS inside the UAE? ", "answer": ["No. The full mobile number format (i.e. + ) is only needed when you are sending an Email2SMS to international mobile phone numbers. When sending an Email2SMS to a UAE mobile phone number all you need is to address your Email2SMS to a local mobile phone number represented by the Operator code and the mobile number only.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I send the same Email2SMS message to multiple recipients? ", "answer": ["Similar to sending an email to multiple recipients, all you have to do is insert the recipients' mobile numbers, separated by semi-colons (e.g. mobilenumber1@email2sms.ae ; mobilenumber2@email2sms.ae etc.) in the 'To:' field of your email client and click on 'Send' key.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "I am using English characters and sometimes I am not able to send more than 70 characters per SMS, why? ", "answer": ["If your email client is configured to use Unicode (UTF-8) as the default encoding mechanism, the number of characters per SMS will be limited to only 70, as in the case when sending Arabic Email2SMS messages. To solve this problem, all you need to do is to configure your email client to use a different encoding mechanism (e.g. US ASCII, or European ISO) after which you should be able to send higher number of characters (up to 140) per SMS provided that it is written using Latin characters set. You can also use the Etisalat Web Mail (www.etisalat.ae/mymail) which by default supports sending SMS up to 140 characters long.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I preserve my email quota? ", "answer": ["The quota size you are assigned to use covers all the folders you have in your email (inbox, sent items, drafts and trash), so make sure you delete the unnecessary emails every once in a while to avoid quota increase. You can manually delete the unnecessary emails you have in a folder or you can set up your deleting mail option by following these easy steps", "1) Log on tohttp://www.etisalat.ae/mymail with your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Settings at the top right side of the screen.", "4) You can see the Deleting Mail option, and you will have two options:", "You can either choose \"Move deleted message to\", which requires you to select a folder from the drop-down list, or you can choose \"Mark messages deleted\".", "To move deleted messages to the Trash folder, click the button next to \"Move delete messages to Trash\". Setting this option ensures that when messages are erased a backup copy is saved in the trash. This option allows you to select Empty folder on logout, which empties your Trash folder after logging out. If this option is not set, you should periodically delete your Trash for maximum server performance. If you \"Mark messages deleted\", messages are still active, but marked with an X. When you click Expunge, the messages that are marked for deletion are permanently removed without saving a backup copy.", "Note: Now with EIM mail service you can apply for more quota by visiting "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why do I get indications of new mail but I can't find it? ", "answer": ["When you set your mail forwarding option to receive a copy/indication of new messages via GSM or other emails, you have to make sure that your email quota is not exceeding the limit assigned to.", "Kindly note that if you exceed the quota, you will only receive the indications you set up your account to receive, however new emails will not be available in your inbox. Also be aware that the quota size you are assigned to use covers all the folders you have in your email (inbox, sent items, drafts and trash), so make sure you delete the unnecessary emails every once in a while to avoid quota increase. Also, you can avail of the Deleting Mail option to assist you better with deleting your trash folder"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I use the mail forward option?", "answer": ["Please use the following steps to set your Mail Forward option:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail using your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Settings at the top right side of the screen.", "4) Go to Mail Forwarding and type the address where copies of new messages will be forwarded to.", "5) Click on Save changes to finish the process. (The option to send a copy of every message you receive to a specific email address will be enabled).", "Note: You can enter as many email addresses as you want in the box, one line at time."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I set the \"Vacation Auto-Responder\" option?", "answer": ["Please use the following steps to set your Vacation Auto-Responder:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymailusing your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Vacation Message at the top right side of the screen.", "4) Enable Vacation Message. Select this box to enable the auto-response mode", "5) Vacation Start Date. Specify the date on which to begin sending automatic responses.", "6) Vacation End Date. Specify the date on which to stop sending automatic responses.", "7) Interval for reply to repeat senders. Enter the number of days to wait until this message is sent to repeat senders.", "8) Subject line. Enter the subject of the reply message.", "9) Response to Internal Senders. This is the message that is sent to senders who are within the same domain as yourself.", "10) Message text. Enter the text of the reply message.", "11) Response to External Senders. This is the message that is sent to senders who are not within the same domain as yourself.", "12) Message text. Enter the text of the reply message."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Is there a way to redirect my messages?", "answer": ["Yes there is. With EIM mail service you can benefit from the Redirect Messages option which allows you to redirect your messages to any address based on a specified condition. To redirect your messages to a specific address, please follow the steps below:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail using your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Settings at the top right side of the screen.", "4) Click on Manage Incoming Messages under Mail Filters.", "5) Select Set Mail Filter on your left.", "6) Click on Add.", "7) Select Redirect Messages From the filter templates pull-down menu.", "8) Fill in the Redirect Messages template:", "- Name. Specify a name for the filter.", "- If the header line. Select the header line on which to search.", "- Contains the phrase. Specify the phrase for which to search.", "- Then redirect the message to the address. Specify an email address where the message will be redirected"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I change my email password online?", "answer": ["You can easily change your password through the web. To change your Password online:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail using your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile", "3) Select Password at the top center of the screen.", "4) Now you have three fields, all of which must be filled in: - Enter your old password: - Enter your new password: - Confirm your new password:", "5) Click Change Password to confirm new password, or Reset to retain old password. Note: please make sure that you fulfil the following requirements:", "1. The new password MUST differ from the old password in as many characters as possible.", "2. Contains EIGHT alpha-numeric characters EXACTLY.", "3. Consists of letters and numbers ONLY, and should contain AT LEAST two numbers.", "4. Different from the USER ID."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Is it possible to keep my sent messages?", "answer": ["Yes it is possible to keep your sent messages in any folder using the following steps:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail with your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Setting at the top right side of the screen.", "4) Mark the Sent Messages option and choose from the drop down menu the folder you wish to save your sent messages in.", "5) Click on Save changes to finish the process."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How do I customize the appearance of my email account?", "answer": ["To customize the appearance of your web mail you need to follow the steps below:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail with your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Appearance at the top right side of the screen.", "4) Use the form to modify the look of your Web Mail. - Display Font : You can customize the font face and font size used in messages. Choose what you want from the drop-down lists. - Message List View :You can set the number of messages to show per page, and you can sort the messages in ascending or descending order.", "5) Click on Save changes to finish the process."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I update my Personal Information?", "answer": ["Yes you can update your personal information by following the steps below:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail using your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile.", "3) Select Personal Information at the top.", "4) Use the form to change your personal information.", "5) Click on Save Changes at the bottom to finish the process ."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I view my account summary?", "answer": ["You can view your account summary including your Email addresses, name and how much quota you have used by following the steps below:", "1) Log on to www.etisalat.ae/mymail using your user name and password.", "2) Click on Profile on your left .", "3) Then select Account summary at the top left side of the screen"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I check my email while I am overseas?", "answer": ["Yes you can check your email by visiting the EIM Web Mail homepage at www.etisalat.ae/mymail then type your User ID and Email Password to log on.", "Make sure you disable the UAE proxy settings in your browser when you try to check your email."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I getting \"Check your password and try again\"?", "answer": ["You may get this message due to different reasons:", "1) You may be typing a wrong password. In this case, check your password again and make sure that you are using the correct letter case as the password field is case sensitive. Also note that Iif you have changed your Internet access password from the EIM homepage, this will not change your email password you still need to change it separately.", "2) Check the configuration of the email client that you are using and make sure that your account (username) is correct.", "3) Check your due bills, your account may be suspended due to non-payment. 4) You may have not accessed your email account for more than 4 months and consequently your account has been de-activated. You can re-activate your account by visiting www.ecompany.ae/mail/reactivate."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I send messages to more than one person? ", "answer": ["If you want to send a message to more than one person, you can easily type all the email addresses of the recipients separated by a comma, in the TO, CC or BCC fields, you can also select more than one address from your email client address book. Another alternative is to create a group that contains the required addresses and then send the message to that group name. We have set the limit on the total number of email addresses in the TO, CC, BCC fields per email message to a maximum of 50, to try to fight Spam and limit spammers from misusing our email system.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I getting same messages downloaded every time?", "answer": ["If you are using the POP3 protocol to retrieve your messages and you have the option 'keep messages on server' set to ON and then you used a different email client or PC to check your email then you will have the same messages downloaded again. Another reason is that there may be a corrupted email in the mailbox which keeps downloading each time you access your email box. To remove this email, log on to our EIM web mail interface at http://www.etisalat.ae/mymail and delete the corrupted message. To avoid this problem please change the settings for your email client option 'keep messages on server' to OFF."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I getting an E-mail with the subject line \"EIM removed a virus(es) from this message, it is safe to check the message/attachment(s)\"? ", "answer": ["Email messages can not contain viruses. However, files that are attached to messages can contain viruses. EIM Mail Service provides free scanning of attachments to all subscribers who get incoming email through the web interface as well as to those who use POP3 through an E-mail client.", "When you receive a message with a subject line that reads \"EIM removed a virus(es) from this message, it is safe to check the message/attachment(s)\" it means that the originator of that E-mail is infected with a virus and the attachment that was sent was effectively a virus. However, with EIM's Anti Virus Service in place it will automatically check the attachment for any known viruses.", "If no viruses are found, the file will be downloaded as is. In case an attachment(s) is contaminated by a virus, the EIM Mail Anti Virus Service will remove the virus-contaminated attachment and replace it with a virus-free alert attachment explaining the name of the virus as well as any action(s) taken by the service. The original subject of the message will be modified to alert the recipient that a virus(es) was removed. The new subject line of the message will then look like this: \"EIM removed a virus(es) from this message, it is safe to check the message/attachment(s): \" and then the original subject is appended. This alert message is only sent to your email account if you opt to receive it. By default, this alert message is not sent to your EIM Mail account.\"", "To provide the most comprehensive protection, viruses will be removed rather than simply cleaned. This is because when a virus is contained in an attachment, it may alter the information in the document before it can reach the anti virus software. This, in turn, can alter the files contents and result in the recipient receiving inaccurate, misleading information without being aware it has been corrupted.", "EIM Mail subscribers have the option of disabling the anti virus service should they wish to do so, although this is not recommended by"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is Spam?", "answer": ["Email spam is unsolicited bulk commercial or junk email sent to a number of users at once. Spam is often used to advertise products or to broadcast some political or social commentary. Spam is considered to be an extremely efficient and cost-effective way to distribute a message form the senders' point of view. To most recipients, spam is just junk e-mail. Spammers typically send a piece of e-mail to a distribution list in the millions, expecting that only a tiny number of readers will respond to their offer .\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How bad is the Spam problem worldwide?", "answer": ["By January 2004, spam accounted for 60% of the emails world wide. In 2002, time and resources used to deal with spam cost US companies almost $9 billion (source: Ferris Research). Worldwide, spam is expected to cost businesses $30 billion this year, and $113 billion by 2007 (source: Radicati Group). Over 70% of technology professionals believe the spam problem has reached epidemic proportions (source: TrendMicro).\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why is Spam annoying?", "answer": ["Email users consider Spam annoying because:", "Users did not ask for these type of emails.", "Users find their email boxes full with email that do not concern them which leads them to spend time and money dealing with such issues.", "Email users spend more time on the Internet to download emails that are meaningless to them which costs them stress, time and money.", "Spam usually contains offensive material."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is considered a Spam activity by EIM?", "answer": ["According to Etisalat, Acceptable Use Policy, the following activities are identified as spamming activities:", "To send unsolicited mass e-mailing (Spamming or bulk junk e-mail) to Internet users be it on EIM email or any other Internet service provider.", "To post private e-mail message to any newsgroup, forum or mailing list without the explicit approval of that entity.", "To post or send e-mail to any person who does not wish to receive it, if a recipient asks to stop receiving e-mail. Accordingly, obtaining the business card or the email address of a customer does not give the automatic right to send spam emails. The customer needs to agree to receive promotional emails in writing for such messages for it not to be considered a spam. In such a case, your spam email need to have a facility to remove the customer from the list should he/she opt to be removed. However, if you are the email administrator of an email domain hosted with EIM, e.g. yourcompany.ae, you have the right to send all type of emails to your domain email accounts about your products and services"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is EIM doing to protect me from Spam?", "answer": ["Currently at the network level, Etisalat takes the following steps to protect your email from spammers: Throttles email from high-volume sources and Blocks known spammers on an adhoc basis. Provides users with the option to subscribe to use the anti spam filters available as part of the EIM Web mail. Limit the number of recipients for incoming and outgoing messages to 50 email addresses only\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What can Etisalat do against spammers?", "answer": ["Etisalat has strict policy against spamming. Etisalat email users who spam other users inside or outside the UAE, risk losing their internet connection. All Etisalat email users signed the Etisalat Acceptable Use Policy which clearly defines spam and the list actions that can be taken against spammers. The policy is outlined below: Etisalt Acceptable Use Policy The following guidelines are designed to protect the interests of Etisalat's service and our customers. Violation of these guidelines may result in suspension or termination of Etisalat services.", "Emirates Telecommunications Corporation also reserves the right to institute legal action in case of such violations. All Etisalat customers shall abstain from and shall not participate to assist or contribute to all or any of the following prohibited activities:", "To post any advertisement or commercial solicitations to any newsgroup, e-mail mailing list or Forum.", "To post articles to newsgroup without compliance with the written charter for those newsgroups. To post any copyright material to any newsgroup, forum or mailing list without the explicit permission of the copyright holder. Forging of header information or to impersonate another user or falsify user information (e.g. using fake or incomplete names) in e-mail or any post to any newsgroup, forum or mailing list. To send unsolicited mass e-mailing (Spamming or bulk junk e-mail) to Internet users be it on Etisalat or any other Internet service provider.", "To post private e-mail message to any newsgroup, forum or mailing list without the explicit approval of that entity. To post or send e-mail to any person who does not wish to receive it, if a recipient asks to stop receiving e-mail.", "To engage in any of the foregoing activities using the service of another provider, but channeling such activities through Etisalat account as a mail drop for responses."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I report a Spam to Etisalat?", "answer": ["Of course. You need to send to abuse@eim.ae all the details of the spam email message. Most of these details are hidden by email programs. However, you are usually given the option of displaying them. Many email programs have a menu or toolbar option that you can access in order to \"display headers\" in an email. This is the process of identifying who sent the message with", "Outlook Express: Open the message by clicking on it. Click on the File menu, and select Properties Click on the Details tab in the dialog box that appears. Click on the Message Source button. the process of identifying who sent the message with", "Netscape mail: Open the message by clicking on it. Click on the View menu, and select Message Soruce. This will display all the headers and the text of the email message. To make a copy of the headers and message: Click the right mouse button on the text of the headers. Select \"Select All\" from the pop-up menu. The text will then be \"marked\".", "Click the right mouse button again, and this time choose \"Copy\". A copy of the message and headers is then saved in memory. Close the dialog box. To paste the headers into an email message, compose your message in the normal way. Then click the right mouse button in the text area of your message, and select all Paste all. Now, send it to buse@eim.ae with Subject : Spam complaint. Etisalat will take care of your complaint."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "From where do spammers get my email address?", "answer": ["Etisalat does not sell or otherwise disclose its users email addresses to third parties.", "Spammers use a number of techniques to collect email addresses: One of the most popular sources of email addresses is Usenet (Internet news) newsgroups. This is because your email address is automatically included in your message.", "Your email address on your web site.", "Use of spambot which is a program designed to collect, or harvest, e-mail addresses from the Internet in order to build mailing lists for sending unsolicited e-mail. A spambot can gather e-mail addresses from Web sites, newsgroups, special-interest group (SIG) postings, and chat-room conversations.", "Online competition that requires you to submit your email details. Chat services that require your email address. Spammers have been known to make up email addresses. From a purely statistical viewpoint, if you generate millions of random email addresses, you are likely to create a percentage of valid ones."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I minimize receiving Spam on my Etisalat email account?", "answer": ["There are a number of strategies users can adopt to avoid or minimise spam.", "Keep your email address private especially the one on your business cards.", "Do not send your real email address to any newsgroup or mailing list.", "Always check the privacy act before submitting your real email address.", "Never reply to spam messages because this will confirm that your email address is real.", "Unless it is a mailing list you have subscribed to DO NOT click any unsubscribe links within the email.", "When you publish your email address on your web site, use a form that allows users to submit email messages via your web site."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Where can I get 3rd party software to protect me from Spam?", "answer": ["These are programs which are provided by 3rd party suppliers. Etisalat does not offer any technical support for these suppliers, See the list of resources below:", "Internet Industry Association - National Spam Initiative (Includes free anti spam trial vendors) http://www.iia.net.au/nospam/", "MailTalkX - http://www.softbytelabs.com/", "MailWasher - http://www.mailwasher.net/", "SpamKiller - http://www.spamkiller.com/", "SpamBuster - http://www.contactplus.com/products/spam/spam.html", "SpammerSlammer - http://www.spammerslammer.com/"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I access the contents of my \"Spam\" folder?", "answer": ["To access the contents of your \"Spam\" folder, log on to your Web Mail page and click on the \"Spam\" folder to view its contents. In case you are using other email client (e.g. MS Outlook, MS Outlook Express, Netscape Messenger,.....etc.) and have configured it to use the IMAP protocol, you can subscribe to the \"Spam\" folder to view the messages stored from within your email client.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "When does my FREE Etisalat Internet Mail account become deactive?", "answer": ["Etisalat bundles free email(s) with every Dialup and AlShamil Internet connection services. If these free emails accounts are not accessed for more than four consecutive months, Etisalat might automatically deactivate them. This will result in losing any emails stored in any folder including the Inbox folder. Dialup and AlShamil customers will always enjoy the free email account service. Should your account become deactivated, you can activate it again by visiting www.ecompany.ae/mail/reactivate.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why are some messages deleted from my email account?", "answer": ["etisalat is committed to provide you with the most reliable email service. The ever increasing traffic of electronic mail communication has prompted the formulation of etisalat email Storage and Retention Policy. This is to ensure that you enjoy an increased capacity and functionality of the email service. Messages that are older than 100 days in your Inbox might get removed automatically by the email system. On weekly basis, messages kept in the trash folder that are older than three days might also get removed automatically by the email system\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "I have re-activated my email account, what would my new email password be?", "answer": ["Once you have re-activated your email account successfully, your email password will be reset to be the same as your current Internet Access password\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is POP3, IMAP & SMTP Server?", "answer": ["POP3 (Post Office Protocol 3) is a standard protocol for receiving e-mails. POP3 is a client/server protocol in which e-mail is received and held for you by the Internet server. Periodically, you (or your client e-mail receiver) check your mail-box on the server and download any mail.", "An alternative protocol is Internet Message Access Protocol (IMAP). With IMAP, you view your e-mail at the server as though it was on your client computer. An e-mail message deleted locally is still on the server. E-mail can be kept on and searched at the server. POP can be thought of as a \"store-and-forward\" service. IMAP can be thought of as a remote file server.", "POP and IMAP deal with the receiving of e-mail and are not to be confused with the Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP), a protocol for transferring e-mail across the Internet. You send e-mail with SMTP and a mail handler receives it on your recipient's behalf.", "Then the mail is read using POP or IMAP"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is my email password?", "answer": ["Your email password is the password you use to retrieve your emails using Etisalat web mail client or your own email client. This password is given at the time of subscription to the service and can be changed at any time through the web mail interface.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How can I change my email address?", "answer": ["To Change your email address you will need to change your user ID of your EIM Internet connection account. To do so you will have to submit an application for change of Internet user id by visiting your nearest Etisalat branch. (Fees may apply)\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I able to send but can not receive emails? ", "answer": ["1) Verify that you are entering the correct email password, and that the email client is configured as follows:", "Incoming Mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae", "User ID: username", "2) Check your email forwarding settings from within the web mail interface and make sure that forwarding is not configured. c) Check your email storage quota, if it is completely used then try to free some space by deleting some of the emails stored, or apply for an upgrade to your email storage quota."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Why am I able to receive but can not send emails?", "answer": ["1) Make sure of writing your full email address in lowercase letters in the email address field, and that your email client is configured as follows:", "Outgoing Mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae", "2) Make sure you are sending to a valid email address, any mistake in typing the address can cause this problem"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I configure more than one Email A/C in OutlookExpress?", "answer": ["Yes, please follow the following:", "1) Open Outlook Express, click on Tools - Accounts and select Mail", "2) Click on ADD button and choose the Mail option", "3) Follow the instructions to configure the new email account", "Incoming Mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae", "Outgoing Mail server: mail.emirates.net.ae User ID: username"], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I get more than one email address?", "answer": ["Yes, Etisalat email allows Residential/Individual users to have more than one email account. If you are a Business/Corporate customer you can apply to the Virtual Email where you can have your email at your company domain (e.g. employeename@companydomain.com) All email account(s) can be accessed via a POP3/IMAP email client (e.g. Microsoft Outlook, Netscape, etc.) or from any where in the world via our Etisalat web mail Interface, or even via your WAP/GPRS enabled mobile phone.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "I have deleted all the emails from Outlook Express, Still I am getting emails saying 'Low quota warning' What shall I do?", "answer": ["In such a case, make sure that you do the following: 1 Delete all messages to the Trash folder. 2- Change your email client settings to permanently remove messages in the Trash.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is the use of \"External Mail Option\"? Can I get my hotmail emails by using this?", "answer": ["The use of the \"External Mail Option\" is to provide you with a facility to access your other email accounts that are hosted on mail servers other than the EIM email server. This option can be used with email servers configured to use the POP3 protocol; if your account is hosted on any such server then those messages can be downloaded and viewed at the EIM web Mail\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Can I import my address book from my outlook express? ", "answer": ["Currently, this feature is not supported., however there is a plan to include this as part of our next major upgrade of the EIM Web Mail Service\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Is my address book size inclusive of my mailbox size?", "answer": ["No, this is not the case; your mailbox capacity is available only for your emails.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "I like to check the emails by using outlook express. But before downloading it I want to keep a copy of the mail on the server. How do I do that?", "answer": ["You have two options: 1) Using POP3 you can configure your email client to \"leave messages on server\". Or", "2) Using IMAP you can view your messages directly on the server without the need for downloading them."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "What is the email Alias Service?", "answer": ["The Alias allows you to change your 8 characters email accountl name to a more meaningful name. For example, instead of having your Etisalat email as abc@eim.ae, you can set it to yourfirstname.lastname@eim.ae. You will be able to send and receive emails using your new email alias(es). You can have up to 3 aliases for your email. Once you set your email alias, you will be able to receive emails on both your main email and all aliases email associated to it.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "Experiencing Web mail compatibility issues with your browser?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", ", to access with your existing credential, your email via a different portal, compatible with your browser.", " Your address book will be automatically copied within 24 hours after your first log-in."], "cat": "internet", "sub_cat": "internet_email"},
{"question": "How will I be charged for subscribing to this pack?", "answer": ["When you subscribe to this pack, charging will apply upon 1st usage in eligible countries (not upon subscription)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Where and how will I be able to use the pack?", "answer": ["See below table as quick guide for your pack usability:", "*Preferred country is a destination with at least 1 preferred roaming partner"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What happens if I call a non-preferred country/destination?", "answer": ["The call will proceed but will be charged as per standard roaming rates. We advise you to be aware of the destination you are calling to avoid extra roaming charges."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel (or unsubscribe) the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["Yes, you can unsubscribe from the daily packs as follows:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Through roaming USSD *177#\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Send SMS keywords to 1010 (standard charges apply)\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0- To cancel Daily Combo Plan, send \u201cC RDC\u201d\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0- To cancel Daily Data Plan, send \u201cC RDD\u201d\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Through My etisalat App\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Through our Customer Care by dialing +9718002300 (standard charges apply)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I purchase more than one pack or different types? What is the priority?", "answer": ["Yes, you can simultaneously purchase roaming packages whether similar packs or different packs.\r\n", "\r\nHowever, allowances and validity periods are not cumulative. Usage priority shall be on the higher value.", "Example: Daily Combo Pack + Weekly Combo Pack\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you start a valid roaming usage (whether voice or data), it is consumed first from the Weekly Combo Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 Once data is fully-consumed (but pack is still valid with voice allowances), succeeding data usage will activate the Daily Combo Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you make valid outgoing calls or receive incoming calls, it will consume from the Weekly Combo Pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Will Roaming Callback usages be part of this voice pack allowance?", "answer": ["No. Roaming callback usages will be charged separately as per its standard rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance?", "answer": ["etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage?", "answer": ["When consuming data from a roaming data package, or at a pay-as-you-go rate your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments. Only in Lebanon, your pay-as-you-go roaming data usage without any package, will be rated on a 10 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How will I be charged for subscribing to this pack?", "answer": ["When you subscribe to this pack, charging will be applied immediately but validity starts upon 1st applicable usage in eligible countries (not upon purchase)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Where and how will I be able to use the pack?", "answer": ["See below table as quick guide for your pack usability:", "\u00a0", "*Preferred country is a destination with at least 1 preferred roaming partner"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What happens if I call a non-preferred country/destination?", "answer": ["The call will proceed but will be charged as per standard roaming rates. We advise you to be aware of the destination you are calling to avoid extra roaming charges."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel (or unsubscribe) the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["No. Cancellation of any one-time packs is not allowed."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I purchase more than one pack or different types? What is the priority?", "answer": ["Yes, you can simultaneously purchase roaming packages whether similar packs or different packs.\r\n", "\r\nHowever, allowances and validity periods are not cumulative. Usage priority shall be on the higher value.", "Example: Daily Combo Pack + Weekly Combo Pack\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you start a valid roaming usage (whether voice or data), it is consumed first from the Weekly Combo Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 Once data is fully-consumed (but pack is still valid with voice allowances), succeeding data usage will activate the Daily Combo Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you make valid outgoing calls or receive incoming calls, it will consume from the Weekly Combo Pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Will Roaming Callback usage be part of this voice pack allowance?", "answer": ["No. Roaming callback usage will be charged separately as per its standard rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance?", "answer": ["etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage?", "answer": ["When consuming data from a roaming data package, or at a pay-as-you-go rate your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments. Only in Lebanon, your pay-as-you-go roaming data usage without any package, will be rated on a 10 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How will I be charged for subscribing to this pack?", "answer": ["When you subscribe to this pack, charging will be applied immediately but validity starts upon 1st applicable usage in Saudi Arabia (not upon purchase)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Where and how will I be able to use the pack?", "answer": ["See below quick guide for your pack usability:\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 For data and voice usages, you can connect with any network in KSA (Mobily, STC, Zain)\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When making outgoing voice calls from your pack, you can call UAE + ", "* but excluding satellite, maritime, flight and premium numbers.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0(*Preferred country is a destination with at least 1 preferred roaming partner)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What happens if I call a non-preferred country/destination?", "answer": ["The call will proceed but will be charged as per standard roaming rates. We advise you to be aware of the destination you are calling to avoid extra roaming charges."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel (or unsubscribe) the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["No. Cancellation of any one-time pack is not allowed."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I purchase more than one pack or different types? What is the priority?", "answer": ["Yes, you can simultaneously purchase roaming packages whether similar packs or different packs.\r\n", "\r\nHowever, allowances and validity periods are not cumulative. Usage priority shall be on the higher value.", "Example: Daily Combo Pack + Umrah & Hajj Pack\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you start a valid roaming usage (whether voice or data), it is consumed first from the Umrah & Hajj Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 Once data is fully-consumed (but pack is still valid with voice allowances), succeeding data usage will activate the Daily Combo Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you make valid outgoing calls or receive incoming calls, it will consume from the Umrah & Hajj Pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Will Roaming Callback usage be part of this voice pack allowance?", "answer": ["No. Roaming callback usage will be charged separately as per its standard rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance?", "answer": ["Yes you can. Pack is valid for 2 weeks (14 days) from subscription/activation date & time."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage?", "answer": ["When consuming data from a roaming data package, or at a pay-as-you-go rate your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How will I be charged for subscribing to this pack?", "answer": ["When you subscribe to this pack, charging will be applied immediately but validity starts upon 1st applicable usage in eligible countries (not upon purchase)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Where and how will I be able to use the pack?", "answer": ["See below table as quick guide for your pack usability:", "\u00a0", "*Preferred country is a destination with at least 1 preferred roaming partner"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What happens if I call a non-preferred country/destination?", "answer": ["The call will proceed but will be charged as per standard roaming rates. We advise you to be aware of the destination you are calling to avoid extra roaming charges."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel (or unsubscribe) the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["No. Cancellation of any one-time pack is not allowed."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I purchase more than one pack or different types? What is the priority?", "answer": ["Yes, you can simultaneously purchase roaming packages whether similar packs or different packs.\r\n", "\r\nHowever, allowances and validity periods are not cumulative. Usage priority shall be on the higher value.", "Example: Daily Combo Pack + Economy Class Pack\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you start a valid roaming usage (whether voice or data), it is consumed first from the Economy Class Pack.\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 Once data is fully-consumed (but pack is still valid with voice allowances), succeeding data usage will activate the Daily Combo Pack\r\n", "\r\n\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 When you make valid outgoing calls or receive incoming calls, it will consume from the Economy Class Pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Will Roaming Callback usage be part of this voice pack allowance?", "answer": ["No. Roaming callback usage will be charged separately as per its standard rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance?", "answer": ["etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage?", "answer": ["When consuming data from a roaming data package, or at a pay-as-you-go rate your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments. Only in Lebanon, your pay-as-you-go roaming data usage without any package, will be rated on a 10 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What are the Voice Roaming packs offered by Etisalat & their benefit?", "answer": ["Etisalat offers a wide range of incoming voice roaming packs giving you a unique saving plan to receive calls for as low as 0.5 AED/Min."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Where can we use the pack?", "answer": ["Pack covers all travel destinations; excluding satellite, maritime & flight operators. (Almost 700 roaming partners in more than 200 countries). Please ", " to view the list of all Etisalat Roaming Partners and the availability of roaming services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What is the eligibility for subscription?", "answer": ["All Etisalat post-paid & pre-paid customers (Consumer & Business) are eligible."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Do I need to have roaming service activated?", "answer": ["Yes. Post-paid customers should have full roaming or special roaming service enabled prior to subscription.", "Prepaid subscribers must have enough balance to cover the pack fee prior to subscription."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How do I purchase Etisalat's Incoming Voice Roaming Pack?", "answer": ["It's simple to purchase the voice packs. You can use any of the following 3 methods:", "- Dial *177# (can be done from UAE or abroad).\r\n", "\r\n- Text the desired SMS purchase code (below listed) to 1010 from UAE or abroad.\r\n"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How can I check my pack status?", "answer": ["You can always inquire about usage/pack via *177#.", "Also SMS will be sent to the customers in case of:\r\n", "\r\n- Consuming 100% of pack allowance before time expiry\r\n", "\r\n- Time expiry before consuming the full allowance"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I purchase the pack before traveling?", "answer": ["Yes, we advise you to do so.", "Pack validity starts only from first terminated call received abroad as below:\r\n", "\r\n- Weekly voice pack: Valid form 1st terminated call abroad until end of 7 days.\r\n", "\r\n- Monthly voice pack: Valid form 1st terminated call abroad until end of 30 days."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["No. It is not allowed to cancel the pack as it is a one time subscription."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I buy more than one voice pack at the same time?", "answer": ["No. It is not allowed to have the same pack subscribed more than once at the same time. You can repurchase the same pack after the old one expires."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I re-purchase Voice Roaming Packs?", "answer": ["You can re-purchase them once:\r\n", "\r\n- If the pack is expires due to time validity (day/week) or\r\n", "\r\n- The consumption of incoming voice allowance is before the time validity (day/week)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How can I view & purchase any other roaming pack?", "answer": ["By dialling *177# or sending ROAME (for English) or ROAMA (for Arabic) to 1010 for SMS purchase codes. Detailed information is also available on ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Do I need to have roaming service activated?", "answer": ["Yes. Post-paid customers should have full roaming or special roaming service enabled prior subscription.", "Prepaid subscribers must have enough balance to cover the pack fee prior to subscription."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I purchase the pack before traveling?", "answer": ["Yes, we advise you to do so.", "Pack validity starts only from first internet access abroad until end of 30 days"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I cancel the pack after purchasing?", "answer": ["No. It is not allowed to cancel the pack as it is a one time subscription."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How can I view & purchase any other roaming pack?", "answer": ["By dialling *177# or sending ROAME (for English) or ROAMA (for Arabic) to 1010 for SMS purchase codes. Detailed information is also available on ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance?", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion \u2013\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes\r\n"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage?", "answer": ["When consuming data from a roaming data package, or at a pay-as-you-go rate your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments. Only in Lebanon, your pay-as-you-go roaming data usage without any package, will be rated on a 10 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What is International Roaming?", "answer": ["International Roaming lets you use your mobile phone to make calls when travelling outside the UAE. You can easily reach your family and business colleagues back home as well as make calls to anywhere in the world."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How to call a number in another country whilst International Roaming?", "answer": ["If you are roaming in the UK and would like to call someone in Dubai on telephone number, you need to dial as follows:\r\n", "\r\n+971 4 xxxxxxx = (country code) + (area code) + (number you wish to call).\r\n", "\r\nPlease add '+' before the country code while dialing any number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How to call a number in the same (visited) country whilst International Roaming?", "answer": ["If you are roaming in the UK and want to call someone in the UK (London) on telephone number, you need to dial as follows:\r\n", "\r\n0207 xxxxxxx = (London area code) + (number you wish to call)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance?", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion \u2013\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes\r\n"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage?", "answer": ["When consuming data from a roaming data package, or at a pay-as-you-go rate your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments. Only in Lebanon, your pay-as-you-go roaming data usage without any package, will be rated on a 10 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat Roaming Callback Service?", "answer": ["Etisalat introduced a callback service allowing customers to make calls while roaming at very special flat rate of AED 3/min using a USSD string to convert the outgoing call to an incoming one. With this service, we offer price discount of up to 77% on charges of outgoing direct roaming calls.", "With the new Etisalats Roaming Callback App, you can initiate a callback to any number within the visited country, UAE or other countries without the need to manually dial the USSD callback code each time you make a call."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Does the flat rate cover all outgoing calls?", "answer": ["The number called can be within the UAE, the visited country or any other IDD numbers (excluding calls to satellite, maritime and premium numbers).", "However, video calls are not supported."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How can customers avail of this special rate?", "answer": ["No opt-in/activation is required. Flat rate is offered by default to all postpaid and prepaid customers, consumers and business."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How does this Roaming Callback service work?", "answer": ["\u2022 Just download the Etisalat Roaming Callback App for free from Google Play store or Apple App store (for iOS 9 and above) based on your device and install\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Select a contact from your contact list and make a call normally\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 A pop-up will notify you about receiving an incoming call from Etisalat, showing your own number\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Accept this call to connect you immediately with the desired destination/number and enjoy the special rate of outgoing call"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What are the benefits of Etisalat Roaming Callback Application?", "answer": ["\u2022 No need to opt-in. Just download the Etisalat Roaming Callback App for free, install and use\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Hassle-free dialling\u2013 no need to manually dial the USSD codes and contact number anymore\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 No data connection required to use the App\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Displays the same contact list from your native phone book\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Added features like recent call history and USSD-ready dialpad for unsaved numbers\r\n"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "How will I enjoy the service if I don\u2019t have an Apple or Android smartphone?", "answer": ["Even if you don\u2019t have an Apple or Android smartphone, you can still make an outgoing roaming call at this special flat rate through callback service by dialling*145*00(CountryCode)(PhoneNumber)# and then pressing the call button.", "You can also use either \u201c+\u201d or \u201c00\u201d e.g. If you are roaming in the UK, dial *145*009715XXXXXXXX# (to call an Etisalat number) or *145*0096611YYYYYYY# (to call a landline in KSA\u2013 Riyadh)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I enjoy this roaming callback service anywhere?", "answer": ["The Roaming Callback service is offered by Etisalat across 188 countries through more than 600 partner networks. For the list of roaming partners and availability of roaming services, please visit ", ".", "Please note that the Roaming Callback service code *145* could be blocked by some of the operators or used for their local services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What happens if I use this service in a destination barred by Etisalat?", "answer": ["You will be notified (via flash message) \"Callback cannot be initiated through this operator, please try another one.\""], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What happens if I call a barred number?", "answer": ["You will be notified (via flash message) \"Callback cannot be initiated to dialled destination.\""], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I also use this callback service while in the UAE?", "answer": ["No, the service is only allowed while roaming."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Can I use my voice roaming pack for USSD callback?", "answer": ["No, USSD calls will not be deducted from your roaming pack allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "Will these USSD callback calls appear in my bill/invoice?", "answer": ["Yes, they will be billed in your postpaid account as \"Roaming Callback\"."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_roaming"},
{"question": "What is 2G to 3G Device Trade-Up Program?", "answer": ["2G to 3G Trade-Up Program is an offer for Etisalat customers where they can trade in their old 2G/3G devices in working condition to get upfront discount on purchase of new BE phones with 6 months free 100 MB/month data plan offer. This offer would be available from selected Etisalat Business centers/outlets, selected key retail locations and independent retailers. This offer would be applicable only against purchase of a new BE phone from Etisalat. Customers can get a brand new Android based BE smart phone at AED. 299/- by giving away their old working mobile phone."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Which old mobile phones are acceptable?", "answer": ["Any mobile phone in working condition. The device should be able to turn on and off."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What if the phone is not switching on?", "answer": ["If the phone is not in working condition then it is not eligible for trade up."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What if the phone is switching on and working, but has crack on the body?", "answer": ["Phone is acceptable."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "How to check the IMEI validity?", "answer": ["Type *#06# and check if that number matches with the IMEI mentioned on the back side of the phone."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can non Etisalat customers trade in a device and purchase a new device?", "answer": ["Yes. Customer need to buy a new Etisalat number first and trade-in their old device against purchase of a new BE phones."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "How to clear personal information and data from the device?", "answer": ["Most devices allow erasing all of personal data - contact list, photos, text messages, etc. -and resetting the device to its factory settings. Just refer to the owner's manual or the manufacturer's website.", "Please make sure to remove any user locks, or set the password to 0000, before submitting the device."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Should the customer submit charger and other accessories?", "answer": ["No. Only the device with the battery in the unit is required to be traded up."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "When will the customer buy the new BE phone after submitting old phone?", "answer": ["Immediately over the counter."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can the customer buy the new BE phone and come back later to submit old device?", "answer": ["No. Customer should submit the old device before purchasing the new BE phone."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What if a business or a company is interested and would like to submit multiple devices?", "answer": ["They should bring all devices to the outlet and follow the same procedure for each device to purchase new BE phones."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Is it possible to purchase multiple BE phones against one old phone?", "answer": ["No. Only one new Be Social 4 phone can be purchased against one old device."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Is it possible to purchase other products against trade-up?", "answer": ["No. Only Be Social 4 phone can be purchased."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What if the customer says that his old phone is more valuable than new BE phone?", "answer": ["It is upto the customer to purchase BE phone against his old phone."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Is the customer allowed to ask for the device back once submitted for trade-up?", "answer": ["No. Customer will not be able to ask the device back once the form is signed. Transaction is full and final."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Does the customer get a refund if he changes his mind after the purchase of BE phone?", "answer": ["No. Trade-up once completed is full and final."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What is 3.5G Router? ", "answer": ["The Etisalat 3.5G Router is simply a super speed connecting device that can be plugged into\r\n", "\r\n- any PC or laptop for single user mode, or\r\n", "\r\n- plugged into the power socket for multi user mode to provide Internet connection up to 7.2Mbps over HSDPA network (High Speed Downlink Packet Access)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I install the 3.5G Router myself? ", "answer": ["The 3.5G Router is a plug and play device and installs the software by itself once you have plugged it into the PC or laptop. There are no other drivers or software required."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What are the minimum requirements for my PC or laptop to work with the 3.5G Router?", "answer": ["The following are the minimum requirements for the 3.5G Router:\r\n", "\r\n- Any PC or laptop with at least one free USB interface\r\n", "\r\n- CPU: Pentium 500MHz or above\r\n", "\r\n- Memory: 128MB RAM or above\r\n", "\r\n- Hard Disk: 50MB free disk space\r\n", "\r\n- Operating system: Windows 2000/XP/Vista\r\n", "\r\n- Display resolution: 800*600 pixels or above 1024*768 is recommended)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use the 3.5G Router overseas?", "answer": ["Yes. You can use the router overseas provided there is HSDPA / 3G / GPRS coverage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can the Internet connection, using the 3.5G router, be shared with my family?", "answer": ["Yes. The router is portable and can be used with any laptop or PC."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What do the LED lights represent?", "answer": ["Your router shows you its network status with a small coloured light. This LED is handy to see your current connection type & status at a glance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What else do I need to use start using this product?", "answer": ["All you need to have is the router, insert a 3G SIM card in the device and plug it into any PC or laptop that needs to be provided with an Internet connection."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Do I need a specific SIM card?", "answer": ["Yes. You need a 3G USIM card. Or, you can apply for a new GSM Data line connection dedicated for Internet access and SMS services only; all other calls and services - such as video call, voice call, etc. including incoming calls will be disabled. This option is suitable for those users who wish to have a special card dedicated for Internet access via laptop."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What are the different service schemes available?", "answer": ["There are two different price plans to choose from:\r\n", "\r\nPay as You Use: This is suitable if your usage varies every month and if you do not wish to make an upfront payment every month.\r\n", "\r\nData bundles: This provides a certain amount of data per month for a fixed fee with additional usage charged separately. Data bundles are suitable if your usage is consistent every month and you want to control your monthly cost. Medium and high packages are available for data users. ."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use a SIM card from other operators on the Router?", "answer": ["No, 3.5G Routers delivered by Etisalat are SIM locked and cannot be used with other operators."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Where can I purchase the 3.5G Router?", "answer": ["3.5G Routers are available in the commercial stores of Etisalat main Business Centers or at retail outlets across the UAE."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Will my 3.5G router work with Windows Vista?", "answer": ["Yes. 3.5G Routers are Vista ready and are supported by Windows Vista."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What is the 3.5G USB Modem? ", "answer": ["Eltisalat USB Modem is a perfect option for Internet access on the go. This innovative product features an eye-catching stylish design and great speeds that can be used on laptops as well as on desktop computers. The 3.5G modem provides you with wireless Internet access."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I install the Data USB Modem myself? ", "answer": ["The 3.5G Modem is a plug and play device and installs the software by itself once you have plugged it into the PC or laptop. There are no other drivers or software required."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What are the minimum requirements for my PC or laptop to work with Data USB Modem?", "answer": ["The minimum requirements for the 3.5G USB modem are as follows: Any PC or laptop with", "- at least one free USB interface", "- CPU: Pentium 500MHz or above", "- Memory: 128MB RAM or above", "- Hard Disk: 50MB free disk space", "- Operating system: Windows 2000/XP/Vista", "- Display resolution: 800*600 pixels or above 1024*768 is recommended)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use the Data USB Modem overseas?", "answer": ["Yes. You can use the router in those countries where the mobile operator provides HSDPA / 3G / GPRS coverage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can the Internet connection, using the 3.5G USB Modem, be shared with my family?", "answer": ["Yes. The router is portable and can be used on any laptop or PC, subject to the minimum requirements mentioned above."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Why am I getting the message \"Modem not responding\"?", "answer": ["What is the maximum number of characters in an SMS text message? Each message can contain 70 Arabic characters or 1000 characters in English. However, while sending, the messages are broken down into 160 characters per message for English."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What do the LED lights represent?", "answer": ["Your USB Modem shows you its network status with a small coloured light. This LED is handy to see your current connection type & status at a glance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What else do I need to use start using this product?", "answer": ["Besides the USB modem you will need a 3G SIM card. Insert the 3G SIM card in the device and plug into any PC or laptop that needs to be provided with an Internet connection."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Do I need a specific SIM card?", "answer": ["Yes, you need a 3G USIM card. Or, you can apply for a new GSM data line connection dedicated for Internet access and SMS services only; all other calls and services - such as video calls, voice calls, etc. including incoming calls will be disabled. This option is suitable for those users who wish to have a special card dedicated for Internet access via laptop."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What are the different service schemes available?", "answer": ["There are two different price plans to choose from: Pay as You Use: This is suitable if your usage varies every month and if you do not wish to make an upfront payment every month. Data bundles: This provides a certain amount of data per month for a fixed fee with additional usage charged separately. Data bundles are suitable if your usage is consistent every month and you want to control your monthly cost. Medium and high packages are available for data users."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use a SIM card from other operators on the USB Modem?", "answer": ["No, the 3.5G Modems delivered by Etisalat are SIM locked and cannot be used with other operators."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Where can I purchase the USB Modem?", "answer": ["USB Modems are available in all the commercial stores of Etisalat main Business Centers or at retail outlets across the UAE."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Will my 3.5G modem work with Windows Vista?", "answer": ["Yes. 3.5G USB Modems are Windows Vista enabled and are supported by Windows Vista."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What is MobileCam? ", "answer": ["It is a camera in which one can insert a SIM card and can monitor the camera from a handset. Moreover, the camera can be adjusted from the mobile i.e. adjust the angle, brightness and zoom of the camera."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What type of SIM card can I insert in the camera?", "answer": ["You should insert a 3G prepaid or postpaid SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Do I need a special handset for the MobileCam Service? ", "answer": ["Yes, you need to have a 3G handset to be able to use this service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What do I need to use this service? ", "answer": ["All you need to have is a MobileCam device. Insert a SIM card which supports the 3G service in the device and enjoy the service from your 3G handset."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Where can I get a MobileCam?", "answer": ["MobileCams is available in the commercial stores of Etisalat main business centers. Retailers will be appointed soon."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can a prepaid subscriber use the Mobile CAM service? ", "answer": ["Yes, provided the user has subscribed to the video call service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What are the service charges? ", "answer": ["Charges will be based on the normal video calls tariff. No additional charges are applicable."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What is the MobileCam device priced at?", "answer": ["The MobileCam with amazing features is offered at AED 799/-."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Is it possible for others to use my MobileCam?", "answer": ["Yes, you can add 20 numbers of individuals who can use the same camera."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I block anyone from using the camera? And how? ", "answer": ["Yes you can. You should access the main menu in the camera and enter the \u2018Delete User\u2019 interface or send an SMS command to the camera."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use SIM card from other operators on the MobileCam device? ", "answer": ["No, all MobileCam devices delivered by Etisalat are SIM locked and can not be used with other operators."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I record using the camera from my mobile? How? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can. You should access the main menu in the camera and enter the \u2018Video Recording\u2019 interface."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Where will the recorded file be saved? How can I open it? ", "answer": ["The recorded file will be saved in the T-Flash card. You can open it by using the card reader in the PC."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I change the camera administrator of the camera? How?", "answer": ["Yes you can, you should access the main menu in the camera and enter the \u2018Administrator Change\u2019 interface or send an SMS command to the camera."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Do I need to enter any password when I access the camera? ", "answer": ["Yes, the camera administrator will be prompted to enter the user\u2019s PIN code (the default PIN code is 0000) followed by * key."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I change the PIN number used for accessing the camera? ", "answer": ["Yes you can, you should access the main menu in the camera and enter the \u2018Change PIN\u2019 interface or send an SMS command to the camera."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What if I forget my PIN Code? ", "answer": ["Visit the nearest Etisalat Business Center for assistance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "How can I find out if my area supports 4G LTE network?", "answer": ["Etisalat covers the widest coverage in UAE almost 0% of the populated area.", "You can check if your area is within the network by clicking ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can the Wifi coverage be affected by any factor?", "answer": ["Yes, even within a coverage area, many factors, including location factors (indoor/outdoor), frequency differences, and device capability, building materials, foliage and weather which may cause a drop in connections, slower data speeds affect availability and quality of service or otherwise impact the quality of services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What type of SIM Cards will I use?", "answer": ["You will require data Sim cards to be inserted in to the Wifi or USB modem. (Data SIM Cards are available for AED 25)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use Etisalat internet devices with non Etisalat data SIM cards?", "answer": ["Etisalat internet devices are compatible with Etisalat network only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What happens when I complete my contract?", "answer": ["Any customer that completes the 6 or 12 month's contract can either:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What if I want to cancel my contract at any time and keep the device?", "answer": ["Any customer on a contract who wishes to cancel/terminate his line will have to pay all remaining amount in his contract before terminating the line.", "The remaining amount in the contract will be automatically by the system and sales will be able to share the amount with sub before confirming the cancellation."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "Can I use My Data Plan packages while roaming? ", "answer": ["The included Data volume is limited to local only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "I am subscribed to the Hard cap, will I be able to use the daily free data between 12:00-03:00 am, if I consumed the allocated data?", "answer": ["Yes, you can enjoy Free Data hour even if you have consumed the subscribed data pack, with or without hard cap"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_modems"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat's eLife AnA Emarati offer?", "answer": ["It's an exclusive giveaway of benefits worth around AED 3000 to Emarati Nationals on eLife 3.0 Value Packs. This offer is applicable for our eLife Value Pack Emarati Nationals, as applicable, and comprises of:\r\n", "\r\n- Free Speed Booster up to 100 Mbps\r\n", "\r\n- Free special landline number\r\n", "\r\n- 2nd home, 50% monthly rental discount (upto AED 200)"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "My nationality is not UAE. Can I avail this benefit?", "answer": ["Sorry, this offer is exclusive for UAE nationals."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "I already have a landline number? Can I change this?", "answer": ["Yes. You can change this once, free-of-cost. What's more, we also provide a free change number announcement for 3 months with this. After 3 months, the free change number announcement alone will be removed.", "Subsequent number change requests (more than once) will be charged as per the standard rates."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Do I need to subscribe to receive the eLife AnA Emarati Offer?", "answer": ["Yes. Customers of Emarati nationality have to subscribe to eLife Value Packs to get the eLife AnA Emarati benefits mentioned in this document."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "I have an standalone eLife landline or eLife broadband or eLife TV. Can I get the eLife AnA Emarati benefits?", "answer": ["Sorry; Benefits are given only to eLife Value Packs. Namely, Basic, Sports, Movies, or Premium.", "You can also avail the offer if you are an eLife Lite customer, but, you will only enjoy specific benefits."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "I am an eLife Premium Value Pack customer. Why is my free speed booster only providing me with 100Mbps speed?", "answer": ["This promotion only provides a maximum of 100Mbps home broadband speed."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "When will the promotion start and end?", "answer": ["This is an ongoing promotion and Emarati customers will continue to enjoy these benefits."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Will my router support the increased speeds being offered as part of the free speed booster?", "answer": ["Nearly all routers on our network support the increased speed. You can check your routers compatibility by calling 101 - our customer service agents will be able to advise on your specific configuration."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "I already have an existing speed booster. What happens to this?", "answer": ["Your existing speed booster will be made free. As per current product design, you will not be able to purchase more than one speed booster."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "How do I avail the 50% discount on my 2nd home?", "answer": ["You can get 50% rental discount up to a maximum of AED 200 on your second eLife connection. This is applicable only for your second connection and not for any further additional connections. The second eLife connection should be an eLife Lite / 3.0 bundle and should be equal or less than the primary interims rental to avail this discount.", "Two or more customers cannot select the same eLife account as the second account."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Will I notice the difference in speed?", "answer": ["Absolutely. For those customers with Etisalat-provided routers, there will be a significant noticeable difference in speed as you will now enjoy double Internet speeds. The maximum speed you will get free as part of eLife AnA Emarati is 100Mbps."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What is the exit penalty?", "answer": ["eLife has a minimum period of hire. If you opt to leave within this, you will be charged an exit penalty as applicable.", "As an eLife AnA Emarati customer, this clause will be waived for your subscription.", "However:\r\n", "\r\n- Exit charges for devices bought within eLife and also for the devices given as part of the eLife contract will continue to be applicable.", "To learn more, contact our customer service representative in our business center / 101"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What is Ana Emarati Satellite bundle and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["Ana Emarati Satellite is a new postpaid bundle based on satellite communication technology that is known for global outdoor coverage and is targeted at customers looking to go beyond boundaries. This bundle includes call minutes and SMS that can be made using the satellite network and is renewable on a monthly basis.", "To use this technology, you would need a satellite adaptor device, which Etisalat can provide for free should you opt for the contract plan. Normally, satellite communication to the UAE costs around AED 15 per minute. However, with the Ana Emarati Satellite bundle, it will cost you just AED 1.5\u2014which means a whopping 90 per cent discount. Ana Emarati Satellite bundle offers you the best value for money while keeping you in touch with your family and friends during your adventures."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What is the difference between satellite and GSM coverage? ", "answer": ["GSM coverage is based on a group of antenna towers that broadcast the GSM signal in certain areas to enable a phone connection. However, for a satellite network, the satellite station is located 35 thousand kilometres above ground level, which allows for global coverage. So, wherever you will go around the earth, your phone will be able to communicate regardless of your geographic location."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Who is eligible for Ana Emarati Satellite bundle?", "answer": ["Any postpaid customer can activate the Ana Emarati Satellite bundle with his/her postpaid line."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "How is Ana Emarati Satellite bundle beneficial to me?", "answer": ["Some of the benefits include:", "\u2022 Ultimate connectivity with your family and friends to tell your story from remote areas and beyond boundaries\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 FREE additional SIM card with your same number to make satellite calls\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Great savings"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What does Ana Emarati Satellite bundle include and how much it costs?", "answer": ["The Ana Emarati Satellite bundle includes the below auto-renewed monthly benefits:", "With every SatSleeve hotspot device you will get a FREE additional SIM card with your same number to be used inside the device."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to the Ana Emarati Satellite bundle?", "answer": ["To subscribe, you would first need to buy the SatSleeve hotspot device from any Etisalat outlet and then activate the satellite add-on.", "To activate:\r\n", "\r\nThrough SMS, send sat to 1012\r\n", "\r\nThrough USSD, dial *140#"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "How do I check my satellite bundle balance?", "answer": ["You can check your bundle balance at any time. Just send TB to 1012 or use the USSD code *140#", "However, once you deplete your bundle 100%, you will receive a notification of the same."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What will happen after I consume one or all of my benefits?", "answer": ["You will be charged for out of bundle rate as below:", "\u2022 Out of bundle rate for the satellite minute is AED 2\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Out of bundle rate for the satellite SMS is AED 1"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What will happen to the Ana Emarati satellite bundle after my 12 months contract is over?", "answer": ["During your 12-month contract period you will pay AED 300 per month against 100 minutes (outgoing/incoming) and 100 SMS on satellite network, after which the monthly rental will be reduced to AED 150 and the satellite hotspot device is totally yours."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "How do I set-up my SatSleeve hotspot device and make my first satellite call?", "answer": ["1. Download and open the Thuraya SatSleeve Hotspot app on your smartphone.\r\n", "\r\n2. Insert your FREE secondary SIM in the SatSleeve device.\r\n", "\r\n3. Switch on your SatSleeve device by pressing the power button for 3 seconds.\r\n", "\r\n4. Turn on your smartphone Wi-Fi and connect to the satellite unit (SATxxxxxxx). Your default password is 12345678.\r\n", "\r\n5. Go to an open area and fully extend the antenna on the satellite unit.\r\n", "\r\n6. Thuraya network will connect automatically.\r\n", "\r\n7. Dial *105# from the hotspot app to activate the SIM inside the SatSleeve device as the primary one.\r\n", "\r\n8. All your outgoing/incoming satellite calls will be consumed from your satellite bundle.\r\n", "\r\n9. If you want to disconnect from the Thuraya network please remember to change your primary SIM again to the one inside your smartphone by dialling *105#.\r\n", "\r\n10. To know which SIM card is primary, dial *#105#."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "How much do I pay for the additional SIM card that I get upon purchasing the SatSleeve hotspot device?", "answer": ["The additional SIM is totally FREE with no monthly renewal and it holds your same number."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Can I use the SatSleeve hotspot with any other postpaid number? ", "answer": ["Yes you can, but you need to activate the satellite bundle on that number. Any satellite calls made will display the mobile number inside the SatSleeve."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Can I activate the satellite bundle on a Wasel line? ", "answer": ["No, the satellite bundle is only available with a postpaid plan."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Are there any excluded destinations when using the satellite minutes/SMS?", "answer": ["You can use your satellite minutes to call any UAE number (fixed/mobile) or international number (fixed/mobile). However, calls/SMS to satellite/premium numbers/short codes are excluded from the bundle and normal rates will apply."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "What will happen to the Ana Emarati satellite bundle if I move to another postpaid tariff plan?", "answer": ["You have the freedom to move to any consumer tariff plan and the bundle will remain active. However, if you move to a prepaid or business plan, this will be treated as an early termination of the contract and you will be charged AED 150 multiplied by the remaining months."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Which smartphone models can be used with the Thuraya SatSleeve Hotspot?", "answer": ["The following smartphone models have been tested:", "(iOS 6, 7, 8 and 9)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 4\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 4s\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 5\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 5s\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 5c\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 6\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 6 plus\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 6s\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPhone 6s plus\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPad Air\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 iPod Touch\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\nAndroid\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy S3\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy S4\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy S5\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy S6\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy Note 3\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy Note 5\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy Note Edge\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1\u201d 2014 edition tablet\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy A8\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy J7\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy E7\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Samsung Galaxy Alpha (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Huawei Honor 4C (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Huawei Ascend G750\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Huawei Y635\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 HTC One M8 (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 HTC Desire Eye (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Sony Xperia Z1 (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Sony Xperia Z2 (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 CAT S50 smartphone (tested with Android 4.4)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Asus Memo Pad 8 ME180A tablet"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "ana_emarati_faqs"},
{"question": "Can I avail eLifeTV plus if I have already a Personal Video Recorder Set Top Box?", "answer": ["Yes, additional charge will apply. You can choose if you want your STB to record your TV programs on the Local PVR Hard Disk or with eLifeTV Plus."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What is the new eLife TV experience?", "answer": ["eLife TV now has a new user interface that will allow easy navigation and enhanced content discovery. The new experience also includes more details and information on movies and TV shows including IMDb ratings and the advanced recommendation feature will recommend to you movies and TV shows based on your selected favorites or previous viewership."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How do I get the new experience?", "answer": ["The new eLife TV experience is limited to the latest Technicolor- manufactured eLife TV Box (STB). Older boxes do not support this new interface."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What is the \"Popular Channels\" category in the new UI? ", "answer": ["These are the channels that are most watched at that particular point in time on eLifeTV over the entire subscriber base. This lists gets updated every 10 to 15 mins."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What is Trending in the new UI?", "answer": ["These are movies and TV shows that are gaining popularity. It includes OnDemand movies, Catch Up content, TV Channels and Video Packs."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What is being recommended to me in the new UI?", "answer": ["This section shows all recommended content from movies, TV shows and Sports based on your previous viewership and is customized for each profile."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What is Last Viewed in the new UI?", "answer": ["What you have watched lately will appear under this section and will include movies, TV shows from OnDemand, Catch Up, Live TV Channels and Video Packs. Each section has a progress bar that shows where you reached in viewing that particular content (for OnDemand, Catch Up and Video Packs) and for Live TV the progress bar will show the status of the program running on the channel (time lapsed)."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Where can I access Catch Up TV?", "answer": ["While Catch Up TV content will be available under most sections, for specific access to Catch Up TV content, with the menu button on the remote control please select \"TV\" and then move right using the arrow keys to select \"Catch Up\". The \u201cdate\u201d and \u201cTV channel\u201d selection options will then appear on the screen."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Where can I access OnDemand Movies?", "answer": ["With the menu button on the remote control please select \u201cMovies\u201d and then move right using the arrow keys to select any of the sub sections or simply select Movies and move up / down to view the titles available under each section."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Where can I access Video Packs?", "answer": ["While content from Video Packs is available under most sections, for specific access to Video Packs, with the menu button on the remote control please select \"My Media\" and then move right using the arrow keys to select \"Video Packs\"."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Why it is recommended to create multiple profiles?", "answer": ["User profile is a key feature that helps you personalize your experience. Having configured this, you can keep track and customize of all your purchases, bookmarks, last viewed content, recommendations, favorites etc. With multiple users at home, using same set top box, each user can personalize & manage their TV experience better by logging on to their individual profiles."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How do I set my profiles?", "answer": ["With the menu button on the remote control please select \"Settings\" and then you may create new profiles or edit existing profiles. The default profile is Admin and the default password is 1111. Once profiles are created you may simply switch profiles from the top most icon in the menu bar. You can create up to 10 user profiles."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Do I need always to enter my PIN code to login or content rentals?", "answer": ["PIN code is an optional feature that is available if you want to protect your profile or rentals. You can enable or disable PIN code requirement from setting page. For each profile you can independently mange PIN code setting for both Login and rentals."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What should I do, if I forget or lost my PIN code?", "answer": ["If you lost your admin's profile PIN code, please call \"101\" and our support agents will help you reset your PIN. However, if you forgot the sub-profile PIN, login with \"Admin\" profile, go to \"Setting\", and select the profile you want to reset their PIN code for and simply update the PIN code, and then \"Save\"."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How to hide channels that I am not subscribed to? ", "answer": ["This feature is available for all live TV channels. Please press \"OK\" on the eLife remote to bring \"Channel List\", then press \"Green Button\" on your remote to bring channel filter pop up. Change \"All Channels\" to \"My Subscriptions\", then \"OK\""], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "I cannot control the Audio for some channel even if reduce the volume on the STB remote? ", "answer": ["This case happens with specific TV manufacturers or models due to compatibility with Dolby Audio. To solve it, please do the following: go to \"Setting\", then \"Preferences\", then \"Audio Output\" and change it to \"Stereo\"."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How can I change the interface color?", "answer": ["To fine tune the interface's color to better suit your home setup, please go to \"Setting\", then \"Preferences\", then \"Themes\" and select your prefered \"Theme\"."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What if I don\u2019t have the new eLife TV box / STB (Technicolor)?", "answer": ["If you do not have the latest Technicolor Box, you may continue to enjoy the existing user interface."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What are the terms and conditions if I want to upgrade to the new STB and how do I request for this? ", "answer": ["You may request for an additional eLife TV Box to get access to this new eLife experience."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How can I control Live TV?", "answer": ["- Pause Live TV for up to 120 minutes, then play and resume the paused program.\r\n", "\r\n- Fast-forward your paused program or simply press the stop button to catch-up with Live TV.\r\n", "\r\n- Rewind and repeat your favorite parts of the program. - Pause Live TV for up to 120 minutes, then play and resume the paused program.\r\n", "\r\n- Fast-forward your paused program or simply press the stop button to catch-up with Live TV.\r\n", "\r\n- Rewind and repeat your favorite parts of the program."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How many hours of TV content can I record?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "This will depend on the type of Set Top Box (STB), but the average is up to 60 hours of video \u2013 (SD & HD combination)."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "What are the recording choices I have?", "answer": ["\r\n            ", " - You can record one live channel while simultaneously watching another.", " - Pick your favorite programs from the Program Guide and record them."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How do I see how much recording space I have left?", "answer": ["Press \"Menu\" key on your remote control, then press the Up Arrow Key to launch the system menu, navigate using the left / right arrow keys and select hard disk information."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "If I pause live TV on one channel, then change to another channel for a bit, can I go back to watch what I missed on the first channel?", "answer": ["No, if you change the channel the saved material will be that of the new channel."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "If a Call Display onscreen pop-up appears during a recording or if I view the menu screen, will these images be recorded?", "answer": ["No, it will only record the program you are watching."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Can I record On Demand (VOD)?", "answer": ["No you cannot record On Demand."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "If my STB is on stand-by, will it still record a future program?", "answer": ["Yes, the STB will turn on to start recording and turn off when the recording is completed."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "If I reboot my STB will I lose my future scheduled recordings?", "answer": ["No, all of this information will be saved."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Can I watch a previously recorded program while recording a new one?", "answer": ["Yes, recorded material is stored on your STB's hard drive and watching it does not interfere with recording live TV."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How to pair my Bluetooth device with my STB?", "answer": ["Click on the following link to learn how to pair your Bluetooth device."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "I have a my own game pad, can I use it with eLife TV Gaming?", "answer": ["Specific USB and Bluetooth GamePads from the retail market that use standard protocols are compatible with eLife TV Gaming, please click on this link for a not so exhaustive list of the controller that have been tested and confirmed to be working with eLife TV Gaming."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "How long will the GamePad that I order on TV or on the Wed take to reach me at Home?", "answer": ["etisalat appointment center will call you for appointment within 24 hours."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Can I use the etisalat controller with my PC ? ", "answer": ["Yes, you just need to change the front switch of the controller to \u201cD\u201d mode (X mode for eLife TV Gaming)."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "My controller is not working?", "answer": ["Try replacing the AAA batteries with new ones. If the problem persists, please call 101 and they will assist you with finding the nearest after-sales point."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "I cannot play games in multiplayers mode?", "answer": ["Multiplayer gaming at home or with other subscribers is under development and will be made available soon."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elifetv_faqs"},
{"question": "Having problems with your iPhone? ", "answer": ["Please log on the link ", " and troubleshoot your particular concern. Should there be a need for you to drop your phone for repair or further assistance, you can use the link For full list ", " to locate the nearest Apple After Sales Service Center to you or call Apple UAE contact center at 8000 444 0407 for further support.\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "What is flexible minutes?", "answer": ["Flexible minutes is a new type of add-on introduced by etisalat, it allows you to make local, international calls & receive calls while roaming as well from the same bundle."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "Can I upgrade/downgrade between different packages in etisalat smartphones plans?", "answer": ["Yes you can as per the matrix below. However upgrade/downgrade between available plans is allowed only once, during your contract."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to different postpaid add ons such as preferred number add on? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "Can I cancel my contract at any point of time? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can. However, if you cancel your contract before completing the full period, you will be liable to pay exit charges for the remaining months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "Which day of the month would I receive my monthly allowance from voice minutes & data?", "answer": ["On the first of every month, we will reset your account and provide you with your subscribed voice minutes & data."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "What happens after my contract expires?", "answer": ["When your contract expires you can do any of the following:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Purchase a new phone & renew your contract, or\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Cancel your package & subscribe to anyone of etisalat mobile packages that suits your needs\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Continue receiving the same benefits without a yearly commitment"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "What is Auto payment?", "answer": ["Auto payment facility will allow Etisalat to charge your credit card with your monthly bill to ensure payments are made on time."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "Can I buy an iPhone without any contract?", "answer": ["Yes you can. We are offering different packages where you can purchase an iPhone without any yearly commitment."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "Can I use the data service provided with my iPhone plan while roaming?", "answer": ["The contract only comes with local data package, however, you subscribe to one of etisalat\u2019s roaming data packages.\r\n", "\r\nFor more info please visits ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "What is the warranty details for my iPhone?", "answer": ["Your iPhone will be under warranty for 12 month from the date of purchase, you can purchase Apple Care+ for extended warranty or accidental damage coverage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_devices"},
{"question": "What is eLife TV?", "answer": ["The new eLife TV experience is a key part of the eLife \"Triple Play\" bundle. With over 490 TV channels at your fingertips, you're always sure to find something to enjoy. Plus, you can choose from over 15 different packages featuring Sports, Family Entertainment, News and more. If you're looking for great TV entertainment, you came to the right place. The latest shows, movies and sports events, a crystal-clear digital picture with all the extras:\r\n", "\r\n- Recorder\r\n", "\r\n- OnDemand\r\n", "\r\n- Guide\r\n", "\r\n- Catch Up TV"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "How does eLife TV work?", "answer": ["eLife is based on Next Generation Fiber Optic Technology which allows you to receive high quality voice, superfast Internet and a High-Definition TV into one amazing experience. It offers you better picture quality as the picture is completely retained in digital format."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "How is eLife TV better than my existing TV connection?", "answer": ["eLife TV is powered by Etisalat's Fiber Optic technology, hence the picture and sound quality is better than your building TV system and more reliable than Satellite TV. Besides elevating you to a new technology eLife TV offers you innumerable other advantages that will change the way you watch television :\r\n", "\r\n- All your selections of TV channels can be made available through the same Set Top Box\r\n", "\r\n- Easy options to relocate / shift\r\n", "\r\n- Uninterrupted Viewing\r\n", "\r\n- Amazing new features such as Recorder, On Demand, Catch-Up TV etc."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What equipment is required to receive eLife TV services?", "answer": ["A Set-Top-Box (decoder) is required to receive the eLife TV service. The Set-Top-Box is available from Etisalat. You can also access eLife TV services on iPad/iPhone, PCs and Android devices with only an additional monthly access fee."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What are the TV packages available on eLife TV?", "answer": ["Packages offered reflect the viewing preferences of residents within the United Arab Emirates. The pricing is very competitive and offers a good entertainment value for the money to our viewers. To see what is offered please ", "."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Can I use Satellite / Building TV service as well as eLife TV simultaneously?", "answer": ["Yes. Satellite and eLife TV services can be used simultaneously on a single TV set. While the satellite / building system can be used as per regular practice, eLife TV gets connected to one of the HDMI / AV inputs of the TV set. Select the specific input from your TV remote to enjoy eLife TV services."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Will I be able to view all the channels as my TV set has very few channels?", "answer": ["Yes. You will be able to view all the channels even if your TV set has very few channels. The Set Top Box provided by Etisalat enables a large number of channels to be viewed irrespective of the number of channels supported by your TV. However, kindly note that only the channels that you have subscribed to will be available for you to enjoy. You can subscribe to additional TV packages directly from the TV menu."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "I have more than one TV set at my home. Can I connect my eLife TV subscription to all of them?", "answer": ["Yes, you may subscribe to additional connections for a nominal monthly fee plus additional subscription charges for some of the Premium TV packages."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "How can I personalize my TV experience?", "answer": ["You can create user profiles for the different family members. This allows you to ensure better control. Define or change allowed rating for channels or movies, limit On Demand consumption, create different favorite channel lists and languages for all members of the family."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is the Guide?", "answer": ["The Guide is the electronic program guide of eLife TV. It lists the current and upcoming programs on most channels. The Guide allows you to navigate through the menu using the arrow keys, selecting and discovering programming by channels, time and title. Additional information including a brief synopsis of the program you select is also available."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What kind of Mobile Data Offers does Etisalat have for its Prepaid customers?", "answer": ["Etisalat offers all Prepaid Wasel customers the option to purchase one-time data packs, or auto-renewal data plans that give choice & value depending on the need.\r\n", "\r\nOffers also include combo packs which include flexi minutes & local data, and other limited period one-time data packs.\r\n", "\r\nFor complete list of packages, ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is On Demand?", "answer": ["You're busy. We know it. With On Demand, you're no longer ruled by the programming grid. Movies On Demand is like having a video store in your living room. It gives you access to a large collection of movies of every genre. "], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is Catch Up TV?", "answer": ["Catch Up TV is a cool feature of eLife TV that allows you to catch up with TV content you may have missed form your favourite TV channels. Using your eLife TV remote control, you can access the Catch Up TV application, select from the available channels listed and go back in time up to seven days to watch the program you may have missed."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is the difference between recording a program and watching it later or watching the same program on Catch up?", "answer": ["Not all of your favorite channels will be available on Catch Up. So for channels that are not, you will need to use the Recorder to record a program to watch it later. Also programs are available on Catch Up for up to seven days only, so you will need to use the recorder if you want to keep the program for replay, longer than that."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Do I have to choose a Basic TV package?", "answer": ["One or two Basic TV packages of your choice is recommended. There are a good number of pay TV channels in every Basic package. eLife TV includes many channels free even before you choose a Basic package subscription. To the free channels and Basic packages you may add any Premium packages or a la carte channels."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Will a channel I am watching get recorded automatically?", "answer": ["Yes temporarily to allow you to pause and rewind/replay. Changing the channel erases this automatic recording to start recording the new channel. While watching a particular TV channel, it is very easy to start impulse recording."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Will all my recordings remain in my box?", "answer": ["Yes. However, you will not be able to view the programs that you have recorded if your eLife subscription becomes inactive. Once you have utilized the full capacity of the recorder hard disk, then older programs will be deleted to record new ones."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is High Definition TV (HD TV)?", "answer": ["High Definition is a greatest advance in television since the arrival of color TV in the 1960s. Until now, TV picture quality has been limited in resolution by the \"number of lines\" displayed on screen; about 625. This has not changed since TV standards were established. Even the best TV picture broadcast was never sharp and crisp or deep with details due to this limit which was locked-in due to the early TV technology limitations. The new HD standard is a huge step forward. Full HD displays a picture in 1080 lines of resolution so that fine details of a scene or textures and shades of objects are presented well."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Can all my TV channels be HD if my TV is HD?", "answer": ["No. Only channels that are recorded and broadcast in High Definition will be in HD."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is required to watch HD TV?", "answer": ["Three things must be present to enjoy HD TV:\r\n", "\r\n- HD content and signal from a broadcaster\r\n", "\r\n- An eLife TV Set Top Box\r\n", "\r\n- An HD-ready or full HD TV screen"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "In electronics shops, TV screens are sold as HD-Ready or Full HD. What is the difference?", "answer": ["The LED, LCD or Plasma TV screens being sold today are offered in these two resolutions mainly due to cost differences. An HD-Ready screen can receive and display HD TV picture with excellent quality and performance. However, when viewed side-by-side to a similar screen that is Full HD, there is a noticeable increase in picture quality due to the higher resolution."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is e-junior?", "answer": ["The first and only kids channel that belongs to the children of the UAE. A fantasyland for kids where they can learn, discover, love and laugh. From everyone's lovable cartoon characters to live action, there's something for children of all ages and nationalities. ", " for more information on e-junior and for new features such as kid's online drawing board and much more."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "eLife Home Moving", "answer": ["Home moving is always a hectic job but we can spare you from one of your crucial home moving tasks: Shifting of eLife services.", "Just visit one of our ", " or call ", " and our staff will be ready to help you to arrange the shifting of eLife service to your new location.", "You will simply provide us the address of your new location, any Landline number working in that area and your planned date for moving. The existing service will be ceased at your old location and our field technicians will visit to install the service at your new location. The appointment for installation will be set as per your convenience.", "Please carry with you the Wireless Router (Wi-Fi) and TV Decoder (Set Top Box) to your new location and keep these items ready for installation.", ": Please ask for the Shifting of your existing eLife Services to new location and don't request for eLife (New Account) as a New Subscriber."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is eLife Double Play?", "answer": ["eLife Double Play is your combined offering of Landline Telephone and Broadband Internet services in one convenient bundled offer. It provides HD voice quality with superfast Internet speeds of up to 30Mbps. eLife bundles have built-in value with the landline service including Caller ID, Voice Mail, and a monthly credit of 20-international call minutes. Your PC is protected against viruses with Norton antivirus, and email accounts are available with generous storage."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Do I subscribe on a monthly basis?", "answer": ["All eLife bundles are initially subscribed on a 12-month commitment. Thereafter, the subscription is monthly."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "If I am already an Al Shamil subscriber, what do I get if I move to eLife Double Play?", "answer": ["You will enjoy home services will in one convenient bundled account. There are value benefits and cost savings when compared to separate service subscriptions."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "Will I be charged if I terminate my contract before the completion of 12-months?", "answer": ["Yes. You will be charged whatever free or discounted benefits you have received when you first subscribed."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "How many phone lines do I get when subscribing to the eLife Double or Triple Play?", "answer": ["All eLife bundles include one landline phone connection. Bundles of 16Mb and above have an optional second line, free upon request. The second line is billed separately from your eLife bundle bill and has no built-in credits or free services that are included in the first line."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is a Router and do I need one?", "answer": ["A router is a device that provides the connection to eLife broadband and wired or wireless access to the Internet and connected devices in a home network. It is not a must, but almost everyone uses a router for the convenience of multiple connections that a home usually requires.", "Etisalat offers the latest router models at very reasonable prices, cash or in 12-installments. Routers are also sold in the local market"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What is eSupport and do I need to register for it?", "answer": ["eSupport is a connection and PC problem solving application with the capability of preventing and resolving many common problems. It's a free tool to solve technical Internet & related PC problems and guides you to what should be done for a fix. eSupport allows computers to become self-repairing devices by having a virtual agent inside which is always ready and active to solve your technical issues and direct you to the correct channel of support.", "In order to get eSupport, please visit ", " and click on Download. Then, click on RUN and follow the wizard"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "If I am away from home, can I access the Internet at a public Wi-Fi (Hotspot) location?", "answer": ["Yes. If you want to access the Internet at a mall, a local coffee shop or public location, you may either connect with the username/password provided by the coffee shop or alternatively, you may use the username and password of the eLife bundle that you subscribed to. A Free monthly Hotspot usage allowance comes with eLife bundles (starting from the 1Mbps) How to use your Free Hotspot Hours:\r\n", "\r\n- Enable the wireless connection in you device\r\n", "\r\n- Select Etisalat as network SSID\r\n", "\r\n- Select eLife Subscribers payment method from the drop down list\r\n", "\r\n- Enter your eLife account User Name & Password\r\n", "\r\n- Click Submit and enjoy surfing Internet"], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "I get an email account with my eLife. How do I add new boxes?", "answer": ["To add your additional email account(s), you may visit ", " Please login with your eLife username and password and then you may add the extra email accounts that come with your service bundle."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "I am afraid to get a computer virus on my PC. How can I protect my computer against virus infections?", "answer": ["With your eLife broadband service, you receive a free Norton Anti Virus license. You can download your free subscription of the antivirus software from its support page. Visit ", " and login with your eLife username and password. Click on Secure Desktop Service and install."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "If I move out from my home, can I bring along the white fiber box (ONT) with me?", "answer": ["The fiber box or Optical Network Terminal \"ONT\" installed in your residence belongs to Etisalat. It is intended to remain for the use of the next resident. Customers are not allowed to take them away when they move out."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "What are One-time Data Packs?", "answer": ["One-time Data Packs place convenience before commitment, where you can subscribe multiple times to the same pack, or mix and match different ones, depending on your need. This way, you never run out of Data with the flexible short and long validity options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What are Auto-renewal Data Plans? ", "answer": ["Auto-renewal Data Plans offer you peace of mind. No more hassle of re-subscribing to data every day, or month as these plans are automatically renewed at the end of assigned validity. Choose the plan you want and just ensure you have the right balance when it's time to renew and the plan will do the rest."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What\u2019s the \u2018Data Bonanza\u2019 on Monthly Data Plus Packs? ", "answer": ["Etisalat understands your need for more data & is permanently upgrading allowances on all one-time & auto-renewal monthly data packages. Now with \u2018Data Bonanza\u2019 you\u2019ll get up to 100% extra social data on Monthly Data Plus Packs.\r\n", "\r\nThe extra \u2018Social Plus \u2019allowance will cover usage on Facebook, Messenger, WhatsApp , Twitter, WeChat, LinkedIn, Snapchat, Instagram, BOTIM* & C\u2019Me*\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n* Social allowances may be used for messaging, for video and audio calling customer needs to subscribe to Internet Calling Plan (ICP)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I activate the Data Packs & Plans? ", "answer": ["For regular data packages & combos dial *170# for a choice of both one-time packs and auto-renewal plans. In addition, to explore other limited period one-time data packs dial *135#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Do I have to activate the One-time Data Packs every time they expire? ", "answer": ["Yes, the one-time packs can be purchased as many times as you wish whenever needed. They can be purchased in addition to your exiting daily or monthly data plans. At the end of the validity period the packs will be expired and you would have to repurchase them again."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What happens in case of the Auto-renewal Data Plans? ", "answer": ["The auto-renewal plans do not need to be subscribed again and are renewed automatically at the end of the assigned validity."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I Deactivate these Packs & Plans? ", "answer": ["For the one-time packs there is no need to deactivate since you have already paid for the data allowance. Once validity expires the pack will be automatically removed from your prepaid line.", "The auto-renewal plans can be deactivated from the USSD Menu *170#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I purchase multiple Data Packs or Plans of the same category at the same time? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can purchase multiple one-time packs of the same category at the same time - each pack will have its own allowance and validity period.", "Multiple subscription to auto-renewal plans will reset the renewal date, while both allowances will be available for usage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What happens if I don't use all my data allowance within the validity period?", "answer": ["Any remaining MBs will automatically expired and won't be carried over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I monitor my remaining balance? ", "answer": ["You can keep track of your data usage using the below three options:\r\n", "\r\n- Via SMS: SMS 'DATA' to 1010\r\n", "\r\n- Via USSD: Dial *170#\r\n", "\r\n- Via Etisalat UAE Mobile App", "You will also be notified via SMS in the following cases:\r\n", "\r\n- On consuming 80%, 90%, and 100% of data packages"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Data Packs and Plans on my BlackBerry? ", "answer": ["If you have a BB10 operating system and above you can enjoy any of the data packs and plans. Older BB operating system customers would not be able to benefit from these."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What happens if I don't have enough balance in my account?", "answer": ["- First time subscription: You will have to recharge your wasel prepaid account within 7 days, and the package will be activated automatically.\r\n", "\r\n- Auto-Renewal: You will have a grace period of 10 days to recharge your account in order to continue enjoying the plan, after which the plan will be removed from your account. Once removed and you have enough balance, you will have to activate the plan again."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is Data Bonanza on postpaid Monthly Data Plus Packs? ", "answer": ["Etisalat understands your need for more data and is permanently upgrading allowances on all auto-renewal monthly data packages. Now with \u2018Data Bonanza\u2019 you will get up to 100% extra social data on Monthly Data Plus Packs.", "The extra \u2018Social Plus \u2019allowance will cover usage on Facebook, Messenger, WhatsApp , Twitter, LinkedIn, Snapchat, WeChat, Instagram, BOTIM* & C\u2019Me*\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n* Social allowances may be used for messaging, for video and audio calling customer needs to subscribe to Internet Calling Plan (ICP)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How much Social Plus data will be added to each data pack? Is it 100% for all? ", "answer": ["You will receive up to 100% extra Social Plus data with every data pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Do I need to pay extra charges for Social Plus data?", "answer": ["No, you do not need to pay any extra cost for Social Plus data. You will enjoy extra Social Plus data with all mentioned data packages at no extra cost."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Will I get Social Plus data in unlimited pack?", "answer": ["No, there is no additional Social Plus data in unlimited pack. You can enjoy 100GB data at full speed within a bill cycle; after 100GB, the speed is throttled to 64Kbps."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What will happen if I purchase a data pack?", "answer": ["You will receive the extra Social Plus data along with your main data immediately."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How I will be able to purchase the Data Plus Packs?", "answer": ["You can purchase the data packs via SMS, USSD, IVR, Mobile app, calling customer care 101 or by visiting any Etisalat Business Centres."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What happens if I do not use all my data allowance within the validity period? ", "answer": ["Any remaining MBs will automatically expire and will not be carried over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I monitor my remaining balance? ", "answer": ["You can keep track of your data usage using the below three options:\r\n", "\r\n- Via SMS: SMS \u2018DATA\u2019 to 1010\r\n", "\r\n- Via USSD: Dial *170#\r\n", "\r\n- Via Etisalat UAE Mobile App\r\n", "\r\nYou will also be notified via SMS in the following cases:\r\n", "\r\n- On consuming 80%, 90% and 100% of data packages"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How I will be able to unsubscribe from Data Plus Packs?", "answer": ["You can unsubscribe from Data Plus Packs via SMS, USSD, IVR, Mobile app, calling customer care 101 or by visiting any Etisalat Business Centre"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for 1GB package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1GB = 1,000MB; 1MB = 1,000KB; 1KB = 1,024Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I upgrade or downgrade between the different eLife bundles?", "answer": ["Yes, you can. However, there will be a nominal fee of AED100 for the downgrade. If the downgrade or upgrade happens within a promotional period, (i.e. during the 3-months of discounted rentals) your new speed will be charged at the regular price only."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "How does the monthly bill look like \u2013 would I receive separate bills for the eLife services?", "answer": ["For your ease of understanding and convenience, you will receive one consolidated bill for all eLife bundled services. The bill summarizes each service and provides details of any usage for each."], "cat": "elife_faqs", "sub_cat": "elife"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the new Start/Stop Data service for prepaid customers?", "answer": ["Start/Stop Data service gives you the option to use mobile data for short periods, as and when needed, where you can use as much data as you want and pay only for the time you use at a very affordable rate.", "Minimum access charge of 30 fils applies for the first 15 minutes of usage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How does the charging work in Start/Stop Data service?", "answer": ["After you 'Start' a data session, you will be charged for 15 minutes of usage directly (minimum session), post which charging will continue on a per-minute basis.", "For example, if you use Start/Stop Data for 21 mins, 14 secs, you\u2019ll be charged for 22 mins @ 2fils/minute or 44 fils.", "Important to note, a minimum prepaid balance of 30 fils is needed to initiate a Start/Stop Data session to cover for the minimum access charge."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How much data can I use with the Start/Stop Data service?", "answer": ["The Start/Stop Data service has no volume limit on usage, so there is no need to worry about how much data is consumed during any session."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What kind of data speed will I get with the Start/Stop Data service?", "answer": ["Data speed will be limited to 1Mbps during any Start/Stop Data session. This is more than adequate for accessing any mobile optimised site, uploading/downloading rich content or streaming videos."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I manage my Start/Stop Data sessions?", "answer": ["You can Start/Stop/Check your data sessions by dialing *777#", "Dial *777*1# to START", "Dial *777*2# to STOP", "Dial *777*3# to CHECK"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Start/Stop Data service with other Data Packs and Plans?", "answer": ["You can use the Start/Stop Data service even if you have existing daily or weekly data subscriptions to pay by the minute and save your other data allowances. Data usage on Start/Stop will have the highest priority over all other data offers.", "You will, however, not be able to use the service if there's remaining allowance in any of your monthly data subscriptions."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "For how long can I use the Start/Stop Data service in a single session?", "answer": ["The maximum allowed limit for any Start/Stop Data session is 4 hours, after which you will be disconnected and will have to initiate a new session."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I monitor my usage time on the Start/Stop Data service?", "answer": ["You can dial *777*3# anytime to know the status of your Start/Stop Data session as Active or Inactive. SMS notifications will be sent every 2 hours for better tracking of your data access time."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What will happen after I \u2018Stop\u2019 my Start/Stop Data session?", "answer": ["You will be protected from paying charges for 2 hours after you \u2018Stop\u2019 your data session. This means, further data usage will be moved to other available data subscriptions (if available) or be blocked for 2 hours."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Start/Stop Data service multiple times in a day?", "answer": ["The Start/Stop Data service has no limit on the number of sessions you can have in a day. However, the minimum access charge will apply for every new session."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I share my data with others while using the Start/Stop Data service?", "answer": ["You will not be able to share your data access with other devices or users while within a Start/Stop Data session."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Start/Stop Data service on my BlackBerry?", "answer": ["If you have a BlackBerry 10 operating system or higher, you will be able to enjoy the Start/Stop Data service. Older BlackBerry customers would not benefit from this."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Start/Stop Data service on my Data SIM?", "answer": ["The Start/Stop Data service will not work on Data SIMs."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Start/Stop Data service while on Roaming?", "answer": ["The Start/Stop Data service works for local usage only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat Internet Calling Plan?", "answer": ["Etisalat Internet Calling Plans are an add-on to your existing Etisalat mobile and/or eLife service that allow you to make free App to App voice and video calls using a group of calling applications as long as you have active mobile data or home eLife Wi-Fi.There are 2 types of Internet Calling plans designed to fit your needs:", "\u00a0\u00a01.\u00a0", " This plan allows you to make free App to App voice and video calling on the move using your mobile data plan", "\u00a0\u00a02.\u00a0", " This plan allows you to make free App to App voice and video calling from your home eLife Wi-Fi", "To get started, follow the steps below:", "\u00a0\u00a01. Subscribe to any of the Internet Calling Plans by sending the respective keyword.", "\u00a0\u00a02. Once the Internet Calling Plan subscription is confirmed, download any of the supported applications.", "\u00a0\u00a03. Follow the application instructions to create and register your account on the application.", "\u00a0\u00a04. Ensure you have internet connection", "Now you can call any of your contacts who have the same application"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Who can subscribe to Etisalat Internet Calling Plan?", "answer": ["\u2022 Any of the following categories of customers can subscribe to the plans:", "\u00a0\u00a01. ", ", individuals or business accounts", "\u00a0\u00a02. ", " ( excluding Business customers)", "\u2022 For mobile customers \u2013 subscribe to the mobile Internet Calling Plan", "\u2022 For e-Life \u2013 subscribe to the eLife Internet Calling Plan"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What are the subscription charges for Etisalat Internet Calling Plans and how I will be charged? ", "answer": ["\u2022 The Internet Calling Plans have monthly subscription fees:", "\u00a0\u00a01. ", " per month for the eLife Internet Calling Plan", "\u00a0\u00a02. ", " per month for the Mobile Internet Calling Plan", "\u2022 The Internet Calling Plan subscription ", ":", "\u00a0\u00a01. ", ": The fees will be deducted from your mobile account, and the plan will be valid for 30 days. The service shall be automatically renewed and will remain active unless the Subscriber removed it.", "\u00a0\u00a02. ", ": The fees will be billed monthly and service shall be automatically renewed and will remain active unless the Subscriber removed it. When the subscriber add the plan for the first time, the Subscriber will be charged on prorated basis till end of bill cycle.", "\u00a0\u00a03. ", ": The fees will be billed monthly and service shall be automatically renewed and will remain active unless the Subscriber removed it. When the subscriber add the plan for the first time, the Subscriber will be charged on prorated basis till end of bill cycle."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What subscription I need to start using any of the supported applications to call my friends & family members outside UAE who are not Etisalat customers?", "answer": ["\u00a0\u00a01. Make sure to download one of the supported Applications that you wish to use", "\u00a0\u00a02. Ask you friends and family members to download the same App", "\u00a0\u00a03. Make sure that both users have an active internet connection", "\u00a0\u00a04. You as an Etisalat customer needs to make sure that you are subscribed to one of the Internet Calling plans that fits you", "\u00a0\u00a05. Now you can start making & receiving calls"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Does the purchase of the mobile internet calling plan grant me free mobile data?", "answer": ["When purchasing an Internet Calling Plan for Mobile, you will be charged for the data consumption used by the supported apps in accordance with your existing postpaid and/or prepaid data service. The purchase of the Plan does not grant you free data."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use any data package with my Mobile Internet Calling Plan?", "answer": ["\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 ", " the Internet Calling Plan will work with any mobile data package on Etisalat mobile postpaid or prepaid service.", "\u00a0\u00a0\u2022 ", " Please ensure you have an active mobile data package, to avoid charged at Pay as You Go rate"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use my Mobile Internet Calling Plan while roaming?", "answer": ["Yes, you can use your mobile Internet Calling Plan while roaming on Etisalat mobile data. (Data will be charged at standard roaming rates or from your data roaming package if available)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can my family and friends living outside UAE install the supported Apps?", "answer": ["Yes, you can ask all your friends and family members to install any of the supported applications in order for you to enjoy the App to App free unlimited voice and video calling facility using your mobile data or home eLife Wi-Fi."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Does it require from the supported App users who are living outside the UAE to subscribe to the Internet Calling Plans?  ", "answer": ["No, only Etisalat customers should subscribe to the Internet Calling plans (Mobile or eLife Home Broadband)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "If I\u2019m an Etisalat subscriber calling a user outside UAE using one of the supported application, then what subscription is required?", "answer": ["Once both users have the same application and internet connection, only Etisalat UAE subscribers need to have the internet calling plan active on their mobile or eLife home."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the supported Apps to make voice and video calls while connecting to public Wi-Fi like shopping malls, restaurants, etc.?", "answer": ["No, the internet calling plans are available for e-Life (Home broadband accounts) and Mobile subscribers, but if you would like to use the supported Apps on the move we recommend you to subscribe the mobile internet calling plan and ensure you have an active mobile data package"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "If I do not subscribe to the internet calling plans, can I still download and use the supported Apps?", "answer": ["Yes of course, and you will be able to send and receive messages and chat with your friends and family members around the world but will not be able to have the access to use the voice and video calling"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "If the eLife internet calling plan is active on my eLife account, can all members connected to the same Wi-Fi use the supported Apps to make voice and video calling?", "answer": ["Yes, if the internet calling plan is active on the eLife account, then all supported Apps users connected to that Wi-Fi can make voice and video calls."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to the Mobile internet calling plan and the e-Life internet calling plan in the same time?", "answer": ["Yes, you can subscribe to both types of the Internet Calling Plans at the same time you will be charged for both plans separately."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What subscription I need to start using any of supported applications to call my friends & family members inside UAE who are Etisalat customers?", "answer": ["\u00a0\u00a01. Make sure to download one of the supported Applications that you wish to use", "\u00a0\u00a02. Ask you friends and family members to download the same App", "\u00a0\u00a03. Make sure that both users have an internet connection", "\u00a0\u00a04. As an Etisalat customer you ", " need to make sure that you are subscribe to one of the Internet Calling plans that fits you", "\u00a0\u00a05. Now you can start making & receive call"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Are the supported applications available on all Application stores?", "answer": ["Yes, supported Apps are available on the Google play and Apple Store"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How do I use the supported apps with my Internet Calling Plan?", "answer": ["To use the supported apps with your Internet Calling Plan, follow these steps:", "\u00a0\u00a01. Subscribe to the Internet Calling Plan of your choice", "\u00a0\u00a02. Download any of the supported apps (check the website for details)", "\u00a0\u00a03. Install the app on your device and create your account (follow the app instructions)", "\u00a0\u00a04. Ensure you have internet connection", "Now you can call any of your contacts who have the same app"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "I am not receiving notifications when the app is closed or in the background, or if my screen is locked. What should i do?", "answer": ["In android phones some devices have an option to restrict notifications or background activities of apps due to battery optimization features. Please make sure your battery optimization is off if your device has such feature. Also, please make sure you enable Floating and lock screen notifications."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How do I unsubscribe from the Internet Calling Plan?", "answer": ["To stop your Internet Calling Plan subscription, please do the following", "\u00a0\u00a0", "\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0- Send \u2018CCP\u2019 to 1012 or", "\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0- use the My Etisalat App", "\u00a0\u00a0", "\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0- Send C EICP to 1010 or", "\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0- use the My Etisalat App", "Once you have un-subscribed from your Internet Calling Plan, the service will be cancelled immediately, there will be no refund of rental fees when un-subscription is done"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What are the new Nonstop Daily Data Plans for Prepaid customers? ", "answer": ["With Etisalat, you can now choose a mobile data plan by speed, and stay connected all day long with the new Nonstop Bronze, Silver, or Gold Daily Plan. You never run out of data, or get charged at out of bundle rates on these plans. The new daily plans are renewed every day at the same time of subscription for your added convenience.", "\u2022 Fair usage policy applies - speed reduces after daily fair usage allowance"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Which Websites & Apps can I use with the Nonstop Daily Plans? ", "answer": ["The Non-stop Daily Plans don\u2019t have any restriction on the type of content you access. However, your choice of speed will define your experience on these sites and apps \u2013 for example if you are into video streaming, we suggest you opt for the Nonstop Gold Daily Plan that gives full 4G LTE speed for un-buffered video streaming experience."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the fair usage allowance on the Nonstop Daily Plans? ", "answer": ["All three Nonstop Daily Plans have been optimized to offer great value through high fair usage allowances every day, exceeding which data is throttled at 64kbps for the rest of the day.", "The fair usage allowance is reset on re-subscribing to the same Nonstop Daily Plan or upgrading between plans."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to, or cancel the Nonstop Daily Plans? ", "answer": ["You can manage your Nonstop Daily Plan subscription using the below three options:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Do I have to subscribe to the Nonstop Daily Plans every day? ", "answer": ["The Nonstop Daily plans are renewed every 4 hours from the time of your last subscription or renewal. A confirmation SMS will be sent every time the plan is renewed successfully."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What happens if plan renewal fails due to non-availability of Prepaid balance? ", "answer": ["In case of failed renewal due to non-availability of Prepaid balance, the plans will go into a 3 day grace period for you to recharge your account. If no renewal happens during the grace period, the plan will be completely removed.", "During grace period data access will be charged at pay-as-you-use rate of AED 1/MB."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Nonstop Daily Plans with other Data Packs & Plans? ", "answer": ["The Nonstop Daily Plans may be used with regular volume based data packs and plans \u2013 however data usage will be consumed first from the volume based packages, and then from your Nonstop access.", "The Nonstop Daily Plans will not coexist with the Unlimited Social Plans, Old Unlimited Daily Plan, or Monthly Combo Plans."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I upgrade or downgrade between the three Nonstop Daily Plans? ", "answer": ["Yes, you may upgrade or downgrade between the Nonstop Daily Plans anytime. In case of upgrades (Bronze to Silver/ Bronze to Gold/ Silver to Gold) your old plan will be removed immediately and the new plan will become effective.", "In case of downgrades (Gold to Silver/ Gold to Bronze/ Silver to Bronze), you will have to cancel your old subscription first and then subscribe to the lower plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I monitor Data Usage on the Nonstop Daily Plans? ", "answer": ["You can keep track of your data usage using the below three options:", "You will also be notified via SMS in the following cases:", "There is no out of bundle data rating on the Nonstop Daily Plans."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Nonstop Daily Plans on my BlackBerry?", "answer": ["If you have a BB10 operating system and above you will be able to enjoy the Nonstop Daily Plans. Older BB operating system customers would not benefit from these plans."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "1. What is Data Booster? ", "answer": ["Etisalat understands your need for more data and introducing 2 new data boosters to offer you great value for money data boosters. Data boosters are one time data pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "2. What are the data boosters available now?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "3. How I will be charged? ", "answer": ["You will be charged full and data allowance will be given in full irrespective of subscription date."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "4. Who are eligible to purchase data boosters?", "answer": ["Any Postpaid customer, who is subscribed to any 1 GB or higher data pack, can purchase data booster."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "5. How I will be able to purchase data booster?", "answer": ["You can purchase the data packs via sms, USSD, IVR, Mobile app"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "6. Can I purchase multiple data boosters?", "answer": ["Yes, you can purchase multiple data boosters."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "7. What happens if I do not use all my data allowance within the validity period? ", "answer": ["Any remaining MBs will automatically expire by end of bill cycle and will not be carried over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "8. How can I monitor my remaining balance?", "answer": ["You can keep track of your data usage using the below three options:", "- Via SMS: SMS \u2018DATA\u2019 to 1010\u00a0", "- Via USSD: Dial *170#", "- Via Etisalat UAE Mobile App", "You will also be notified via SMS in the following cases:", "- On consuming 80%, 90% and 100% of data boosters", "- On consuming 80%, 90% and 100% of data boosters"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "9. How I will be able to unsubscribe from data boosters?", "answer": ["Data boosters are one-time packs .Data boosters will not renew automatically."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "10. What is the priority of data consumption?", "answer": ["Your data will be consumed in the following way :", "First, your data allowance in plan will be consumed, then if data allowance of any data pack you have purchased and then the data allowance of data booster."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "11. How many data units will I get for 1 GB package allowance?", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion", "1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "12. How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the new Data Balance Transfer service?", "answer": ["The new Data Balance Transfer service allows you to transfer data from your own monthly allowance to any other Prepaid or Postpaid Etisalat number as below:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Transfer in multiples of 100MB\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Transferred data will have 10 days validity\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 AED 3/ 100MB Transfer Fee\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Maximum 5 transfers allowed per Month\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Allowed for monthly plans with 1GB data allowance or more", "The flexibility and value that come with the Data Balance Transfer service are unmatched, as you can now transfer your unused data to your friends & family if they run out of data anytime."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Who can send or receive data using Data Balance Transfer?", "answer": ["All Prepaid & Postpaid subscribers can use the Data Balance Transfer service. Postpaid customers need to have been using their connection for at least 3 months to be able to transfer.\r\n", "\r\nData Balance Transfer is not allowed for Visitors and Business customers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I transfer data using this service?", "answer": ["You can transfer data to any Etisalat number using the below three options:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Via USSD Direct Dial: Dial #100*Receiver-Number*Data-in-MB# to Transfer data\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 For example, Dial #100*05XXXXXXXX*1000# to Transfer 1GB data to Receiver Number 05XXXXXXXX\r\n", "\r\n\u2022Via USSD Menu: Dial #100#"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How will I be notified about the status of the Data Balance Transfer?", "answer": ["Upon successful Data Balance Transfer, both you & the receiver will receive an SMS confirmation. In case of failed transaction, you will receive an SMS notification with the reason for failure."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Is there any limit on how much data I can transfer to others?", "answer": ["The following restrictions apply for Data Balance Transfer service:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Successful Transactions Limit - 5 Per calendar Month\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Minimum MB Amount per Transaction \u2013 100 MB\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Maximum MB Amount per Transaction\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Unlimited if you are sending from a prepaid line; 5GB if you are sending from a postpaid line\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Also, transfers are accepted as long as remaining allowance doesn\u2019t dip below 100MB in your own plan"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How will the Transferred Data Balance work?", "answer": ["The following rules apply on the Transferred Data Balance:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Transferred data will have a fixed validity of 10 days\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 There is no restriction for receivers on number, or value of data transfers \u2013 every transfer will have its own allowance and validity\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 In case the receiver has other general volume based data plans [like 1GB, 5GB, 10GB plans], then consumption will be first from the transferred data balance and then from the other plans\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 In case the receiver has only the transferred data balance, and the balance is depleted but still not expired, he/ she will be protected from out of bundle charges and data access will be blocked\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Lastly, transferred data may be re-transferred to others"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How will the receiver track usage of the Transferred Data Balance?", "answer": ["Receiver will be able to track usage from the transferred data balance via USSD by dialing *121*170#. He/ she will also be notified via SMS on consuming 100% of the transferred data allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I block the Data Balance Transfer service on my mobile?", "answer": ["Yes, you can. To block Data Balance Transfer service on your mobile, call Customer Care on 800101, or make a request at any of our Business Centers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Will the Transferred Data Balance work on BlackBerry?", "answer": ["If the receiver has a device with BlackBerry 10 operating system or higher, he/ she will be able to enjoy the Transferred Data Balance. Older BlackBerry customers would not benefit from this service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Will the Transferred Data Balance work on Data SIMs?", "answer": ["Yes, the Transferred Data Balance works on Data SIMs."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Will the Transferred Data Balance work while on Roaming?", "answer": ["No, the Transferred Data Balance is for local usage only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the NEW Daily Unlimited Social Data Plan? ", "answer": ["The NEW Daily Unlimited Social Data Plan offers all etisalat prepaid - Wasel customers daily unlimited access to Facebook, WhatsApp, BBM, Twitter and LinkedIn applications for only AED 2 a day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the Monthly Unlimited Social Data Plan? ", "answer": ["The Monthly Unlimited Social Data Plan offers all Etisalat prepaid and postpaid customers monthly unlimited access to Facebook, WhatsApp, BBM, Twitter and LinkedIn applications for only AED 49 a month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What can I do in these social applications? ", "answer": ["You can perform activities such as:", "- Access Facebook to send messages, add friends, upload photos, update profile, like other's posts, etc.", "- Use WhatsApp to chat, send and receive pictures, or videos and broadcast messages.", "- Use Twitter to tweet, reply to a tweet, re-tweet, follow others, search for trending topics, etc.", "- Log in to BBM to chat, create groups, share photos, update profile and broadcast messages", "- Log into LinkedIn to view posts, posts updates, browse contacts, send messages", "* External links to view articles, photos and videos will be blocked"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I activate the Unlimited Social Data Plans? ", "answer": ["To activate the Daily Unlimited Social Data Plan just dial *170#, or SMS 'DSP' to 1010.", "To activate the Monthly Unlimited Social Data Plan dial *170#, or SMS 'SP' to 1010.", "Once the plan has been activated a confirmation SMS will be sent."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Do I have to activate the Unlimited Social Data Plans every day/ month? ", "answer": ["For the New Daily Unlimited Social Data Plan, once activated, you'll enjoy unlimited social access every day. The plan is automatically renewed every 24 hours, at the same time you first activated the plan. You'll stay subscribed to the plan until you deactivate. E.g. if you activate the plan at 7pm, the plan will remain active for 24 hours, and get renewed the following day at 7pm.", "For the Monthly Unlimited Social Data Plan, once activated, you'll enjoy unlimited social access every month. The plan will be automatically renewed every 30 days."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I really use these social applications without any limit?  ", "answer": ["Yes. You can use Facebook, Twitter, WhatsApp, BBM or LinkedIn on your smartphone or data device without having to worry about how much data you are using. You can use it as much as you like as long as your plan is active.", " Please note that the download of the social applications and their updates are not part of the New Unlimited Social Data Plan. You will need to have a data pack or Wi-Fi access to be able to download the social applications and their updates to your smartphone or data device."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I Deactivate the plan? ", "answer": ["You can deactivate the Daily Unlimited Social Data Plan at any time by sending SMS 'C DSP' to 1010. Unlimited access to social applications that is part of this plan will be disabled.", "Similarly, you can deactivate the Monthly Unlimited Social Data Plan by sending SMS 'C SP' to 1010."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I access the internet or watch a video if I subscribe to the Unlimited Social Data Plans? ", "answer": ["The Unlimited Social Data Plans are designed to cover all your social networking needs, if you wish to browse the internet or access any other specific application you need to activate a regular Data package."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I still enjoy my current prepaid tariff plan? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can continue to benefit from your existing tariff. Any social network data usage will first be consumed from your Unlimited Social Data Plan, and any usage beyond that will be consumed from other existing data allowance that you have."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "I have an existing data plan - can I still activate the Unlimited Social Data Plans?", "answer": ["Yes, you can still activate the Unlimited Social Data Plans even if you already have an existing data plan. All use of Facebook, WhatsApp, Twitter, BBM & LinkedIn will be unlimited as long as you have the plan active. All other data usage will be taken from your existing data plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I use the Unlimited Social Data Plans on my BlackBerry?", "answer": ["If you have a BB10 operating system and above you can enjoy the Unlimited Social Data Plans. Older BB operating system customers would not be able to benefit from it."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I activate the Unlimited Social Data Plans if I am subscribed to the Free Social Data Promotion?", "answer": ["If you are subscribed to the Free Social Data Promotion you will not be able to activate the Unlimited Social Data Plans. You will have to first unsubscribe from the promotion then try activating the new plan again. This is being done so that you are not charged for social data, since we are offering it for free as part of the promotion. Once the promotion is over, you can re-subscribe to any plan of your choice."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t have enough balance in my account?", "answer": ["First time subscription: You will have to recharge your wasel prepaid account and try activating the plan again.", "Renewal: You will have a grace period of 3 days to recharge your account in order to continue enjoying the plan, after which the plan will be removed from your account. Once removed and you have enough balance, you will have to activate the plan again."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the Filipino Offer and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["Etisalat has launched a special offer for the Filipino community in UAE, wherein prepaid mobile customers can opt-in to this offer and enjoy call rates of 0.75 fils per second (45 fils per minute), with a call set up fee of AED 1 per call. These rates are valid 24 hours a day, 7 days a week."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What would be my call charges to other countries? ", "answer": ["The call charges to other countries would be as per your tariff plan or add on that you have subscribed to."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "I am an existing Wasel customer, how would I be charged for my calls after I have opted into this Offer?", "answer": ["Once you have opted-in this offer, all your calls to Philippines would be charged at 0.75 fils per second, for both per minute and per second billing customers. A call Set-up Fee of AED 1 will apply. All calls to other destinations and local calls would continue to be charged as per your tariff plan and billing pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Are there any limitations or restrictions on the number of calls (or) the length of the call that I make to Philippines?", "answer": ["There are no restrictions applicable with this offer. You can make as many calls as you wish for as long as you want."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to the Filipino Offer?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to the Filipino Offer by: Dialling ", " and pressing the dial key", "Once you have been successfully opted-in, you will receive an SMS from Etisalat confirming the same. The benefits of the Filipino Offer will be applicable for all calls made after this confirmation SMS has been received by you."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Who should buy the Wasel Premium Number?", "answer": ["Anyone who is interested in getting a special number without any commitment or monthly rental should buy this plan"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I opt out of the Filipino Offer? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can opt-out any time by\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\nDialling *140*4# and pressing the dial key\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\nOnce opted-out, you will be charged for calls to Philippines as per your existing tariff plan. You can opt-in again any time before end of the promotional period."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Are there any registration / subscription charges associated with this Filipino Offer?", "answer": ["No, there are no registration / subscription charges associated with this Offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Once I have opted-into this Offer, can I change my tariff plan? ", "answer": ["You can migrate to any of Etisalat's available tariff plans by following the subscription process specific to that tariff plan or offer.", "Even after subscription to another tariff plan, your subscription to the Filipino Offer will continue to exist and your calls to Philippines will be charged as per the Offer rates until the offer ends."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "For how long is this offer valid?", "answer": ["This offer is available for a limited period."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What are the Plan options and prices?", "answer": ["The Global Data Plan can be subscribed to with a 3 months Contract on Postpaid."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to & unsubscribe from the Global Data Plan?", "answer": ["Subscription SMS & USSD Dial:", "Un-subscription SMS & USSD Dial:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How do I get Roaming Data and WiFi Access on the Global Data Plan?", "answer": ["Only one opt-in required to 'Get it All' - Successful Subscription will lead to:", "* 10GB Local Data Allocation\r\n", "\r\n* 1GB Roaming Data Allocation\r\n", "\r\n- No need to subscribe separately while Roaming\r\n", "\r\n- Roaming Data will be available over preferred roaming partners", "* Local WiFi username & password\r\n", "\r\n- Required to log-in the first time\r\n", "\r\n* eWiFi username & password with link to download the App\r\n", "\r\n* Required to find Hotspots while Roaming", "Regular Data balance check over SMS & USSD will work for Local & Roaming volume allowances. There will be no usage check for WiFi as the allowances are unlimited."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What are the Preferred Roaming Partners where I can use my 1GB Roaming Data allowance? ", "answer": ["Please click on the following link to get the full list of Preferred Roaming Partners: "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Where will I get Etisalat WiFi Hotspots in UAE?", "answer": ["The below locations will have Etisalat WiFi Hotspots that can be accessed with the Global Data Plan. More Locations including 100+ Cafes would be added to the list."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I access the WiFi Hotspots in UAE?", "answer": ["NEW USER", "- Enter Etisalat WiFi zone (i.e. in a shopping mall)\r\n", "\r\n- Turn on WiFi and click on the Etisalat SSID\r\n", "\r\n- Enter username and password for first log-in\r\n", "\r\n- Etisalat will register the device, and allow it access\r\n", "\r\n- Session will end once (i) phone is out of WiFi zone (ii) WiFi is disabled on the phone", "RETURNING USER", "Enter Etisalat WiFi zone with WiFi turned on\r\n", "\r\n- Etisalat will remember the device, and allow it access - no need to login again\r\n", "\r\n- Session will end once (i) phone is out of WiFi zone (ii) WiFi is disabled on the phone"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "How can I access WiFi Hotspots while Roaming?", "answer": ["Roaming eWiFi will be enabled immediately at the time of subscription of the Global Data Plan.\r\n", "\r\nYou will receive the eWiFi login and password via SMS with a link to download the Etisalat eWiFi application. This message would also be sent whenever you are on roaming. When outside UAE, you can use this application to find eWiFi hotspots, and when in range of them, you can type the login/ password received from Etisalat to get access.\r\n", "\r\nFor eWiFi login/ password retrieval, SMS \"remind\" to 1010."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to the Global Data Plan, if I have other Data Packs / Plans active?", "answer": ["You can subscribe, or already be subscribed to any other data pack/ plan while having the Global Data Plan. Both pack/ plan will coexist, and you will benefit from two package capacities."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the minimum commitment period to subscribe to this Plan, and what are the Exit Charges?", "answer": ["The minimum 3 months commitment comes with a cancellation fee of the remaining months' rentals as explained below:", "- Cancellation before 1 month - Same month rental + 2 months' advance rental\r\n", "\r\n- Cancellation between 1-2 months - Same month rental + 1 month's advance rental\r\n", "\r\n- Cancellation between 2-3 months - Same month rental in full"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What is the Fair Usage Policy on the Unlimited access on local WiFi?", "answer": ["Fair Usage Cap of 50GB/ month will apply post which WiFi speed will be throttled @128 kbps."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to the Global Data Plan, if I have a Blackberry Device?", "answer": ["The Global Data Plan does not support Blackberry Devices. For Data Packages on Blackberry please ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_data"},
{"question": "What are the benefits with Wasel Premium Number?", "answer": ["With a one-time fee of AED 1,000 you get:\r\n", "\r\n- Choice of your own Special Premium Number\r\n", "\r\n- Free 3GB data every month for 6 months\r\n", "\r\n- Free Wasel Prepaid Line", "*Note: 5% VAT Excluded"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I get a Wasel Premium Number?", "answer": ["You can visit select Etisalat outlets to choose and buy your own Wasel Special Number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I carry forward the unused data from 3GB data pack?", "answer": ["No, the free 3GB data is only valid for 30 days from the date of credit. It will be renewed every 30 days until the 6th month, however, any unused data for the month will expire."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens after the 6 months free data benefit period is over?", "answer": ["In order to continue enjoying mobile data on your line, you need to subscribe to one of the "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I decide to transfer the ownership of my line?", "answer": ["In case you transfer the ownership of your line, the free 3GB data benefit will be discontinued."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is my line with Wasel Special Premium Number valid for a lifetime?", "answer": ["As long as you keep making calls or sending messages, your line has lifetime validity. In case you do not use your line for 3 consecutive months, then you would be charged AED 10 per quarter (once in 3 months) to remain in lifetime validity. In case you do not have 10 AED balance, your line will be moved to a time-based validity, in which you would have another 6 months to start using your line.", "If no usage is observed during this 6-month period, service will be temporarily withdrawn for a period of 3 months, and subsequently deactivated."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is WASEL?", "answer": ["You can rely on instant connectivity on the go, unrivalled network coverage, more value for money and complete control over your spending with Wasel Prepaid line.", "Get full control of your spending:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 All local and international calls are charged on a per second pulse\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Feel secure with Prepaid Line lifetime validity\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Enjoy instant connectivity with the fastest and widest network coverage"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can WASEL Customers dial emergency numbers? Is there a charge for this?", "answer": ["WASEL customers can dial emergency numbers 998, 999 and 997 and obtain prompt assistance. No charge is applicable for calls made to these numbers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long I can keep my prepaid number if I don\u2019t use the line?", "answer": ["\u2022 To keep your free Lifetime Validity, simply continue using your line by recharging, making and receiving calls, or even sending SMS.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 In case you stop using your line, then it will be retained for 12 months. During this period you can revive your LifeTime Validity again by making any recharge or call, as per the following ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Does WASEL have an International Roaming Facility?", "answer": ["Yes, Wasel International Roaming Services allows users to receive incoming calls and make outgoing calls while they are roaming internationally. For details related to tariffs and offers "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do we need to recharge our WASEL subscription before leaving the country?", "answer": ["Yes. We recommend that your WASEL subscription is recharged prior to leaving the country and sufficient credit is available in your account to ensure that you receive incoming calls while roaming"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can we recharge our WASEL subscription while roaming from abroad?", "answer": ["You can use any standard telephone in the country where you are roaming to recharge your WASEL subscription. Simply dial +9714004120. You will be prompted to enter your WASEL number and the Etisalat Prepaid Card Number"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can we check the available balance on our WASEL Service from abroad?", "answer": ["You can check the available credit balance on your WASEL Service by simply dialing +9714004121 from any standard telephone available in the country where you are roaming and following the voice instructions."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Are the numbers +009714004120 and +009714004121 chargeable? ", "answer": ["Yes. Both these numbers are charged as per IDD rates."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can WASEL customers receive incoming calls while roaming internationally?", "answer": ["Yes."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can WASEL customers make outgoing calls while roaming internationally?", "answer": ["No. Currently this facility is not available."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Are there any charges for subscription to WASEL International Roaming Service? ", "answer": ["WASEL International Roaming Service has no deposit, connection, quarterly rental or activation charges. When you receive a call while roaming, your caller (from UAE/elsewhere) will pay the call charges for a call to the Etisalat Network and the user pays charges for the international rerouting of the call from the UAE to the country where you receive the call. An extra roaming surcharge is also applicable by that country and this could vary from 10% to 25%. Incoming Roaming Call Charges are as per the existing charges for normal GSM Roaming."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can WASEL subscribers receive SMS messages while roaming? ", "answer": ["Yes. WASEL subscribers can receive SMS Text Messages FREE while roaming."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Wasel Plan and who is eligible for it? ", "answer": ["The New Wasel Plan is a prepaid mobile package from Etisalat.", "Prepaid lines activated after the 12th of November 2012 will be automatically activated onto this tariff plan, while existing customers would have to opt for it."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How different is the New Wasel from the earlier Wasel plan? ", "answer": ["Calls made under New Wasel are charged on a \"per second\" basis; under the Wasel plan, calls are charged on a \"per minute\" basis. Therefore, if you are on the New Wasel plan, all your calls are charged to the exact second you talk for and not rounded off to the nearest minute. Moreover, international calls during off-peak hours made to a preferred country of your choice are charged at a discounted rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is the New Wasel a temporary offer? ", "answer": ["No. The New Wasel is a permanent plan"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Are there any registration/subscription charges associated with this tariff plan? ", "answer": ["No, there are no registration/subscription charges associated with this tariff plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How do I migrate to another plan? ", "answer": ["You can migrate to any of Etisalat's available plans by following the subscription process specific to that tariff plan.", "Upon subscription to another tariff plan, the system will automatically cancel your subscription to the New Wasel."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I have purchased a New Wasel connection. Can I still subscribe to this plan? ", "answer": ["All prepaid lines activated after the 12th of November 2012 will be automatically activated onto the New Wasel plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the Visitor Line and who can benefit from it? ", "answer": ["Visitor Line is a new prepaid pack from Etisalat, exclusively designed for the visitors travelling to the UAE. Whether you are on a business trip or a tourist or a job seeker or just visiting family, the Visitor Line gets you connected immediately with a rich pack selection of your choice. You can enjoy benefits that suit your needs from:", "- Data+ Wi-Fi pack (recommended for visitors on business)", "- Voice & SMS pack (recommended for family/leisure visitors)", "- Data, Voice, SMS pack (for the leisure/business visitor)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the benefits of the Visitor Line and how much do I pay? ", "answer": ["For just AED 100; about 27 US$, you can instantly connect with your friends and family back home during your stay with the choice of ONE of the suitable packs, which needs to be SELECTED AT TIME OF PURCHASING THE LINE. Each pack is valid for 14 days from the date of activating them.", "The SIM card will be valid for 90 days and the validity can be extended for an additional period of 90 days for just AED 10."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens after 14 days? Can I recharge and use my Visitor Line?", "answer": ["Visitor pack is available at all Etisalat outlets. The pack is also available at all Airport arrivals, spanning Etisalat outlets & Duty free shops across Abu Dhabi, Dubai and Sharjah. The pack is also available in Etisalat business centres & outlets in malls.", "To know the current balance of your pack, SMS VBB to 1012 or use the Etisalat Mobile App. Or you can simply recharge and use your Visitor Line.\r\n", "\r\nYou can recharge your Visitor Line using any of the following methods; which are available across more than 10,000 outlets across the UAE.\r\n", "\r\n- Etisalat Mobile App; using your credit card\r\n", "\r\n- eRecharge - any denomination; minimum from AED 5\r\n", "\r\n- Recharge cards \u2013 available in denominations of 25,50,100,200 and 500\r\n", "\r\n- eVoucher \u2013 available in denominations of 25,50,100,200 and 500\r\n", "\r\n- Etisalat payment machines at over 1000 locations\r\n", "\r\nTo check your prepaid balance - use Etisalat Mobile App or dial *121# or call 121."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will my rates be if I recharge and use my Visitor Line?", "answer": ["In case you have opted not to subscribe to any of the packs above and just want to recharge and use your Visitor Line, you will be charged Pay-as-you-go rates,, which are listed below."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Where can I buy the Visitor Line? ", "answer": ["Visitor Line is available at Etisalat outlets and at all airport arrivals, covering Abu Dhabi, Dubai and Sharjah. It's also available in outlets in malls and other key touristic spots. Some outlets are listed below:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long can I use my Visitor Line?", "answer": ["You can use the Visitor Line for 90 days from the date of activation. "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I retain my number, if I find a job and become a permanent resident of UAE?", "answer": ["After 30 days from activation, just log onto the Etisalat Mobile App or dial *101# to upgrade to Wasel Prepaid service. You will retain the same number and up to AED 100 of your Visitor Line balance will be transferred. After which, please, visit the nearest Etisalat Business Centre to fulfill your UAE resident registration process, with valid identification documents."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to other Etisalat tariff plans, bundles or promotions on Visitor Line?", "answer": ["Visitor Line comes with its own rich set of exclusively designed packs and a hassle-free experience. Stay connected with your friends and family with the all-in-one Visitor Line. Simply choose a suitable pack and enjoy your stay in the UAE."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "9Will I be able to \"Roam\" with Visitor Line?", "answer": ["Yes, you will easily be able to enjoy roaming services. While roaming, the visitor packs will not available. You will need to recharge your line and the standard roaming tariff will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is Wi-Fi service and how it is different than mobile data?", "answer": ["Wi-Fi service is provided to access the Internet in certain areas wirelessly. These areas can be indoor or outdoor and are called Wi-Fi hotspots. There are two ways to connect to the Internet wirelessly, one is Wi-Fi, which is considered more economical but with limited coverage (within hotspot only) and the second is through a mobile network. A mobile network has wider coverage for mobile data or Internet connectivity."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Where is Etisalat Wi-Fi service available?", "answer": ["Etisalat Wi-Fi service is available in major public areas including shopping malls, cafes, restaurants and parks (in process). Just search Etisalat Wi-Fi on your device and if you are in coverage areas you will get the Etisalat Network to login."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I manage my Visitor Line or get support? ", "answer": ["You can conveniently manage your Visitor Line with Etisalat Mobile App:\r\n", "\r\n- Check your balance and track your usage\r\n", "\r\n- Subscribe instantly to a pack of your choice\r\n", "\r\n- Get notifications when you are running out of minutes, data and SMS\r\n", "\r\n- Recharge your line\r\n", "\r\n- Live chat for support from our agents\r\n", "\r\nEtisalat Mobile App works with iOS, Android, BB 10 OS and Windows. Download \"Etisalat UAE\" App now from your app store and enjoy maximized convenience.\r\n", "\r\nOr\r\n", "\r\nYou can visit any of the Etisalat Business Centres or call 101 from your mobile for any help at any time."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What kind of Mobile Data Offers does Etisalat have for its Prepaid customers?", "answer": ["Etisalat offers all Prepaid Wasel customers the option to purchase one-time data packs, or auto-renewal data plans that give choice & value depending on the need.\r\n", "\r\nOffers also include combo packs which include flexi minutes & local data, and other limited period one-time data packs.\r\n", "\r\nFor complete list of packages, ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are One-time Data Packs?", "answer": ["One-time Data Packs place convenience before commitment, where you can subscribe multiple times to the same pack, or mix and match different ones, depending on your need. This way, you never run out of Data with the flexible short and long validity options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are Auto-renewal Data Plans? ", "answer": ["Auto-renewal Data Plans offer you peace of mind. No more hassle of re-subscribing to data every day, or month as these plans are automatically renewed at the end of assigned validity. Choose the plan you want and just ensure you have the right balance when it's time to renew and the plan will do the rest."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What\u2019s the \u2018Data Bonanza\u2019 on Monthly Data Plus Packs? ", "answer": ["Etisalat understands your need for more data & is permanently upgrading allowances on all one-time & auto-renewal monthly data packages. Now with \u2018Data Bonanza\u2019 you\u2019ll get up to 100% extra social data on Monthly Data Plus Packs.\r\n", "\r\nThe extra \u2018Social Plus \u2019allowance will cover usage on Facebook, Messenger, WhatsApp , Twitter, WeChat, LinkedIn, Snapchat, Instagram, BOTIM* & C\u2019Me*\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n* Social allowances may be used for messaging, for video and audio calling customer needs to subscribe to Internet Calling Plan (ICP)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I activate the Data Packs & Plans? ", "answer": ["For regular data packages & combos dial *170# for a choice of both one-time packs and auto-renewal plans. In addition, to explore other limited period one-time data packs dial *135#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to activate the One-time Data Packs every time they expire? ", "answer": ["Yes, the one-time packs can be purchased as many times as you wish whenever needed. They can be purchased in addition to your exiting daily or monthly data plans. At the end of the validity period the packs will be expired and you would have to repurchase them again."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens in case of the Auto-renewal Data Plans? ", "answer": ["The auto-renewal plans do not need to be subscribed again and are renewed automatically at the end of the assigned validity."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I Deactivate these Packs & Plans? ", "answer": ["For the one-time packs there is no need to deactivate since you have already paid for the data allowance. Once validity expires the pack will be automatically removed from your prepaid line.", "The auto-renewal plans can be deactivated from the USSD Menu *170#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I purchase multiple Data Packs or Plans of the same category at the same time? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can purchase multiple one-time packs of the same category at the same time - each pack will have its own allowance and validity period.", "Multiple subscription to auto-renewal plans will reset the renewal date, while both allowances will be available for usage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don't use all my data allowance within the validity period?", "answer": ["Any remaining MBs will automatically expired and won't be carried over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I monitor my remaining balance? ", "answer": ["You can keep track of your data usage using the below three options:\r\n", "\r\n- Via SMS: SMS 'DATA' to 1010\r\n", "\r\n- Via USSD: Dial *170#\r\n", "\r\n- Via Etisalat UAE Mobile App", "You will also be notified via SMS in the following cases:\r\n", "\r\n- On consuming 80%, 90%, and 100% of data packages"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I use the Data Packs and Plans on my BlackBerry? ", "answer": ["If you have a BB10 operating system and above you can enjoy any of the data packs and plans. Older BB operating system customers would not be able to benefit from these."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don't have enough balance in my account?", "answer": ["- First time subscription: You will have to recharge your wasel prepaid account within 7 days, and the package will be activated automatically.\r\n", "\r\n- Auto-Renewal: You will have a grace period of 10 days to recharge your account in order to continue enjoying the plan, after which the plan will be removed from your account. Once removed and you have enough balance, you will have to activate the plan again."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "1. What are the data packs and how can I activate them?", "answer": ["* Note: all data packs mention above are one time.\r\n", "\r\nSocial Chat Includes - Facebook, Messenger, WhatsApp , Twitter, LinkedIn, BOTIM* & C\u2019Me*\r\n", "\r\n* Social allowances may be used for messaging, for video and audio calling customer needs to subscribe to Internet Calling Plan (ICP)", "* Note: Social Data Packs are automatically renewed\r\n", "\r\nSocial Chat Includes - Facebook, Messenger, WhatsApp , Twitter, LinkedIn, BOTIM* & C\u2019Me*\r\n", "\r\n* Social allowances may be used for messaging, for video and audio calling customer needs to subscribe to Internet Calling Plan (ICP)\r\n", "\r\n*Prices are subject of 5% VAT"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "2. What are the BlackBerry data packs and how can I activate them?", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "3. How can I check the remaining allowances?", "answer": ["You can Check your remaining allowances by dialing *101# and choose Option 1 - Account Management"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Why do I have to register my number?", "answer": ["This is a TRA policy for Consumer mobile customers to avoid the Fraud cases."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will I know that I have to renew my Registration details?", "answer": ["An SMS will be sent to you telling that the document details to have been expired and you need to renew it."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will happen if I fail to renew my details?", "answer": ["You will be given one grace period, after that the line will be TOSSED for a period of time, if you fail to renew the registration during that period then the line will be disconnected."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Am visiting UAE on a visitor visa, do I have to register my line?", "answer": ["The visitor customers are given a line valid for 90 days only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How many time do I have to renew my registration?", "answer": ["You need to renew your registration every time your Identification expire."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Am using mobile number, & am owning a business in UAE but I don\u2019t have residence visa, while am visiting the country from time to time, how can I renew my registration?", "answer": ["You can send an email to care@etisalat.ae and providing a proof of your business along with a valid passport."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the acceptable document?", "answer": ["a) Valid Original UAE ID or\r\n", "\r\nb) Valid Original Passport or\r\n", "\r\nc) Valid Original GCC National ID\r\n", "\r\nd) Additional document approved by TRA for limited time:\r\n", "\r\ni.Labor Card\r\n", "\r\nii.Diplomat card"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the registration policy means?", "answer": ["This is a new Policy from the Telecom Regulatory Authority (TRA) in UAE, that require all SIM owner in UAE to register the SIM cards under their custody. This will ensure updating the subscriber profile at the operator with original and valid ID information."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Why should I register my line?", "answer": ["Registration policy means that all Mobile owners must submit their valid approved document to the operator to ensure updating the profile of the customer. Customer must submit the document in person for proper verification."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "As a subscriber, what will be the consequence if I don't register?", "answer": ["In case the subscriber fails to register within the specified period after receiving the SMS notification, SIM card will be suspended for a period of 3 months. Then after the 3 months passes, the number will be ceased as per Etisalat policy for 3 months before Etisalat will be able to resell the number again to any customer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay to register my line?", "answer": ["Registration is FREE OF CHARGE."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Will my service be interrupted by this registration process?", "answer": ["The service will not be affected/ Interrupted during the registration process in fact there will be only updating customer profile."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long it will take to register my line?", "answer": ["Customer ready with all his line will be processed within 10 minutes time, whereas customer who can't provide all his numbers, the process might take longer to ensure all his numbers are found and processed."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Should I submit my original documents or copy?", "answer": ["Original valid document is required & copy of ID document as well. The Original document is required for verification during the registration process. Also copy of the original document will be retained for the record."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Will my number be changed when I register?", "answer": ["Your mobile number will remain the same."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I do it for someone else?", "answer": ["Yes, if you have the original power of attorney or letter from the owner of the SIM signed with his original valid approved ID. SIM owner representative can register the SIM card with his his/her original and valid ID along with the legal power of attorney/letter of delegation signed by the owner of the SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "My SIM is not under my name, can I register the SIM?", "answer": ["Yes, you can register the SIM that belong to you after the verification process with the sales staff. SIM holder can register the SIM card temporarily under their name, and for a period of 6 months, before the ownership of the SIM card is transferred permanently to the name of SIM CARD holder, provided the original owner does not claim it within this 6 months period."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I don't have my IDs with me, can I still register?", "answer": ["No. Customers must provide original and valid ID to register his/ her SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Where can I register my line?", "answer": ["All Etisalat Business Center, Service Center, and Outlets are equipped for the registration process across all UAE."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "After registration, do I have to supply less document for replacement of SIM card or apply for new service?", "answer": ["You have to present your Original ID for verification and signed application for any transaction as per the normal practice."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If am a user (age 18) using a postpaid SIM under parents name, will I be able to register it under my name?", "answer": ["As long as you are at the legal age for a service (18 years for prepaid and 21 for postpaid) then you can apply for the registration of the SIM card under your custody, to be under your name."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If I have an existing SIM, I do not register my SIM, what status will it show in your system (active, suspended, non-active) and after what duration will status of SIM will change?", "answer": ["It will show it as un-registered at this moment but when the customer receives an SMS to register the SIM card, then it will show under suspension for 3 months and then de-activated or ceased."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If I am outside the country and will not be back for a long time, can I register via email?", "answer": ["Etisalat contact center will guide you on the process of registration either via:\r\n", "\r\na) Calling from abroad to hold your SIM registration timeline until you comeback by dialing to +971 400444 101.\r\n", "\r\nb) Or faxing a signed letter advising of the same to email 101@contactcentre.ae\r\n", "\r\nc) Or sending representative with a letter signed from your side with your and the representative original ID (document)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If my line is disconnected due to non-registration while I was outside the country, can I reclaim back my number after proving that I was outside the country?", "answer": ["Customer line will be suspended/ tossed for 3 months and then ceased as per Etisalat current policy which is 3 months before Etisalat will be able to resell the number to any customer"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long this Campaign will continue for?", "answer": ["This campaign is expected to last for 18 months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "My Visa/ UAE ID has less than a month to expire; can I register my SIM card?", "answer": ["Yes. You can register your SIM card but it will be valid for one year. However, we recommend that you renew your visa/UAE ID to have longer validity period as of the expiration date of the document."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I register online?", "answer": ["The online registration is not available at this point of time."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Why new subscribers need to re-register?", "answer": ["After July 17, 2012, all new subscribers will meet the TRA policy requirement automatically."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I have 3 numbers under my name, one for me, one for my wife and one for my son (who is under 18), should each of them register his/her number alone or I can still register those numbers under my name?", "answer": ["You can still register those numbers under your name and you will be responsible for all the SIM cards."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am a Prestige customer, do I have to register?", "answer": ["Yes all customers required to register at any of Etisalat point of sales."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is Mobile Number Portability (MNP)? ", "answer": ["Mobile Number Portability (MNP) is the process of transferring (porting) your mobile phone number from one mobile phone network provider to another. You may want to do this if you wish to sign up to a new mobile phone provider and keep your original mobile phone number, thus saving you the inconvenience of updating your contacts with your new telephone number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will you benefit from MNP? ", "answer": ["You are free to choose a new mobile service provider without having to change to a new number. You don't have to notify friends, family and associates about your new operator when you move to Etisalat or any other operator. Just use your phone like you always do."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is porting of numbers? ", "answer": ["Porting of numbers is the actual switching of a mobile operator/mobile service provider without having to change one's mobile number. However, only active mobile numbers can be ported, so you do not have your number disconnected before porting."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the charges for porting a number? Are there any other charges applicable?", "answer": ["Etisalat offers the MNP (Mobile Number Portability) facility free of charge."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long does it take to port a number? ", "answer": ["The entire process of porting takes approximately 2 days. The time for porting a number also depends on the clearance from the donor operator (operator that you are leaving)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What do I need to keep in mind before joining/porting to Etisalat?  ", "answer": ["All existing credit available to prepaid customers will expire upon successful porting and will not be carried forward.", "Call charges, plans and VAS offered by Etisalat may differ from that offered by your earlier service provider."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I port my prepaid/postpaid number to Etisalat?", "answer": ["Yes, you can port any prepaid or postpaid number to Etisalat. However, your credit in case of prepaid will lapse once the port in is successful."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What documents must a prepaid/postpaid customer submit while making a port in request to Etisalat? ", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the process to be followed to port my number to Etisalat?", "answer": ["All you have to do is visit your nearest Etisalat Business Centre or outlet and apply for the service with a valid number and ID documents as mentioned above and Etisalat will take care of the rest.", "Mobile Number Porting at Etisalat is offered as a \"one-stop-shop\" service. You do not have to visit the office of your previous operator. Etisalat will take care of the necessary formalities."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I get an Etisalat Porting Request Application form?", "answer": ["Etisalat MNP forms are available at all Etisalat touch points; they can also be downloaded from the Etisalat website. (Click here to download the application Form)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I port a landline number?", "answer": ["No, the service is applicable only to mobile services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to change my SIM card to port my number to Etisalat?", "answer": ["Yes. Etisalat will offer you a new SIM card when you apply for porting. Etisalat will activate the new SIM card with your existing number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will happen to the contacts in my SIM card?", "answer": ["Your new SIM card will not have your old contacts. It is advised to back up your contacts from the old SIM to phone and then copy them on to the new SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will I know if my porting request is completed or not?", "answer": ["You will be notified once Etisalat activates the new SIM card. Your previous operator shall also notify you on the deactivation of the old SIM card soon after Etisalat activates the new SIM.", "You will also be notified by means of SMS upon successful completion of your porting request."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "When can I apply for a porting request?", "answer": ["You can choose to apply for the service anytime between 8 am to 8 pm on any working day. Porting requests received between 8 am to 1 pm on working days only (Sunday to Thursday) will be processed the same day. However, some of our outlets work 24 hours, so you can submit your port in request at anytime, and our teams will process and verify your requests."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "When will the application received after 1 pm be processed?", "answer": ["The applications received after 1 pm will be processed during the next working day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is it compulsory to visit an Etisalat office to place the porting request?", "answer": ["No. You can become an Etisalat customer without even visiting any of our offices. All you have to do is visit etisalat.ae and place a port request and we will deliver the SIM card at your doorstep. (This service is applicable to destinations within the UAE only.)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "In case I have a balance due with my previous operator, can I still port in or out?", "answer": ["Yes. Even if you have balance due, you will be able to place your porting request."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the \u2018Call International, Pay Local' and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["The Call International Pay Local promotion is available for subscription for all Wasel-Prepaid customers. Upon successful subscription, customers can call 11 countries at the price of local calls (38 fils/min + call set up fee of AED 1.05)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the available countries included in this promotion?", "answer": ["Here is a list of the countries included in the promotion:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to configure or select my preferred country from these countries to enjoy the special rates?", "answer": ["No. Once you have opted into this add-on, you will automatically start enjoying these special rates for calls to the specified countries or operators."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe/unsubscribe to the \u201cCall International Pay Local\u201d offer?", "answer": ["\u2022 Dial *111*1*2*2*1# to subscribe.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Dial *111*1*2*2*2# to unsubscribe."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the Credit Plus/ International Plus? And how do I benefit from it?", "answer": ["\r\n            ", "\r\n          ", "\u2022 ", " - Credit Plus gives you up to 30% extra credit in addition to the value of the recharge card. The total credit (Recharge value + Extra credit) can be used for any kind of usage within the specified validity period. All Credit Plus balance will be consumed at Standard Wasel Rates.", "\u2022 ", " - International Plus gives you up to 60% extra international credit, in addition to the value of the recharge card. The total credit (Recharge value + Extra credit) can be used for any kind of International usage within the specified validity period."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I have 'Credit Plus, \u2018International Plus, as well as standard recharge balances at the same time? And how will I know about the balance status? ", "answer": ["Yes you can have all three types of balances at the same time. For balance enquiry, you can dial below:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If I have only 'International Plus' balance, can I make local calls and SMSs? ", "answer": ["'International Plus' balance can only be used for International voice calls, video calls and SMS from UAE. If you wish to make a local call please recharge your account using standard recharge or \"Credit Plus\" option."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If I am a 'Call International Pay Local customer'. Can I also recharge using 'International Plus' option and use it? ", "answer": ["Yes you can recharge using the International Plus option. All your international calls will first be consumed from your international plus balance at standard rates followed by your main balance (If your calls are to any of the 11 CIPL countries, you will be charged as per CIPL rates, else you will be charged as per your tariff plan)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If I have only 'Credit Plus' can I make international calls with it?", "answer": ["Yes, If you have 'Credit Plus' balance, you can use it for local and international calls and SMS."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I recharge with 'International Plus' more than once? ", "answer": ["If you do multiple recharges of International Plus, the credit gets accumulated and the greater of the validity periods is assigned."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I recharge with the 'International Plus' option but I don\u2019t use the credit within the specified period? ", "answer": ["You will lose the unused 'International Plus' balance if it is not used within the validity period unless another 'International Plus' recharge is done before the validity period is over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will the balances be used when I use my prepaid line? ", "answer": ["The balances will be used in the following order: 1. International Plus 2. Credit Plus 3. Main balance"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat Credit Transfer service? ", "answer": ["Etisalat Credit Transfer service is a new service that gives you the convenience of transferring credit/balance from your Postpaid or Prepaid account to another Prepaid account"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe or activate the Etisalat Credit Transfer service? ", "answer": ["The Etisalat Credit Transfer facility is available to all active Prepaid and Postpaid accounts. No registration or subscription is required to use the service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How do I send credit from one account to another account?", "answer": ["Transferring credit from your account to another account is very easy and quick.", "Just type the following command on your mobile screen (not as a SMS) and press the send key: *Credit transfer Service Code * Mobile number * Amount to be transferred # followed by the Send key.", "The credit transfer code for the credit transfer service is 100. For example, if you want to transfer AED 13 to a mobile number 050 123 4567, you need to Send the following command: *100 * 050 123 4567 * 13 #"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What message will I get after sending the Credit Transfer command?", "answer": ["After sending the Credit Transfer command, you will receive a message confirming the transaction details and requesting you to press 1 to confirm and 2 to cancel."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will happen if I will press 1 to confirm?", "answer": ["On confirming the credit transfer, the recipient will receive the credit in their account and you will receive a message confirming the transfer and stating the balance in your account after the transfer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will happen if I press 2 to cancel?", "answer": ["On cancelling the Credit Transfer, the recipient will not receive any credit in their account and you will receive a message confirming the cancellation and stating the balance in your account."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will the recipient find out that the credit transfer has been credited to their account?", "answer": ["On receiving the credit, the recipient will receive a message indicating the amount transferred to his account from your mobile number and the current balance following credit in his/her account."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will the recipient be notified if the credit/balance transfer to their account has been cancelled?", "answer": ["Upon cancelling the credit/balance transfer, the recipient will not be notified."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Who can use the Etisalat Credit Transfer service?", "answer": ["All Postpaid and Wasel Prepaid customers ca use this service to transfer credit. All Etisalat prepaid customers with active and working accounts can receive the credit"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I transfer credit from my Prepaid Wasel or Ahlan accounts to other GSM Postpaid accounts?", "answer": ["No. At the moment, the credit can be transferred only to prepaid accounts."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I transfer credit from my temporarily disconnected Prepaid Wasel or Ahlan account to other accounts?", "answer": ["No. Credit/balance transfer is not possible from temporarily disconnected accounts."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I transfer credit from my active Prepaid account to a Tossed Prepaid Account?", "answer": ["Yes. You can transfer credit to Tossed Prepaid accounts. This will help you to renew your Tossed account."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I transfer credit from my ceased Prepaid account to other accounts?", "answer": ["No. The transfer of credit is not possible from ceased accounts."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I get back the transferred balance by making a request to Etisalat?", "answer": ["No. The customer is wholly responsible for any balance transfer transaction, similar to the policy of making calls or sending SMS. The transferred credit is not refundable to the sender. The system will give you an option to confirm before transferring the balance. You can check and verify the number to which you are transferring credit before confirming the transaction."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What if the transferred balance did not reach the recipient and has been deducted from my account?", "answer": ["In such cases you may approach an Etisalat office or can call Customer Care on 101. An investigation will be done and in the case of an Etisalat system failure, the amount will be credited back to the donor"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I transfer credit from my active account to a prepaid active account while I am roaming abroad?", "answer": ["Yes, but subject to the availability of sending the Etisalat Credit Transfer command in that particular country."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I transfer credit from my active account to a prepaid active account which is roaming abroad?", "answer": ["Yes. You can transfer the credit to the UAE active prepaid account which is roaming abroad."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the minimum amount that I can transfer?", "answer": ["The minimum amount of transfer per transaction is AED 2"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the maximum amount that I can transfer?", "answer": ["The maximum amount of transfer per transaction is AED 150"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the limit on total number of transactions per day?", "answer": ["There is no limit on the total number of transaction per day. However, the total credit being transferred should not exceed the total amount of AED 150 per day"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the maximum amount that I can transfer in one month?", "answer": ["The maximum amount of credit that can be transferred in a month is AED 1,500 for Prepaid and AED 500 for Postpaid"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is it mandatory to transfer credit in multiples of AED 5 in each transaction?", "answer": ["No. The minimum credit transferred should be AED 2 and the maximum is AED 150 per day. However, any amount (not decimal) in between these figures can be transferred"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will happen if I try to transfer the credit after crossing my daily or monthly limits?", "answer": ["The system will not accept your request and you will be informed via an SMS that your request cannot be processed."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["With Etisalat's Deal of the day, You can enjoy a special offer every day. You need to dial *050# or send DEAL to 1204 in order to know your Deal of the Day offer. On dialing *050# you will receive a sms from sender id 1204 communicating the offer. To avail of the offer you need to reply to the sms by sending \"YES\""], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Who is eligible for Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["All Wasel prepaid customers are eligible for Deal of the Day.", "Deal of the Day is not available for Postpaid/Enterprise and Five Sim customers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can the customer subscribe to the Deal of the Day offer?", "answer": ["\u2022 dial *050# or send DEAL to 1204\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 You will receive sms (from sender id 1204) which will carry the offer the customer is eligible for\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Reply to the message by sending YES to subscribe to the offer. You will receive a confirmation message confirming that the offer is activated"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How many offers can the customer subscribe to every day?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to only one offer daily. The offer is valid only for that day.\r\n", "\r\nIn order to get and subscribe to a new offer you have to dial *050# or send DEAL to 1204 again the next day"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will be the validity of the offers that I receive?", "answer": ["For the Recharge credit offer, Recharge credit is valid for 7 days, for the discounted packs the validity will depend on the type of pack that you."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the balance and/or expiry date of the bonus? ", "answer": ["On activation of your offer, you will receive the confirmation message. This message will have the ussd code that you have to dial in order to know the expiry of the free minutes/offers.", "Example \u2013 Dear Customer, You have received 30 Local minutes valid for today. To check your minutes balance dial *121*37#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the validity of the special offers that customers receive from Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["The validity of the offers depends on the type of offer the customer subscribes. The validity of the offer will be mentioned in the offer sms.\r\n", "\r\nExample - Dear Customer, You have received 15 International minutes valid for 7 days. To check your minutes balance dial *121*35#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is there a limit to the number of offers I can subscribe to?", "answer": ["No, there is no limit to the number of offers you can subscribe to. But you will receive and can subscribe to only one offer in a day. In order to subscribe to another offer, you need to dial *050# again the next day to get and subscribe to a new offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Which countries can be called using the International Calling Offers available as the Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["Please refer to the ", " to know about the countries you can call."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the local minute calling bundles and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["The local calling bundles are daily bundles of local minutes offered at lower rates. These bundles are available to all Wasel customers.", "When you make the first local call after subscription:", "\u2022 The rental for the bundle will be deducted\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 The minutes included in the bundle will be credited to your account\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Once you have used up all the bundle minutes for the day, local calls will be charged at the tariff plan rates for the rest of the day\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 International calls will also be charged as per your tariff plan", "You do not have to subscribe to the bundle every day. It will automatically be assigned to you once you make the first local call of the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to these bundles?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to the bundles by:\r\n", "\r\na) dialling *111# and choosing the relevant options.\r\n", "\r\nb) Sending an SMS to 1010 as follows:", "Once you have been successfully opted-in, you will receive an SMS from Etisalat confirming the same.\r\n", "\r\nOn the day of subscription, the benefits of the bundle will be applicable from the next local call made after you receive the confirmation SMS.\r\n", "\r\nOn subsequent days, the benefits of the bundle will be applicable from the first local call you make for the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Which numbers can be called using these bundled minutes?", "answer": ["You can use these minutes to call any UAE landline or mobile number (Etisalat and du).", "Calls to local premium numbers are not part of these bundles. Such calls will be charged as per your tariff plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long will these minutes in the bundles be valid for?", "answer": ["The bundle of minutes is valid for the day. Unused minutes (if any) will expire at the end of the day (midnight).", "A new bundle will be added to your account the next day as and when you make the first local call for the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How are these local bundles beneficial?", "answer": ["With these bundles you can enjoy a lower rate per minute for your local calls.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Discounted rate - On calls to any mobile or landline in the UAE\r\n", "\r\n- 44% savings on the Daily 5 minute and the Daily 10 minute bundles compared to standard local call rates\r\n", "\r\n- 63% savings on the Daily 30 minute bundle compared to standard local call rates\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Pay only on days you use \u2014 automatic renewal of bundle only on days you make local calls\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Affordable rentals with bundled minutes to suit your needs\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 No extra charges/fees applicable"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Will I be charged for the bundle every day even if I don\u2019t make any local calls?", "answer": ["No. You will be charged for the bundle only on days on which you make a local call.\r\n", "\r\nIf you do not make any local call during a day, there will be no charge for these bundles."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will I be charged for my local calls once I have subscribed to one of these bundles? ", "answer": ["\u2022 If you have subscribed to the 10 minute bundle, AED 2 will be deducted from your balance for the bundle and your account gets credited with 10 local minutes, once you make a local call\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 After you have used up these 10 minutes, your calls from the 11th minute for the day, would be charged as per your tariff plan\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 On days when you do not make any local calls, you would not be charged AED2"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How will I be charged if I do not have sufficient balance to cover the daily bundle rental? ", "answer": ["In case you do not have the necessary balance to cover the bundle rental, your calls will be charged as per the standard Wasel tariff plan.", "Once you have sufficient balance in your account, the rental will be deducted and the bundle minutes will be credited upon your next call of the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Once I use up all the daily minutes in the bundle, can I subscribe to the bundle again to get more minutes? ", "answer": ["Multiple subscriptions within the same day are not possible. However, there are two bundles to choose from; you can subscribe to any bundle that suits your usage pattern.", "Once you have used up all the bundle minutes for the day, local calls will be charged at the tariff plan rates for the rest of the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Are there any registration/subscription charges associated with this offer?", "answer": ["No, there are no registration/subscription charges associated with this offer. You will only be charged the daily rental for the bundle on days when you make a local call."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I upgrade or downgrade my Bundle? ", "answer": ["To upgrade/downgrade your bundle, just subscribe to the new bundle of your choice. The subscription for that bundle will come into effect from the next day.", " You can upgrade/downgrade/subscribe /unsubscribe only once a day and this will be effective from the next day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How do I check on the minutes balance of my bundle?", "answer": ["For enquiry related to this bundle, dial *101*1*2# and choose the relevant options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is this a temporary offer?", "answer": ["No, this is a permanent offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I opt out of this offer? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can opt-out any time. To opt-out, you can either:\r\n", "\r\na) dial *111# and choose the relevant options OR\r\n", "\r\nb) Send the following SMS to 1010", "Once you opt-out, you will be charged for all local calls as per your tariff plan.\r\n", "\r\nYou can opt-in any time again, by dialling *111# and choosing the relevant options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, there are no additional charges for this service. You just pay for the applications you choose to buy."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I need a special plan for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, your Data Plan is enough. Your data usage will be deducted from your plan allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am on Etisalat Postpaid, how I will pay for the apps? ", "answer": ["The amount for every application you purchase will be included in your next bill."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am on Wasel. How I will pay for the apps?  ", "answer": ["The amount will be deducted immediately from your credit balance. Make sure that you have enough balance before the purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is there any limit on my purchase?  ", "answer": ["Below are the limits set for Google Play transactions:\r\n", "\r\n- Per transaction limit AED 100\r\n", "\r\n- Per day transaction limit AED 200\r\n", "\r\n- Per month limit AED 500"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How much is the price for each application? ", "answer": ["Each application has price in AED, so you can easily decide to buy or not (no need to do currency conversion)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I use Wi-Fi only?  ", "answer": ["Yes you can."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What if the Application does not work on my handset?", "answer": ["- In 1st 15 minutes you can refund the application from the google play store itself.\r\n", "\r\n- After the initial 15 minutes, please contact the developer, email id will be mentioned on the application page on Google Play Store."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, there is no additional charge for this service. You just pay for the applications you purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": " Do I need special data plan for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, your Data Plan is enough. Your data usage will be deducted from your plan allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": " I am on Etisalat Postpaid, how I will pay for the apps? ", "answer": ["The amount for every application you purchase will be included in your next bill."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": " I am on Wassel. How I will pay for the apps?  ", "answer": ["The amount will be deducted immediately from your credit balance. Make sure that you have enough balance before the purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How much is the price for each application? ", "answer": ["Each application has price on the store, so you can easily decide to buy or not. No additional charges will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I use Wi-Fi only?  ", "answer": ["Yes, enter your mobile number and verification of your mobile number will be done."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What if the Application does not work on my handset?", "answer": ["Please contact the Windows Phone support, call the support line or send an email."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, there are no additional charges for this service. You just pay for the applications you purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I need special data plan for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, your Data Plan is enough. Your data usage will be deducted from your plan allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": " I am on Etisalat Postpaid, how I will pay for the apps? ", "answer": ["The amount for every application you purchase will be included in your next bill."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am on Wasel. How I will pay for the apps?  ", "answer": ["The amount will be deducted immediately from your credit balance. Make sure that you have enough balance before the purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How much is the price for each application? ", "answer": ["Each application has price in AED, so you can easily decide to buy or not (no need to do currency conversion). No additional charges will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": " Can I use Wi-Fi only?  ", "answer": ["Yes, verification of your mobile number will be done."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What if the Application does not work on my handset?", "answer": ["Please contact the Samsung Apps support, call the support line or send an email."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the Monthly Combo Packs?", "answer": ["The Monthly Combo packs are comprehensive packs containing voice minutes and data that serve the needs of light, medium, and high-end users. Wasel-Prepaid customers can choose the package that suits them the best and save on their monthly spends.", "*Flexi Minutes are applicable for Local &\u00a0 International calls. International calls are applicable to call ", ". Any additional minutes will be charged at regular rates."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I activate the Monthly Combo Packs?", "answer": ["To activate it, just dial *170*6# and choose Combos. Once activated, you\u2019ll receive an SMS confirmation."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What\u2019s the duration of the subscription and validity period of the pack?", "answer": ["Once activated, you\u2019ll enjoy the plan benefits for 30 days. The plan will be automatically renewed every month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I Deactivate the pack?", "answer": ["You can deactivate your Monthly Combo plan anytime by dialing *170*6# and choosing Combos. The remaining allowances will remain valid until their expiry time."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is Create your Number service ?", "answer": ["It is a new online channel to buy postpaid lines with the facility to search and customise your postpaid number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many packs can be purchased per day?", "answer": ["You can activate as many packs as you wish. Each pack will have its own allowance as well as validity period. If you use all your included allowance before the end of the validity period, the remaining usage will be charged as per your recharge type / current tariff plan unless you purchase a new pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I still enjoy my current prepaid tariff plan?", "answer": ["Yes, you can continue to benefit from your existing tariff. All your flexi minutes, data and social data usage will first be consumed from your monthly combo pack\u2019s allowance. Any usage beyond that will be consumed as per standard rates from your International Plus Balance, followed by your Credit Plus Balance, followed by your Main Account balance as per your existing tariff plan rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t use all my units within the 30 days?", "answer": ["Any unused Minutes or Data allowance will automatically expire and can\u2019t be carried over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I find out my remaining balance?", "answer": ["After each call, you\u2019ll receive an SMS containing details of your remaining minutes. For data, you\u2019ll receive an SMS once you\u2019ve used all your allowance. You can also check your remaining balance at any time by dialing *170*6#, and choosing Combo Balance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I use the Monthly Combo Packs on my BlackBerry?", "answer": ["If you are a Blackberry customer, you can use the flexi minutes as usual. However, to get the benefit of the data allowance, you need to have a BB10 operating system and above."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What countries are included in the Monthly Combo Packs?", "answer": ["You can call ", " with the International Minutes Packs."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t have enough balance in my account?", "answer": ["You will have to recharge your wasel prepaid account and activate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Who is eligible to use Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["Multi SIM service is applicable for Consumer plans (Postpaid and Prepaid) only. Multi SIM service is not applicable for Business customers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "If I am a ported-in customer, can I use Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["Yes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Where can I get the Multi-SIM Service?", "answer": ["Visit any of the "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Does my tariff plan matter?", "answer": ["The subscription to Multi SIM SIMs is independent of the main primary package subscribed by the customer.", "Example: if main SIM is data-only SIM then all cloned SIMs will be data-only as well. If customer has New Postpaid on his main SIM then all minutes, SMS, data packs etc. will also be available on cloned SIMs"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Does Multi-SIM support all networks?", "answer": ["Multi-SIM works on all types of networks (2G, 3G, and 4G)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What type of SIM cards work with Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["All SIM card types are supported - The customer will have the flexibility of adding/removing SIM cards and changing their type (mini/micro/nano SIM)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How many additional SIM cards can I get?", "answer": ["For Postpaid Customers:\r\n", "\r\n- You can get 4 additional SIM cards (all types of SIM cards)", "For Prepaid customers:\r\n", "\r\n- You can get 1 additional SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What services will work on Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["All services including roaming will be applicable on SIMs (primary + clones):", "a. Voice, data, SMS etc. will be active on all SIMs simultaneously", "b. Excluding receiving voice calls \u2013 it will be enabled only on one SIM at a time", "c. Excluding BlackBerry service \u2013 it will be active only on one SIM at a time"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I subscribe to a data package?", "answer": ["If a customer adds a data package to its primary service, then the data will be shared among all the SIMs part of the Multi SIM service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens is I migrate my Main SIM?", "answer": ["If a customer migrates from Post-paid to Prepaid Service or Vice-versa:", "The Multi SIM service will be deactivated when a customer requests for migration of service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens is if want to change my Main SIM package or tariff plan?", "answer": ["If the customer wants to upgrade/downgrade the data package or the primary service, then it does not have any effect on the Multi SIM service.", "For example, if the customer wants to migrate from the 1GB plan to a 5GB plan, then the data + voice as per the new plan that customer migrates to, is shared between all the SIMs subscribed by the customer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the codes to operate my Multi-SIM Service?", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am a postpaid customer, how much will Multi-SIM cost me?", "answer": ["All charges will be added to customer\u2019s bill.", "Monthly rental is applied on pro-rated basis (for example if the customer activates service on 15 April, then the customer needs to pay only for remaining 15 days of April)", "If the customer de-activates the service, there will be no refund for unused time during the month"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am a prepaid customer, how much will Multi-SIM cost me?", "answer": ["Rental charges are deducted in full from prepaid balance upfront.", "If rental deduction fails, then Multi-SIM service will be suspended. Customer will have to manually re-activate service after toping up account with required amount.", "If Multi-SIM service is suspended, only the clone SIM will be affected.", "If customer de-activates and re-activates his service, he will be charged the monthly rental in full - no pro-rating."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the Etisalat International Calling Offer and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["The Etisalat International Calling Offer is an optional subscription offer which any Wasel mobile customer can opt into. Upon successful opt-in, you will benefit from special per second International calling rates as per the details below"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What are the benefits of create your number?", "answer": ["There are numerous benefits of create your number such as:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many postpaid lines can I get?", "answer": ["You can get up to five postpaid lines."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I need to login to etisalat portal to purchase?", "answer": ["Yes, you should have Etisalat online account ( ", " ) to purchase the postpaid lines."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I link my postpaid line with my etisalat online account?", "answer": ["Once you signup/register to Etisalat Online Services( ", " ), simply follow the below 4 steps:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any additional cost to get a postpaid line from the website?", "answer": ["Any number to you choose comes for free with the associated plan except if you wish to take the number with the New Postpaid Basic plan, then you have to pay one-time fee of AED 500."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How long my order will take to be delivered ?", "answer": ["Your order will be delivered during 3 working days or less, you will receive a call from the courier to verify the address provided and agree on suitable timing for you."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the available plans to choose from?", "answer": ["If you select special number, you can take it along with any etisalat new postpaid line as below:", "New postpaid 50", "New postpaid 150", "New postpaid 250", "New postpaid 500", "New postpaid 1000"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How does the number search engine work?", "answer": ["After selecting you own choice, you need to select the prefix you wish to search from (050,056,054) then you need to insert any digit from your own choice by the desired sequence.", "Example: you can fill last 3 digits with 000, then system will search for all numbers that end with 000 or alternatively you can search for your birth date, car plate number or any relevant/special number related to your personal life."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I update or cancel my order?", "answer": ["Updating your order is not available for the time being, but you can cancel your order any time before the delivery by calling 101. The SIM card charges of AED 125 will not be returned & any other amount will be refunded back within 15 working days from the date of request of cancellation made through 101."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the Premium Postpaid Plans?", "answer": ["The Postpaid Plans are designed for those who are looking to be differentiated from other by selecting their own desired premium mobile number & the tariff plan which suites their lifestyle/ambitions, where they can get as much as they want from Etisalat in terms of: Special number, local calls, International calls and mobile data in UAE."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees? And what do I get for that rental?", "answer": ["For the details of plans, ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any minimum commitment period for the Premium Postpaid Plan?", "answer": ["Yes, the Premium Postpaid Plan is a 24-month contract plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing postpaid customer, can I migrate to the Premium Postpaid Plan?", "answer": ["No"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing prepaid customer, can I migrate to the Premium Postpaid Plan?", "answer": ["No"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the usage rates for the Premium Postpaid Plan?", "answer": ["The normal usage rates apply but on per second billing after you consume all the bundled minutes and data.\r\n", "\r\nOr if you do not subscribe to any of the Saving packs.\r\n", "\r\n- 0.5 fils per second for local calls.\r\n", "\r\n- 18 fils for National SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- 60 fils for International SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- AED 1/ MB for data usage.\r\n", "\r\n- Standard International rates apply on per second basis."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I use the available free data while roaming?", "answer": ["Data usage on the across all plans are for local data usage ONLY."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I wish to transfer the line to another person during the contract period?", "answer": ["Transfer of ownership is allowed during the contract period with exit charge and new customer will have the option to select any available mobile plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I wish to cancel my contract during the contract period?", "answer": ["Our Premium Postpaid Plan is based on a 24-month contract. If you wish to cancel the contract before hand, exit fees will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I migrate my line to normal postpaid or prepaid?", "answer": ["For line migration to normal postpaid or prepaid it is allowed during the contract period; however, exit fees will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Postpaid? ", "answer": ["The New Postpaid is a completely new approach to how you stay in touch. With our new add-on system, you can customise your New Postpaid with 7 types of add-ons, whenever you want. Beyond flexibility, you'll enjoy great value with our new per-second billing system. Here's a look at some of the perks waiting for you with the New Postpaid:", "- Per-second billing", "- Incredible rates on local, international and incoming roaming calls", "- Great value on data, SMS and extra feature", "- Ultimate add-on flexibility in customising your line"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the 7 add-ons in the new Plan?", "answer": ["The 7 add-ons in the New Postpaid plan are:", "- Local minutes add-on", "- International minutes add-on", "- Flexible minutes add-on", "- Data add-on", "- SMS add-on", "- Incoming roaming minutes add-on", "- Free Etisalat number add-on"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the flexible minutes add-on?", "answer": ["This is a new add-on that allows you to use 150 flexible minutes to make local calls or international calls."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there a call setup fee?", "answer": ["No, there's no call setup fee and there are no additional charges. The rates are charged on a flat, per second basis."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How is this offer beneficial to customers?", "answer": ["- This plan offers great savings on International calls,\r\n", "\r\n- There are no extra charges like call set-up fee\r\n", "\r\n- Enjoy a flat per second rate\r\n", "\r\n- You can make a call any time of the day or week"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to this offer?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to this tariff plan by dialling *135*70#\r\n", "\r\nOnce you have been successfully opted-in, you will receive an SMS from Etisalat confirming the same. The benefits of this offer will be applicable for all calls made after this confirmation SMS have been received."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I benefit from the special promotion of the special calls to NTC-NEPAL?", "answer": ["If you have already subscribed to the International Calling offer, you would have to call any NTC-Nepal number and enjoy the special discounted rates of Rate is 32 fils/min (5% VAT included). If you haven\u2019t subscribed to the offer yet, you would have to first subscribe to the offer by dialing *135*70#, once you have successfully activated your offer you can enjoy the special rates immediately."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What will happen if I call a non NTC Nepal number?", "answer": ["If you are subscribed to the International Calling offer and calling a non NTC- Nepal number then your call will be charged at Rate is 63 fils/Min (5% VAT included)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to configure or select my preferred country from these countries to enjoy the special rates?", "answer": ["No. Once you have opted into this offer, you will automatically start enjoying these special rates for all your calls to the specified countries."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is there a charge for subscription?", "answer": ["Subscription to this offer is free."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am a Per Minute Wasel tariff plan customer. How would I be charged for my calls after I have opted into this offer?", "answer": ["Once you have opted-in to this offer you will be charged as following:", "For full countries list and rates "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am already subscribed to Call International Pay Local & Global Calling Plan. In addition, after I subscribe to this offer, at what rates will my calls be charged?", "answer": ["If you have opted into all three offers, your calls will be charged as per the International Calling Offer rates.", "For example, If you make calls to India, you will be charged at 0.6 fils per second (36 fils per minute)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I subscribed to the Daily Combo Pack and the International Calling Offer. How will I be charged for my calls?", "answer": ["If you've subscribed to any of our bundles, then the minutes would first be consumed from your bundle balance, followed by minutes outside your bundle which will be charged as per the International Calling Offer rates."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I opt out of the International Calling Offer? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can opt-out any time by dialing *135*70#.\r\n", "\r\n- Once opted-out, you will be charged for calls to these countries as per your standard tariff plan.\r\n", "\r\n- You can opt-in any time again, by any of the subscription mode mentioned above."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "International Offers", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the remaining allowances?", "answer": ["You can Check your remaining allowances by dialing *101# and choosing Option 1 - Account Management."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the Pinoy Pack and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["The Pinoy Pack is a weekly bundle, which offers customers a range of benefits for AED 20 weekly fee. Customers enjoy:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 20 minutes to Philippine\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 20 minutes to UAE\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 210 Barkada minutes for all week**\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 250 Flexi SMS\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Non-stop mobile internet - no restrictions on what you can browse or chat!*", "Note: ** Barkada Minutes can only be used to call other Pinoy Pack customers.\r\n", "\r\n* Internet speed is up to 192kbps and reduces to 64Kbps after reaching the weekly fair usage allowance\r\n", "\r\n* Roaming service is not possible with Pinoy pack\r\n", "\r\n5% VAT Excluded"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to these bundles?", "answer": ["- You can subscribe to the bundles by sending ", " as a text to 1012.\r\n", "\r\n- Once you have subscribed, you will receive a text from Etisalat confirming the same.\r\n", "\r\n- After this, you do not have to subscribe to the bundle every week. It will automatically be assigned to you once the validity of the earlier pack is over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I need to buy a new Etisalat number to get the Pinoy Pack?", "answer": ["- No, you can subscribe to the Pinoy Pack from your existing Etisalat prepaid mobile. All you need to do is send ", " as a text to 1012.\r\n", "\r\n- If you have a du number, you can easily upgrade your existing 055/052 number to the Etisalat network and then subscribe to the Pinoy Pack without having to change your number!\r\n", "\r\n- Details on how to upgrade to Etisalat are available on ", "."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How long will these minutes and text messages  in the bundles be valid for?", "answer": ["The bundle of minutes and texts is valid for 1 week (7 days) from the date of opt-in. Unused minutes and texts , if any, will expire at the end of this period. For example, if you subscribe to the pack on 10:00 am on 1st February 2014, the pack and its minutes and texts will be valid till 9:59 am on 8th February 2014. A new bundle will be added to your account as and when the validity of the earlier pack is over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How is the Pinoy Pack beneficial?", "answer": ["\u2022 20 minutes to Philippine\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 20 minutes to UAE\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 210 Barkada minutes for all week**\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 250 Flexi SMS\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Non-stop mobile internet - no restrictions on what you can browse or chat!*", "Note: ** Barkada Minutes can only be used to call other Pinoy Pack customers\r\n", "\r\n* Internet speed is up to 192kbps and reduces to 64Kbps after reaching the weekly fair usage allowance\r\n", "\r\n* Roaming service is not possible with Pinoy pack\r\n", "\r\n5% VAT Excluded"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Once I use up all the minutes/SMS in the bundle, do I have to subscribe to the Pinoy Pack again? ", "answer": ["Once you have used up all the bundle minutes/texts, you will be charged for calls and texts as per your tariff plan for the rest of the week. Upon the completion of 1 week, your pack will be automatically renewed for another week after the rental deduction."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Are there any registration/subscription charges associated with this offer?", "answer": ["No, there are no registration/subscription charges associated with this offer.\r\n", "\r\nYou will only be charged the weekly rental for the bundle."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How do I check on the minutes balance of my bundle?", "answer": ["\r\n            ", " and Choose Special Packs Option."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is this a temporary offer?", "answer": ["No, this is a permanent offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I opt-out or unsubscribe to this offer? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can opt-out any time. To opt-out, send ", " as a text to ", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n- Once you opt-out, any remaining minutes or SMS in your Pinoy Pack account, will remain valid till the end of the subscription period.\r\n", "\r\n- You can subscribe again to the bundles anytime by sending ", " as a text to 1012.\r\n", "\r\n- Any re-subscription will come into effect after the validity of the current pack is over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the Global Calling Plan and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["The Global Calling Plan is an optional subscription offer which any Wasel mobile customer can opt into. Upon successful opt-in, you will benefit from special per second International calling rates as per the details below:", "NOTE: Calls to Other International destinations will be charged as per standard rates on a per-second basis (5% VAT included). ", " for the complete list of countries."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay for the new plan and add-ons? ", "answer": ["- You pay AED 50 per month for each add-on", "- Plan monthly fee is AED 50"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose only some of the add-ons? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can subscribe to any of the add-ons that you choose. You can even subscribe and cancel at anytime during the month", "- Pro rated rental and allowances will be applied in case you add any of the add-ons anytime during the month"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I make and manage my new Plan? ", "answer": ["- You can add/remove and increase/decrease any of the add-ons anytime during the month", "- 6 channels you can choose to do so: Online (e4me) - mobile application - IVR - SMS - USSD - CCC - BC", "- When you add any of the add-ons in the middle of the month, the rental is charged on pro rata basis and the allowance is provided on pro rata basis. Eg.,: if you add one local minute add-on on the 15th of the month, you will be charged only AED 25 and get 100 minutes", "- When you remove any of the add-ons in the middle of the month, the rental is not refunded and the remaining allowances will be kept to use till the end of the month and will be removed at the start of the next month"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay to buy a new postpaid connection?", "answer": ["Connection fees are AED 125."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am an existing postpaid customer can I migrate to the new plan? ", "answer": ["- If you are an existing postpaid customer on a non-contract plan you can migrate to the new plan by calling 101 or visiting a Business Centre", "- If you are an existing postpaid customer on a contract plan you have to first visit the Business Centre, terminate the contract and pay the applicable exit charges and then migrate to the new plan"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing prepaid customer can I migrate to the new plan? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can migrate to the new plan by calling 101 or visiting the Business Centre."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the international minutes add-on be applied to all countries? ", "answer": ["The international minutes add-on and flexible minutes add-on will be applied to most of the countries BUT there will be a list of countries that this will not be applied on."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the Incoming Roaming add-on be applied to all operators?", "answer": ["The incoming roaming minute\u2019s add-on will be applied to most of the operators BUT there will be a list of operators that this will not be applied on."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I would like to cancel my new postpaid connection how can I do that?", "answer": ["You can cancel your new postpaid connection by visiting your nearest etisalat store. Please note that if you cancel within the first 6 months, you\u2019ll be charged a cancellation fee of AED 300."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will I still be able to use the service if the bill amount is not paid by the due date?", "answer": ["Etisalat has put in place a number of SMS reminders starting from a Mini-Statement Bill, to a warning SMS before disconnecting the service and following the legal collection process. In the event of missed payment of dues on your Mobile Postpaid account, Etisalat would follow different processes to remind and recover the dues.", "The process goes through a stepped approach, starting with an initial suspension of video calls functionality, followed by suspending outgoing voice calls and SMS and finally, a full suspension of all services which is suspending incoming calls, SMS and data communication."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Postpaid 150 Plan? ", "answer": ["For the first time in the UAE, the New Postpaid 150 plan gives 6GB Data+ 500 local minutes or 6GB data + 200 flexible minutes and unlimited calls to one preferred Etisalat number for only AED 150 per month. Furthermore, you can still choose to customize your plan with unbeatable value saving packs."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees? And what do I get for that rental?", "answer": ["The monthly rental is AED 150/month and you get:", "6GB data + 600 Local minutes and unlimited calls to one preferred Etisalat number every month", "OR", "6GB data + 250 flexible minutes and unlimited calls to one preferred Etisalat number every month"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I set my free preferred number? ", "answer": ["Please send an sms with \u201cFNF 9715xxxxxxxx\u201d to 1012."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I change my free preferred number?", "answer": ["Please, send an sms with \u201cR FNF space <Old Number> <New Number> \u201d to 1012.", "Note: Free preferred number is allowed only once a month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any minimum commitment period for the New Postpaid 150 Plan?", "answer": ["Yes, the yearly new postpaid plan is a 24 months contract plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I want a new postpaid Connection on the New Postpaid 150 Plan how much should I pay? ", "answer": ["New postpaid connection fees is AED 125."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing postpaid customer, can I migrate to the New Postpaid 150 Plan? ", "answer": ["- If you are a classic postpaid customer OR MyPlan customer without contract OR iPhone customer without contract you can migrate to the new plan by visiting etisalat business center.\r\n", "\r\n- If you are a MyPlan customer with contract OR a smart phone \u201ciPhone/Samsung/HTC\u201d plan customer with contract you have to visit the Business Center and terminate the contract and pay the applicable exit charges and then migrate to the new plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing prepaid customer, can I migrate to the New Postpaid 150 Plan? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can migrate to the new plan by visiting your nearest ", ".\r\n", "\r\n- All the current migration rules and procedures will continue to apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the usage rates for the New Postpaid 150 Plan? ", "answer": ["The normal usage rates apply but on per second billing after you consume all the bundled minutes, SMS and data.", "Or if you do not subscribe to any of the Saving packs.\r\n", "\r\n- 0.5 fils per second for local calls for 12 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 0.6 fils per second for local calls for 24 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 18 fils for National SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- 60 fils for International SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- AED 1/ MB for data usage.\r\n", "\r\n- Standard International rates apply on per second basis."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the 7 Saving packs that I can subscribe to on top of my New Postpaid 150 Plan? ", "answer": ["The 7 Saving packs in the new postpaid plan are:\r\n", "\r\n1. Local minutes saving pack. (200 local minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n2. International minutes saving pack. (100 International minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n3. Flexible minutes saving pack. (150 Flexible minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n4. Data saving pack. (1GB for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n5. Flexible SMS saving pack. (500 Flexible SMS for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n6. Incoming Roaming minutes saving pack. (50 Incoming roaming minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n7. Unlimited calls to Etisalat numbers saving pack. (1 preferred number for AED 50/month)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees for each of the saving packs?", "answer": ["The monthly rental fee for each saving pack is AED 50/month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose only some of the Saving packs? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can subscribe to any of the Saving packs that you choose. You can even subscribe and cancel at any time during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- Pro-rated rental and allowances will be applied in case you add any of the Saving packs anytime during the month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How to subscribe/unsubscribe?", "answer": ["To subscribe: SMS 'OGCP' to 1012.\r\n", "\r\nTo unsubscribe: SMS 'COGCP' to 1012"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How is this offer beneficial to me?", "answer": ["- This plan offers great savings on International calls.\r\n", "\r\n- You can make a call any time of the day or week.\r\n", "\r\n- Enjoy a flat per second rate.\r\n", "\r\n- There is no call set-up fee."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to configure or select my preferred country from these countries to enjoy the special rates?", "answer": ["No. Once you have opted into this offer, you will automatically start enjoying these special rates for all your calls to the specified countries."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I know the rate of a particular country on this offer?", "answer": ["To know the rate for a particular destination, you can:\r\n", "\r\n- ", " to see the complete list of countries and tariffs."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "I am a Per Minute Wasel tariff plan customer. How would I be charged for my calls after I have opted into this offer?", "answer": ["Once you have opted-in to this offer, all your calls to:\r\n", "\r\n- (example) India will be charged at 0.63 AED/min.\r\n", "\r\n- (example) Philippines will be charged at 1.26 AED/min.\u00a0\r\n", "\r\n- (example) UK will be charged at 1.89 AED/min.\r\n", "\r\nYour National calls will be charged as per standard rates on a per minute basis. (5% VAT inluded)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Is this offer a temporary offer?", "answer": ["No, this is a permanent / ongoing offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the SMS Packs?", "answer": ["Etisalat offers its Prepaid Wasel customers SMS packs at a great price. You can choose any pack based on your needs. What\u2019s more, you can purchase as many packs as you need."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Local SMS Pack?", "answer": ["*Validity of the packs is 30 days"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "International SMS Pack?", "answer": ["Subscribe to our international SMS bundles and benefit from lower international SMS rates.", "*International SMSs valid for 100 destinations. Additional SMSs will be charged at regular rates. ", "Note: International SMS bundles are valid for prepaid customers only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I activate the SMS Pack?", "answer": ["Once the pack has been purchased a confirmation SMS will be sent."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to activate the SMS Pack every time it expires?", "answer": ["Yes, these are one-off packs that can be purchased as many times as you wish whenever needed. At the end of the validity period the packs will be expired and you would have to repurchase them again.\u00a0"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t have enough balance in my account?", "answer": ["You will have to recharge your wasel prepaid account and try activating the pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I Deactivate these packs?", "answer": ["Since these are a one-off packs there would be no need to deactivate them since you have already paid for them. You can continue using the included messages until your pack expires."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I purchase multiple SMS Pack of the same category at the same time?", "answer": ["Yes, you can purchase multiple packs of the same category at the same time, each pack will have its own allowance and validity period."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I still enjoy my current prepaid tariff plan?", "answer": ["Yes, you can continue to benefit from your existing tariff. Any National SMS sent will first be consumed from your monthly SMS pack, any usage beyond that will be charged from your main balance and as per your existing tariff plan rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t use all my SMS within the validity period?", "answer": ["All unused SMS will automatically be expired."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I check my remaining SMS balance?", "answer": ["After each call, you\u2019ll receive an SMS containing details of your remaining SMS. You can also check your remaining balance at any time by dialing *101# and choosing Option 1 - Account Management."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Easy recharge methods", "answer": ["Etisalat offers you convenient ways to recharge your prepaid line:\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "It is simple. Download the free Etisalat UAE mobile app, create your account, view your information, recharge and do lots more. The app is available on iOS App Store, Google Play, BlackBerry and Windows Stores.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "Recharge your prepaid mobile account on ", ". It is quick, convenient and safe. Enter your mobile number, amount and pay online using your credit or debit card.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "Conveniently recharge your prepaid mobile account on ", ". Log in and pay online using your credit card or debit card.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "Buy an Etisalat recharge card or eVoucher from any store or an Etisalat partner that is closest to you. Recharge by dialing *120*[card number]#.\r\n"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Other recharge methods", "answer": ["\u2022 ", "You can easily and securely transfer credit locally from one prepaid or postpaid mobile account to another prepaid account by dialing *100*phone number*amount# and pressing OK.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "Our International credit transfer service lets you transfer credit to any number in the world at amazing international exchange rates. It is free. Send the international number via SMS to 1700.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "Recharge your prepaid account using Etisalat Payment Machines located at Etisalat\u2019s stores and other strategic locations across the UAE.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 ", "Recharge your prepaid account using your preferred bank\u2019s ATM channel or through the bank\u2019s online banking, phone banking, mobile banking and other services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose multiples of the same saving pack? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can choose to have multiples of the same saving pack up to 10 Saving packs per type of saving pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I make and manage my Saving Packs? ", "answer": ["- You can add/remove and increase/decrease any of the Saving packs anytime during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- 7 channels you can choose to do so:\r\n", "\r\nUSSD *140# \u2013 download etisalat mobile app \u2013 IVR 125 - Etisalat call center 101 - Online (e4me) - Etisalat stores, SMS\r\n", "\r\n- When you add any of the Saving packs in the middle of the month the rental is charged on pro-rata basis and the allowance is provided in pro-rata basis. Ex: customer adds one local minute saving pack in 15th of the month customer is charged only AED25 and gets 100 minutes.\r\n", "\r\n- When you remove any of the Saving packs in the middle of the month the rental is not refunded and the remaining allowances will be kept to use till end of the month and will be removed from start of next month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the International minutes saving pack be applied on all countries? ", "answer": ["The International minutes saving pack will be applied on most of the countries BUT there will be a blacklist of countries that this will not be applied to. Please visit ", " for more details."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the Incoming Roaming saving pack be applied with all operators? ", "answer": ["The Incoming roaming minutes saving pack will be applied on most of the operators BUT there will be a blacklist of operators that this will not be applied to. Please visit ", " for more details."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I would like to cancel my New Postpaid 150 Plan connection, how can I do that?", "answer": ["You can cancel the line by visiting your nearest Etisalat store. Please note that you will be charged early termination fee of AED 100* remaining contract months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Postpaid 250 plan? ", "answer": ["Get up to 18GB data + 1000 local minutes or 500 flexible minutes for only AED 250 per month. In addition, you can choose to customize your plan with unbeatable value add-ons. Also Enrich your lifestyle with smiles points where you can use them for shopping, dining, entertainment and great discounts.", "*smiles points will be given over 12 months period"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees  for the New Postpaid 250 plan? And what do I get for that rental?", "answer": ["The Monthly rental for the New Postpaid 250 plan is AED 250 per month and you get:"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any minimum commitment period for the New Postpaid 250 plan?", "answer": ["Yes, the yearly new postpaid plan has 12 months and 24 months contract options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I want a new postpaid Connection on the New Postpaid 250 plan how much should I pay? ", "answer": ["New postpaid connection fees is AED 125."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I  am an existing postpaid customer can I migrate to the New Postpaid 250 plan? ", "answer": ["- If you are a classic postpaid customer OR MyPlan customer without contract OR iPhone customer without contract you can migrate to the new plan by visiting any Etisalat Business Center.\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n- If you are a MyPlan customer with contract OR iPhone/Samsung/HTC plan customer with contract you have visit the Business Center and terminate the contract and pay the applicable exit charges and then migrate to the new plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing prepaid customer can I migrate to the New  Postpaid 250 plan? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can migrate to the new plan by visiting your nearest etisalat Business Center .\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n- All the current migration rules and procedures will continue to apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the usage rates for the New Postpaid 250 plan ? ", "answer": ["The normal usage rates apply but on per second billing after you consume all the bundled minutes, sms and data.", "Or if you do not subscribe to any of the add ons.\r\n", "\r\n- 0.5 fils per second for local calls for 12 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 0.6 fils per second for local calls for 24 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 18 fils for National SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- 60 fils for International SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- AED 1/ MB for data usage.\r\n", "\r\n- Standard International rates apply on per second basis."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the 7 add ons that I can subscribe to on top of my New Postpaid 250 Plan? ", "answer": ["The 7 add ons in the new postpaid plan are:\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\n1. Local minutes add on. (200 local minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n2. International minutes add on. (100 International minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n3. Flexible minutes add on. (150 Flexible minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n4. Data add on. (1GB for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n5. Flexible SMS add on. (500 Flexible SMS for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n6. Incoming Roaming minutes add on. (50 Incoming roaming minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n7. Unlimited calls to Etisalat numbers add on. (1 preferred number add on for AED 50/month)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees  for each of the add ons ?", "answer": ["The monthly rental fee for each add on is AED 50 per month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose only some of the add ons? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can subscribe to any of the add ons that you choose. You can even subscribe and cancel at any time during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- Pro-rated rental and allowances will be applied in case you add any of the add ons anytime during the month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose multiples of the same add on? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can choose to have multiples of the same add on up to 10 add ons per type of add on."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I make and manage my New Postpaid 250 Plan? ", "answer": ["You can add/remove and increase/decrease any of the add ons anytime during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- 7 channels you can choose to do so:\r\n", "\r\nSMS - USSD - Online (e4me) - mobile application - IVR - Etisalat call center 101 - Etisalat stores.\r\n", "\r\n- When you add any of the add ons in the middle of the month the rental is charged on pro rata basis and the allowance is provided in pro rata basis. Ex: customer adds one local minute add on in 15th of the month customer is charged only AED25 and gets 100 minutes.\r\n", "\r\n- When you remove any of the add ons in the middle of the month the rental is not refunded and the remaining allowances will be kept to use till end of the month and will be removed from start of next month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the International minutes add on be applied on all countries? ", "answer": ["The Incoming roaming minutes add on will be applied on most of the operators BUT there will be a Blacklist of operators that this will not be applied on."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the Incoming Roaming add on be applied with all operators? ", "answer": ["The Incoming roaming minutes add on will be applied on most of the operators BUT there will be a Blacklist of operators that this will not be applied on."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I would like to cancel my new postpaid connection how can I do that?", "answer": ["You can cancel the line by visiting your nearest Etisalat store. Please note that you will be charged early termination fee of AED 100* remaining contract months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the Daily Combo Pack?", "answer": ["The Daily Combo pack is a combination of voice minutes and mobile data for customers with light usage. Once subscribed, customers can enjoy making local and/or international calls, surf the net, use social networking apps, as well as send texts daily."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I activate the Daily Combo Pack?", "answer": ["To subscribe: SMS to 1012 with ODCP"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What\u2019s the duration of the subscription and validity period of the pack?", "answer": ["Once activated, you\u2019ll enjoy the pack benefits every day. The pack is automatically renewed every 24 hours, at the same time you first activated the offer. You\u2019ll stay subscribed to the offer until you deactivate it. E.g. if you activate the pack at 7pm, the pack will remain active for 24 hours and a new pack will be renewed the following day at 7pm."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to activate the Daily Combo Pack every day?", "answer": ["No, the pack will be renewed automatically every 24 hours (from the time of first activation) and AED 2.50 (5% VAT excluded). Will be deducted from your main account. Each day when the pack expires, a new pack will be activated and you\u2019ll be notified via SMS."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I deactivate the pack?", "answer": ["To unsubscribe: SMS to 1012 with C ODCP. The remaining allowance will remain valid until their expiry time. You can re-activate the pack again at any time after the expiry time of your pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I still enjoy my current prepaid tariff plan?", "answer": ["Yes, you can continue to benefit from your existing tariff. All your flexi minutes, data and flexi SMS usage will first be consumed from your daily combo pack allowance. Any usage beyond that will be consumed as per standard rates from your International Plus Balance, followed by your Credit Plus Balance, followed by your Main Account balance as per your existing tariff plan rate."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t use all my allowance within 24 hours?", "answer": ["Any unused Minutes, SMSs or Data allowance will automatically expire and can\u2019t be carried over."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the remaining allowances?", "answer": ["You can Check your remaining allowances by dialing *101# and choosing Option 1 - Account Management."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "Can I use the Daily Combo Pack on my BlackBerry?", "answer": ["If you are a Blackberry customer, you can use the flexi minutes and SMS as usual. However, to get the benefit of the data allowance, you need to have a BB10 operating system and above."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What countries are included in the Daily Combo pack?", "answer": ["You can call 100 countries with the International Minutes Packs. To see the list of countries "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I don\u2019t have enough balance in my account?", "answer": ["- First time subscription: You will have to recharge your wasel prepaid account and try activating the pack again.\r\n", "\r\n- Renewal: You will have a grace period of 3 days to recharge your account in order to continue enjoying the pack, after which the pack will be removed from your account. In case you which to re-subscribe, you will have to recharge your account and activate the pack again."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_prepaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Postpaid 500 Plan? ", "answer": ["Get up to 25GB data + 2200 local minutes or 1200 flexible minutes for only AED 500 per month and ", ". In addition, you can choose to customize your plan with unbeatable value ", ". Also enrich your lifestyle with ", " where you can use them for shopping, dining, entertainment and great discounts.", "*smiles points will be given over 12 months period"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees? And what do I get for that rental?", "answer": ["The Monthly rental for the New Postpaid 500 plan is AED 500 per month added with a lot of benefits:", "*smiles points will be given over 12 months period"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any minimum commitment period for the New Postpaid 500 Plan?", "answer": ["Yes, the yearly new postpaid plan has 12 months and 24 months contract options"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I want a new postpaid Connection on the New Postpaid 500 Plan how much should I pay? ", "answer": ["New postpaid connection fees is AED 125."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing postpaid customer, can I migrate to the New Postpaid 500 Plan? ", "answer": ["- If you are a classic postpaid customer OR MyPlan customer without contract OR iPhone customer without contract you can migrate to the new plan by visiting etisalat business center.\r\n", "\r\n- If you are a MyPlan customer with contract OR a smart phone \u201ciPhone/Samsung/HTC\u201d plan customer with contract you have to visit the Business Center and terminate the contract and pay the applicable exit charges and then migrate to the new plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing prepaid customer, can I migrate to the New Postpaid 500 Plan? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can migrate to the new plan by visiting your nearest etisalat Business Center.\r\n", "\r\n- All the current migration rules and procedures will continue to apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the usage rates for the New Postpaid 500 Plan? ", "answer": ["The normal usage rates apply but on per second billing after you consume all the bundled minutes, sms and data.", "Or if you do not subscribe to any of the Saving packs.\r\n", "\r\n- 0.5 fils per second for local calls for 12 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 0.6 fils per second for local calls for 24 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 18 fils for National SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- 60 fils for International SMS.\r\n", "\r\n- AED 1/ MB for data usage.\r\n", "\r\n- Standard International rates apply on per second basis."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the 7 Saving packs that I can subscribe to on top of my New Postpaid 500 Plan? ", "answer": ["The 7 Saving packs in the new postpaid plan are:\r\n", "\r\n1. Local minutes saving pack. (200 local minutes for AED 50/Mth).\r\n", "\r\n2. International minutes saving pack. (100 International minutes for AED 50/Mth).\r\n", "\r\n3. Flexible minutes saving pack. (150 Flexible minutes for AED 50/Mth).\r\n", "\r\n4. Data saving pack. (1GB for AED 50/Mth).\r\n", "\r\n5. Flexible SMS saving pack. (500 Flexible SMS for AED 50/Mth).\r\n", "\r\n6. Incoming Roaming minutes saving pack. (50 Incoming roaming minutes for AED 50/Mth).\r\n", "\r\n7. Unlimited calls to Etisalat numbers saving pack. (1 preferred number for AED 50/Mth)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees for each of the saving packs?", "answer": ["The monthly rental fee for each saving pack is AED 50/month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose only some of the Saving packs? ", "answer": ["- Yes, you can subscribe to any of the Saving packs that you choose. You can even subscribe and cancel at any time during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- Pro-rated rental and allowances will be applied in case you add any of the Saving packs anytime during the month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose multiples of the same saving pack? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can choose to have multiples of the same saving pack up to 10 Saving packs per type of saving pack."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I make and manage my Saving Packs? ", "answer": ["- You can add/remove and increase/decrease any of the Saving packs anytime during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- 7 channels you can choose to do so:\r\n", "\r\nUSSD *140# \u2013 download etisalat mobile app \u2013 IVR 125 - Etisalat call center 101 - Online (e4me) - Etisalat stores, SMS\r\n", "\r\n- When you add any of the Saving packs in the middle of the month the rental is charged on pro rata basis and the allowance is provided in pro rata basis. Ex: customer adds one local minute saving pack in 15th of the month customer is charged only AED25 and gets 100 minutes.\r\n", "\r\n- When you remove any of the Saving packs in the middle of the month the rental is not refunded and the remaining allowances will be kept to use till end of the month and will be removed from start of next month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the International minutes saving pack be applied on all countries? ", "answer": ["The International minutes saving pack will be applied on most of the countries BUT there will be a blacklist of countries that this will not be applied to. Please visit ", " for more details."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the Incoming Roaming saving pack be applied with all operators? ", "answer": ["The Incoming roaming minutes saving pack will be applied on most of the operators BUT there will be a blacklist of operators that this will not be applied to. Please visit www.etisalat.ae for more details."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I would like to cancel my New Postpaid 500 Plan connection, how can I do that?", "answer": ["You can cancel the line by visiting your nearest Etisalat store. Please note that you will be charged early termination fee of AED 100* remaining contract months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Postpaid 1000 Plan?", "answer": ["Get up to 1000GB data + 5000 local minutes or 2000 flexible minutes for only AED 1000 per month. In addition, you can choose to customize your plan with unbeatable value add-ons. Also Enrich your lifestyle with smiles points where you can use them for shopping, dining, entertainment and great discounts.", "*smiles points will be given over 12 months period"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees? And what do I get for that rental?", "answer": ["The Monthly rental for the New Postpaid 1000 plan is AED 1000 per month and you get:", "*smiles points will be given over 12 months period"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any minimum commitment period for the New Postpaid 1000 Plan?", "answer": ["Yes, the yearly new postpaid plan has 12 months and 24 months contract options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I want a new postpaid connection on the New Postpaid 1000 Plan, how much should I pay?", "answer": ["New postpaid connection fees is AED 125."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing postpaid customer, can I migrate to the New Postpaid 1000 Plan?", "answer": ["- If you are a classic postpaid customer OR MyPlan customer without contract OR iPhone customer without contract, you can migrate to the new plan by visiting any Etisalat business center.\r\n", "\r\n- If you are a MyPlan customer with a contract OR a smart phone \u201ciPhone/Samsung/HTC\u201d plan customer with contract, you have to visit the Business Center and terminate the contract and pay the applicable exit charges and then migrate to the new plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am an existing prepaid customer, can I migrate to the New Postpaid 1000 Plan?", "answer": ["- Yes, you can migrate to the new plan. All you have to do is to pay a visit to the nearest Etisalat Business Center.\r\n", "\r\n- All the current migration rules and procedures will continue to apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the usage rates for the New Postpaid 1000 Plan?", "answer": ["The normal usage rates apply but on per second billing after you consume all the bundled minutes, SMS's, and data; or if you do not subscribe to any of the Saving packs.\r\n", "\r\n- 0.5 fils per second for local calls for 12 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 0.6 fils per second for local calls for 24 months plans\r\n", "\r\n- 18 fils for national SMS\r\n", "\r\n- 60 fils for international SMS\r\n", "\r\n- AED 1/ MB for data usage\r\n", "\r\n- Standard International rates apply on per second basis"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the 7 Saving Packs that I can subscribe to on top of my New Postpaid 1000 Plan?", "answer": ["The 7 Saving Packs in the new postpaid plan are:\r\n", "\r\n1. Local minutes saving pack. (200 local minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n2. International minutes saving pack. (100 International minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n3. Flexible minutes saving pack. (150 Flexible minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n4. Data saving pack. (1GB for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n5. Flexible SMS saving pack. (500 Flexible SMS for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n6. Incoming Roaming minutes saving pack. (50 Incoming roaming minutes for AED 50/month).\r\n", "\r\n7. Unlimited calls to Etisalat numbers saving pack. (1 preferred number for AED 50/month)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much should I pay as monthly rental fees for each of the saving packs?", "answer": ["The monthly rental fee for each saving pack is AED 50/month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose only some of the Saving Packs?", "answer": ["- Yes, you can subscribe to any of the Saving packs that you choose. You can even subscribe and cancel at any time during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- Pro-rated rental and allowances will be applied in case you add any of the Saving packs anytime during the month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I choose multiples of the same saving pack?", "answer": ["Yes, you can choose to have multiples of the same saving pack, up to 10 saving packs per type."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I manage my Saving Packs?", "answer": ["You can add/remove and increase/decrease any of the Saving Packs anytime during the month.\r\n", "\r\nTo do so, you can use 7 channels:\r\n", "\r\n- USSD *140#\r\n", "\r\n\u2013 download Etisalat Mobile App\r\n", "\r\n\u2013 IVR 125\r\n", "\r\n- Etisalat call center 101\r\n", "\r\n- Online\r\n", "\r\n- Etisalat stores\r\n", "\r\n- SMS\r\n", "\r\nWhen you add any of the Saving packs in the middle of the month, the rental is charged on pro rata basis and the allowance is provided in pro rata basis. For example: a customer adds one local minute saving pack in 15th of the month; the customer is charged only AED 25 and gets 100 minutes.\r\n", "\r\nWhen you remove any of the Saving packs in the middle of the month, the rental is not refunded and the remaining allowances will be kept for usage until the end of the month and will be removed as of the coming month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the International minutes saving pack be applied to all countries?", "answer": ["The International Minutes Saving Pack will be applied to most of the countries; however, there is a blacklist of countries that this will not be applied to. Please, visit ", " for more details."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will the Incoming Roaming Saving Pack be applied to all operators?", "answer": ["The Incoming Roaming Minutes Saving Pack will be applied to most of the operators; however, there is a blacklist of operators that this will not be applied to. Please, visit ", " for more details."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I would like to cancel my New Postpaid 1000 Plan connection, how can I do that?", "answer": ["You can cancel the line by visiting your nearest Etisalat store. Please note that you will be charged an early termination fee of AED 100* remaining contract months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is Etisalat Emirati Plan?", "answer": ["Etisalat Emirati Plan is an exciting new plan which offers voice, data and minutes to preferred numbers .That covers your local calls and data usage."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the charges for the Local calls after the included minutes are over?", "answer": ["Local calls out of the included minutes are charged at 0.5 fils/second."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the charges for the International calls after the included minutes are over?", "answer": ["International calls out of the included minutes are charged at 2 fils/second for 175 countries.", "International calls out of the included minutes are charged at 6 fils/second for 48 countries."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are charges for data usage after the included data is over?", "answer": ["The data usage out of the included data is charged at AED 1/MB."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I upgrade/downgrade my Etisalat Emirati plan will my included Local minutes/data and monthly charges be pro-rated?", "answer": ["If you upgrade or downgrade your plan, your Local minutes and charges will be pro-rated, but your data units won't be pro-rated you will get the full data allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the balance of my remaining minutes & data within my plan?", "answer": ["You can check the balance of all your remaining allowances within your plan by sending SMS or USSD.\r\n", "\r\nSMS: BALANCE to 1012 or via USSD: *140#"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": " Can I change my Etisalat Emirati plan to any other postpaid plans? Are there any exit charges accompanied with that change?", "answer": ["You can change your plan to any other postpaid plan:", ".", "In case of upgrading your plan there will be no exit charges, and In case of downgrading exit charges will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to the Data packages, Blackberry services, Value added services\u2026etc. on top of Etisalat Emirati plans?", "answer": ["Yes, you can subscribe to all the Data packages, Blackberry services and VAS services available. But you cannot subscribe to the new postpaid plan add ons."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Are there any exit charges applied in case of line termination?", "answer": ["You can cancel the line by visiting your nearest Etisalat store.", "AED 300 cancellation fee is applied if you are terminating a postpaid connection without any contract or migrating to prepaid in the first 6 months from activation date.", "If you are in 12 months contract early termination fee of AED 50 * remaining contract months will be applied.", "If you are in 24 months contract early termination fee of AED 100 * remaining contract months will be applied."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can i benefit from the free minutes to preferred numbers?", "answer": ["You need to activate the preferred number/s by SMS\r\n", "\r\nTo activate, SMS: 'ACT NAT number' to 1012\r\n", "\r\nTo Change: SMS \u2018Change NAT old preferred number and new preferred number\u2019 to 1012\r\n", "\r\nFor example: the old preferred number is 0501234567 and the new number is 0507654321 then type 'Change NAT 0501234567 0507654321'\r\n", "\r\nNumber can be changed only once a month. AED 25 charge applies.\r\n", "\r\nThe preferred number can be any number in UAE. (Both landline or mobile from any network)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are Etisalat Smart Plans?", "answer": ["Etisalat Smart Plan is an exciting new plan which offers voice and data benefits along with free minutes to preferred numbers. Not only do you get loads of data but you also get a significantly high voice allowance with our new \"Flexible Minutes\" which can be used for any type of call."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are \"flexible minutes\" and how can I use them?", "answer": ["The inclusive \"Flexible Minutes\" flexible, you can use them for national calls, international calls (to 175 destinations) or receiving roaming calls while you're abroad."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the charges for the Local calls after the included minutes are over?", "answer": ["Local calls out of the included minutes are charged at 0.5 fils/second."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the charges for the International calls after the included minutes are over?", "answer": ["International calls out of the included minutes are charged at 2 fils/second for 175 countries.\r\n", "\r\nInternational calls out of the included minutes are charged at 6 fils/second for 48 countries."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are charges for data usage after the included data is over?", "answer": ["The data usage out of the included data is charged at AED 1/MB."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I upgrade/downgrade my Etisalat smart plan will my included flexible minutes/data and monthly charges be pro-rated?", "answer": ["If you upgrade or downgrade your plan, your flexible minutes and charges will be pro-rated, but your data units won't be pro-rated you will get the full data allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the balance of my remaining minutes & data within my plan?", "answer": ["You can check the balance of all your remaining allowances within your plan by sending SMS or USSD.\r\n", "\r\nSMS: BALANCE to 1012 or via USSD: *140#"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I change my Etisalat smart plan to any other postpaid plans? Are there any exit charges accompanied with that change?", "answer": ["You can change your plan to any other postpaid plan:", ".", "In case of upgrading your plan there will be no exit charges, and In case of downgrading exit charges will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe to the Data packages, Blackberry services, Value added services\u2026etc. on top of Etisalat Smart plans?", "answer": ["Yes, you can subscribe to all the Data packages, Blackberry services and VAS services available. But you cannot subscribe to the new postpaid plan add ons."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Are there any exit charges applied in case of line termination?", "answer": ["You can cancel the line by visiting your nearest Etisalat store.", "AED 300 cancellation fee is applied if you are terminating a postpaid connection without any contract or migrating to prepaid in the first 6 months from activation date.", "If you are in 12 months contract early termination fee of AED 50* remaining contract months will be applied.", "If you are in 24 months contract early termination fee of AED 100* remaining contract months will be applied."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can i benefit from the free minutes to preferred numbers?", "answer": ["You need to activate the preferred number/s by SMS\r\n", "\r\nTo activate, SMS: 'ACT NAT number' to 1012\r\n", "\r\nTo Change, SMS: 'Change NAT number' to 1012\r\n", "\r\nNumber must be entered in full format. i.e. 97150xxxxxx\r\n", "\r\nNumber can be changed only once a month. AED 25 charge applies.\r\n", "\r\nThe preferred number can be any number in UAE. (Both landline or mobile from any network)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is the preferred number on any specific plan?", "answer": ["The preferred number option is available on Plans 300, 600 and 1000. You can choose any number of your choice in the UAE (mobile or landline) and speak for 5 hours (300 minutes) for FREE, every month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Are these free minutes in addition to the Flexi Minutes?", "answer": ["Yes, the free minutes to one preferred number are in addition to the flexible minutes that you enjoy on your Plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What do I need to do to enjoy this preferred number?", "answer": ["This special benefit is already available on the Plans 300, 600 and 1000. All you need to do is set your preferred number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I set my preferred number?", "answer": ["You can set your preferred number via:\r\n", "\r\nSMS: ACT NAT Preferred Number to 1012\r\n", "\r\n*Preferred number can be any national number, mobile or landline and must be entered along with the country code 971. E.g.: 97150xxxxxx, 9712xxxxxxx\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", ":\r\n", "\r\nEntering the country code is mandatory.\r\n", "\r\nThere should not be any space in the number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will I know that the preferred number is set?", "answer": ["You will receive an SMS confirming successful setting of your preferred number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I change my preferred number?", "answer": ["You can change your preferred number once during the month at a fee of AED25. Change of number will be with immediate effect. You will receive an SMS confirming successful change of your number.", "You can change your number via:\r\n", "\r\nSMS: Change NAT old preferred number and new preferred number\u2019 to 1012\r\n", "\r\nFor example: the old preferred number is 0501234567 and the new number is 0507654321 then type 'Change NAT 0501234567 0507654321'\r\n", "\r\nIf you are changing the preferred number during the month, your free minutes allowance will not be reset. Your total free allowance of 300 minutes will remain unchanged during the bill cycle."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "From which free allowance are the calls to my preferred number charged?", "answer": ["Calls to your preferred number are free up to the first 300 minutes.\r\n", "\r\nIf you use more, it will then be depleted from your flexible minutes.\r\n", "\r\nOnce you use up both your preferred number minutes and flexible minutes, you will be charged at standard national rates."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will I know that I have used my minutes for the preferred number or any other usage?", "answer": ["You can check the balance of all your remaining allowances within your plan by sending SMS or USSD.\r\n", "\r\nSMS: BALANCE to 1012 or via USSD: *140#"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens to my preferred number if I change my plan?", "answer": ["As long as you are changing to one of Plans 300, 600 or 1000 plan, your preferred number will be automatically migrated. If you choose any other plan, you'll lose the benefits of the preferred number and will be charged at regular national calling rates."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Why do I have to register my number?", "answer": ["This is a TRA policy for Consumer mobile customers to avoid the Fraud cases."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will I know that I have to renew my Registration details?", "answer": ["An SMS will be sent to you telling that the document details to have been expired and you need to renew it."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What will happen if I fail to renew my details?", "answer": ["You will be given one grace period, after that the line will be TOSSED for a period of time, if you fail to renew the registration during that period then the line will be disconnected."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Am visiting UAE on a visitor visa, do I have to register my line?", "answer": ["The visitor customers are given a line valid for 90 days only."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many time do I have to renew my registration?", "answer": ["You need to renew your registration every time your Identification expire."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Am using mobile number, & am owning a business in UAE but I don\u2019t have residence visa, while am visiting the country from time to time, how can I renew my registration?", "answer": ["You can send an email to care@etisalat.ae and providing a proof of your business along with a valid passport."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is Mobile Number Portability (MNP)? ", "answer": ["Mobile Number Portability (MNP) is the process of transferring (porting) your mobile phone number from one mobile phone network provider to another. You may want to do this if you wish to sign up to a new mobile phone provider and keep your original mobile phone number, thus saving you the inconvenience of updating your contacts with your new telephone number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will you benefit from MNP? ", "answer": ["You are free to choose a new mobile service provider without having to change to a new number. You don't have to notify friends, family and associates about your new operator when you move to Etisalat or any other operator. Just use your phone like you always do."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is porting of numbers? ", "answer": ["Porting of numbers is the actual switching of a mobile operator/mobile service provider without having to change one's mobile number. However, only active mobile numbers can be ported, so you do not have your number disconnected before porting."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the charges for porting a number? Are there any other charges applicable?", "answer": ["Etisalat offers the MNP (Mobile Number Portability) facility free of charge."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How long does it take to port a number? ", "answer": ["The entire process of porting takes approximately 2 days. The time for porting a number also depends on the clearance from the donor operator (operator that you are leaving)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What do I need to keep in mind before joining/porting to Etisalat?  ", "answer": ["All existing credit available to prepaid customers will expire upon successful porting and will not be carried forward.", "Call charges, plans and VAS offered by Etisalat may differ from that offered by your earlier service provider."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I port my prepaid/postpaid number to Etisalat?", "answer": ["Yes, you can port any prepaid or postpaid number to Etisalat. However, your credit in case of prepaid will lapse once the port in is successful."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What documents must a prepaid/postpaid customer submit while making a port in request to Etisalat? ", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the process to be followed to port my number to Etisalat?", "answer": ["All you have to do is visit your nearest Etisalat Business Centre or outlet and apply for the service with a valid number and ID documents as mentioned above and Etisalat will take care of the rest.", "Mobile Number Porting at Etisalat is offered as a \"one-stop-shop\" service. You do not have to visit the office of your previous operator. Etisalat will take care of the necessary formalities."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I get an Etisalat Porting Request Application form?", "answer": ["Etisalat MNP forms are available at all Etisalat touch points; they can also be downloaded from the Etisalat website. (Click here to download the application Form)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I port a landline number?", "answer": ["No, the service is applicable only to mobile services."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to change my SIM card to port my number to Etisalat?", "answer": ["Yes. Etisalat will offer you a new SIM card when you apply for porting. Etisalat will activate the new SIM card with your existing number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What will happen to the contacts in my SIM card?", "answer": ["Your new SIM card will not have your old contacts. It is advised to back up your contacts from the old SIM to phone and then copy them on to the new SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will I know if my porting request is completed or not?", "answer": ["You will be notified once Etisalat activates the new SIM card. Your previous operator shall also notify you on the deactivation of the old SIM card soon after Etisalat activates the new SIM.", "You will also be notified by means of SMS upon successful completion of your porting request."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "When can I apply for a porting request?", "answer": ["You can choose to apply for the service anytime between 8 am to 8 pm on any working day. Porting requests received between 8 am to 1 pm on working days only (Sunday to Thursday) will be processed the same day. However, some of our outlets work 24 hours, so you can submit your port in request at anytime, and our teams will process and verify your requests."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "When will the application received after 1 pm be processed?", "answer": ["The applications received after 1 pm will be processed during the next working day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is it compulsory to visit an Etisalat office to place the porting request?", "answer": ["No. You can become an Etisalat customer without even visiting any of our offices. All you have to do is visit etisalat.ae and place a port request and we will deliver the SIM card at your doorstep. (This service is applicable to destinations within the UAE only.)"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "In case I have a balance due with my previous operator, can I still port in or out?", "answer": ["Yes. Even if you have balance due, you will be able to place your porting request."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is Autopay? ", "answer": ["Autopay service is a great way to pay Etisalat's postpaid bills automatically on due date with complete confidence and security through your personal credit card.", "You can now enjoy the convenience of paying your Etisalat\u2019s postpaid bills automatically through a credit card. It only requires a one-time registration."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I enroll for Autopay?", "answer": ["Simply log on to Etisalat Online Services website ", " and register your credit card details. Enjoy peace of mind by paying your bills on time.", "If you have an Etisalat Online Services user ID, you will be able to register your Etisalat postpaid account.", "If you do not have an Etisalat Online Services user ID, you can still use Autopay service by simply logging on to www.etisalat.ae/online and registering any of your Etisalat accounts - either mobile, fixed line, Al Shamil and eLife easily and quickly.", "After successful online registration and log in, you need to register you Credit Card details against the registered account with Etisalat Online Services.", "Alternatively fill-up your credit card\u00a0 details in the ", " and submit to nearest Etisalat Store/ Business centre."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the benefits of subscribing to Etisalat Autopay?", "answer": ["One time registration; thereafter you need not worry about remembering to pay Etisalat bills on time.", "A Safe, convenient and efficient way of paying Etisalat\u2019s bills such as mobile services (Postpaid), Fixed-line, Al Shamil and eLife."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any charges to register for Auto Pay and any monthly debits?", "answer": ["No, there are no charges."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Which credit card types can I use to set up Autopay?", "answer": ["You can register for Autopay using a Visa or MasterCard credit card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What bills can I pay using Autopay?", "answer": ["You can pay your Etisalat mobile services (Postpaid), Fixed-line, Al Shamil and eLife."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "When will be the charging date once Autopay is activated?", "answer": ["The monthly debit will be 15", " of every month. Single date of charging."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any minimum and maximum limit for Autopay?", "answer": ["The minimum bill payment amount is AED 10 and maximum amount is AED 5000 per transaction."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "My credit card number has changed/expired. How do I modify my existing Autopay subscription?", "answer": ["All you need to do is login to ", " and update your credit card details.", "Alternatively you may visit any nearby ", " for assistance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I cancel my Autopay subscription?", "answer": ["All you need to do is login to ", " and cancel your subscription.", "Alternatively you may visit any nearby ", " for assistance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the New Postpaid Combo Add-On?", "answer": ["2 new Combo Add-ons will be launched that will provide customers 40% savings compared to subscribing in individual add-ons.\r\n", "\r\nNow there are 9 Add-ons or saving packs that New Postpaid customers can choose from."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Who is eligible for the Combo Add-On?", "answer": ["Same eligibility of the current Consumer postpaid Add-ons shall also be applicable to the new Combo Add-on.", "\u2022 New postpaid monthly plan (AED 50 monthly plan rental)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 New Postpaid Yearly Contract Plans ( 150 plan / 250 plan / 500 plan / 1,000 plan)\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 New Postpaid Smart Phone Plans"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What channels are available to manage Combo Add-on?", "answer": ["Customers can use any of the following channel to manage subscription or un-subscription in Combo add-on", "1. USSD\r\n", "\r\nDial the add-on menu *140#\r\n", "\r\nAlso, managing the add-on is possible through the unified menu *101#\r\n", "\r\n2. IVR\r\n", "\r\nDial IVR 125 and follow the instruction\r\n", "\r\n3. SMS"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I activate different types of Add-ons? ", "answer": ["Yes, you have the freedom of activating and mixing different types of add-ons you choose. You can subscribe and cancel at any time during the month. Pro-rated rental and allowances will be applied in case you subscribe during the month.", "Add-on subscription is automatically renewed at the beginning of every month. If you deactivate an add-on in the middle of the month, the rental is not refunded and the remaining allowances will be kept to use until end of the month and will be removed from start of next month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the Preferred Number rules?", "answer": ["\u2022 Preferred number can be any active etisalat mobile number.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 It will not be possible to deactivate the preferred number in the Combo Add-on alone. Customer need to deactivate the whole Combo add-on if wishes to delete the preferred number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the remaining allowance in my balance?", "answer": ["1. Postpaid Add-ons USSD *140# \u201cbalance inquiry menu\u201d\r\n", "\r\n2. Etisalat mobile app \u201cmy usage menu\u201d\r\n", "\r\n3. USSD *101#"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Are the Combo Add-on flexible minutes applicable for making calls to all countries? ", "answer": ["Flexible minutes can be used for most of the countries. For countries that flexible minutes are not applied to, please visit the postpaid plans section in "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many data units will I get for my package allowance? ", "answer": ["Etisalat follows uniform data allowance configuration across its packages, and your data units will be based on the below conversion:\r\n", "\r\n1 GB = 1,000 MB; 1 MB = 1,000 KB; 1 KB = 1,024 Bytes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How my data units will be consumed for package, and pay-as-you-go usage? ", "answer": ["When consuming data from a data package, your allowance will be deducted on the basis of 30 KB increments, whereas for pay-as-you-go data usage without any package, you will be rated on a 1 KB pulse."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I earn Smiles points? ", "answer": ["Smiles points can be earned through two ways, Bill payment and the monthly smiles points provided with the New Postpaid yearly plans."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any conditions to earn the plan embedded smiles points?", "answer": ["Monthly smiles points will be added to your smiles account on monthly basis as long as the line is active."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is it a must to download smiles App to earn smiles points?", "answer": ["The application must be downloaded and registered to earn smiles points. The application can be found in google play store and Apple App store."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How and where can I use smiles points?", "answer": ["Smiles points can be redeemed as shopping vouchers, discounts in various locations or bill payment for more details visit smiles.etisalat.ae"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "For how long I will receive the plan embedded smiles points?", "answer": ["For half of the contract duration (Ie 24 months plans will get monthly smiles points for 12 months) after that the customer will continue receiving smiles points from bill payments."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the Rollover Feature? ", "answer": ["Rollover is the new feature that transfers the unused bundled allowances of minutes to the following month.\r\n", "\r\nBoth the unused Local minutes and the International minutes within the MyPlan packages and sPlan packages will be carried over to the following month"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Which Postpaid plans will this feature be applied on? ", "answer": ["Rollover feature will be applied on the following Postpaid Plans:\r\n", "\r\n- MyPlan.\r\n", "\r\n- iPhone Plan.\r\n", "\r\n- sPlan.( HTC One X and Samsung s3)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I subscribe to benefit from this feature?", "answer": ["This feature will be applied automatically, No need to subscribe or opt in.\r\n", "\r\n- All existing MyPlan, iPhone and sPlan customers will be applied automatically from 1 July 2012.\r\n", "\r\n- Any new customers on MyPlan, iPhone and sPlan starting from 1 July 2012 already applied."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Are there any additional charges for this feature?", "answer": ["Rollover is Free of charge and there are no any additional charges to benefit from this feature."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I know the carried forward balance?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", " You will receive an SMS end of every month with the carried forward minutes.\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", " You can check the balance of the carried over minutes any time with the USSD command *170#.\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", " You will find the balance of the carried over minutes from last month and carried forward minutes to next month in your bill"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the SMS content and USSD content? ", "answer": ["- ", " \"Dear Customer, you have xx local minutes and xx International minutes to be carried forward to the next month.\"\r\n", "\r\n- ", "\"Dear Customer, you have xx local minutes and xx International minutes carried over from the previous month.\""], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the priority of consumption?", "answer": ["\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", " Carried over units from the previous month. (If any)\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", " The current month's minutes.\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", " Minutes within the monthly add on packages if the customer is subscribed to any."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I use my carried Over minutes?", "answer": ["Carried over minutes will be used before the new month's minutes. If the carried over minutes are not all used in full before the end of the following month they will expire."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens to my in case of Upgrade/downgrade Package? ", "answer": ["- Remaining minutes in the old package will be kept.\r\n", "\r\n- Pro rated minutes in the new package.\r\n", "\r\n- Balance of carried over minutes will be kept."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe more than once to the same bundle in the same month?", "answer": ["You can only subscribe once to the same bundle each month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I subscribe with multiple bundles in the same month?", "answer": ["You can only have a combination of 1 local bundle and 1 international bundle."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am a New Postpaid Plan customer, can I subscribe to these bundles?", "answer": ["For New Postpaid customers, you have great add ons that you can check here."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the Bill limit service? ", "answer": ["A new service where postpaid consumer customers can keep their monthly expenses under control by setting one of 6 limits.\r\n", "\r\nAED 100 \u2013 AED 200 \u2013 AED 300 \u2013 AED 400 \u2013 AED 500 \u2013 AED 1000."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the service features?", "answer": ["- Customers can select any of the 6 bill limits.\r\n", "\r\n- All types of usage are included in the bill limit consumption except for rental charges and roaming charges on non-camel operators.\r\n", "\r\n- Customer usage will be barred once he reaches his set limit. I.e. all out of bundle usage will be barred when the customer reaches his set bill limit.\r\n", "\r\n- Customers can activate \u2013 deactivate \u2013 increase or decrease their limits during the month as this is an optional limit set by the customer.\r\n", "\r\n- Maximum number of changes during any month are 3 increase and/or decreases per month.\r\n", "\r\n- Increasing the bill limit can happen anytime during the month.\r\n", "\r\n- Decreasing the bill limit can happen anytime during the month only under the condition the customer\u2019s current usage has not exceeded the lower new limit he is setting.\r\n", "\r\n- Customers will receive notifications upon consuming 80%, 90% & 100% of the set limit."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the benefit of this service?", "answer": ["- Keep your bill under control. (No bill shocks)\r\n", "\r\n- Peace of Mind - Convenience"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Who is eligible to subscribe to this service?", "answer": ["Consumer postpaid customers subscribed to the following plans are eligible to subscribe to this service:\r\n", "\r\nClassic - MyPlan - New Postpaid 50 - New Postpaid Yearly Plans 150,250 & 500 - New Postpaid Smartphone Plans - Etisalat Smart plans - Etisalat Emirati plans - VIP plans"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the channels to manage this service?", "answer": ["App - SMS - USSD - 101 & etisalat stores Customers can activate - deactivate - increase and decrease - inquire on their limits & current consumption through all the channels above."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Which services and usage types are included in this limit and which are excluded?", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What can I do when I reach my limit during the month?", "answer": ["Customer has the following options when he reaches his set bill limit in the middle of the month and wants to reconnect his line and start using once again:\r\n", "\r\n1- Upgrade his current bill control limit.\r\n", "\r\n2- Remove/cancel the bill control limit service.\r\n", "\r\n3- Add an Additional Add-on or package. I.e. new postpaid add ons or data/voice packs.\r\n", "\r\n4- Recharge with any prepaid recharge card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I recharge my postpaid line?", "answer": ["You can recharge your postpaid line with any of the prepaid recharge cards and vouchers. This recharge amount will be used to settle your postpaid bill and you can make calls with the full amount recharged.\r\n", "\r\nTo recharge:\r\n", "\r\nDial *120*voucher number#"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "In which cases will the service is removed and which cases I can keep this service on my line?", "answer": ["The service is removed in the following cases:\r\n", "\r\n- Postpaid plan migration from one of the applicable plans to another non applicable plan.\r\n", "\r\n- Postpaid migration to prepaid.\r\n", "\r\n- Transfer of ownership.\r\n", "\r\n- Cessation - port out.\r\n", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\nThe service is kept (not removed) in the following cases:\r\n", "\r\n- Postpaid plan migration from one of the applicable plans to another postpaid consumer applicable plan.\r\n", "\r\n- Sim replacement.\r\n", "\r\n- Change number."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the local minute calling bundles and who is eligible for it?", "answer": ["The local calling bundles are daily bundles of local minutes offered at lower rates. These bundles are available to all Wasel customers.", "When you make the first local call after subscription:", "\u2022 The rental for the bundle will be deducted\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 The minutes included in the bundle will be credited to your account\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Once you have used up all the bundle minutes for the day, local calls will be charged at the tariff plan rates for the rest of the day\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 International calls will also be charged as per your tariff plan", "You do not have to subscribe to the bundle every day. It will automatically be assigned to you once you make the first local call of the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to these bundles?", "answer": ["You can subscribe to the bundles by:\r\n", "\r\na) dialling *111# and choosing the relevant options.\r\n", "\r\nb) Sending an SMS to 1010 as follows:", "Once you have been successfully opted-in, you will receive an SMS from Etisalat confirming the same.\r\n", "\r\nOn the day of subscription, the benefits of the bundle will be applicable from the next local call made after you receive the confirmation SMS.\r\n", "\r\nOn subsequent days, the benefits of the bundle will be applicable from the first local call you make for the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Which numbers can be called using these bundled minutes?", "answer": ["You can use these minutes to call any UAE landline or mobile number (Etisalat and du).", "Calls to local premium numbers are not part of these bundles. Such calls will be charged as per your tariff plan."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How long will these minutes in the bundles be valid for?", "answer": ["The bundle of minutes is valid for the day. Unused minutes (if any) will expire at the end of the day (midnight).", "A new bundle will be added to your account the next day as and when you make the first local call for the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How are these local bundles beneficial?", "answer": ["With these bundles you can enjoy a lower rate per minute for your local calls.\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Discounted rate - On calls to any mobile or landline in the UAE\r\n", "\r\n- 44% savings on the Daily 5 minute and the Daily 10 minute bundles compared to standard local call rates\r\n", "\r\n- 63% savings on the Daily 30 minute bundle compared to standard local call rates\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Pay only on days you use \u2014 automatic renewal of bundle only on days you make local calls\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 Affordable rentals with bundled minutes to suit your needs\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 No extra charges/fees applicable"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will I be charged for the bundle every day even if I don\u2019t make any local calls?", "answer": ["No. You will be charged for the bundle only on days on which you make a local call.\r\n", "\r\nIf you do not make any local call during a day, there will be no charge for these bundles."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will I be charged for my local calls once I have subscribed to one of these bundles? ", "answer": ["\u2022 If you have subscribed to the 10 minute bundle, AED 2 will be deducted from your balance for the bundle and your account gets credited with 10 local minutes, once you make a local call\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 After you have used up these 10 minutes, your calls from the 11th minute for the day, would be charged as per your tariff plan\r\n", "\r\n\u2022 On days when you do not make any local calls, you would not be charged AED2"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How will I be charged if I do not have sufficient balance to cover the daily bundle rental? ", "answer": ["In case you do not have the necessary balance to cover the bundle rental, your calls will be charged as per the standard Wasel tariff plan.", "Once you have sufficient balance in your account, the rental will be deducted and the bundle minutes will be credited upon your next call of the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Once I use up all the daily minutes in the bundle, can I subscribe to the bundle again to get more minutes? ", "answer": ["Multiple subscriptions within the same day are not possible. However, there are two bundles to choose from; you can subscribe to any bundle that suits your usage pattern.", "Once you have used up all the bundle minutes for the day, local calls will be charged at the tariff plan rates for the rest of the day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Are there any registration/subscription charges associated with this offer?", "answer": ["No, there are no registration/subscription charges associated with this offer. You will only be charged the daily rental for the bundle on days when you make a local call."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I upgrade or downgrade my Bundle? ", "answer": ["To upgrade/downgrade your bundle, just subscribe to the new bundle of your choice. The subscription for that bundle will come into effect from the next day.", " You can upgrade/downgrade/subscribe /unsubscribe only once a day and this will be effective from the next day."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I check on the minutes balance of my bundle?", "answer": ["For enquiry related to this bundle, dial *101*1*2# and choose the relevant options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is this a temporary offer?", "answer": ["No, this is a permanent offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I opt out of this offer? ", "answer": ["Yes, you can opt-out any time. To opt-out, you can either:\r\n", "\r\na) dial *111# and choose the relevant options OR\r\n", "\r\nb) Send the following SMS to 1010", "Once you opt-out, you will be charged for all local calls as per your tariff plan.\r\n", "\r\nYou can opt-in any time again, by dialling *111# and choosing the relevant options."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["With Etisalat\u2019s Deal of the day, Etisalat\u2019s customers can enjoy 2 special offers everyday; one Telecom related offer and one lifestyle offer. Customers need to dial *050# or send DEAL to 1204 in order to know the Deal of the Day. On dialing *050#, you will receive an SMS from sender ID 1204 communicating the offer. To avail the offer, you need to reply to the SMS by sending YES. To subscribe to the lifestyle offer, the customer has to reply to the message with \u201cbonus\u201d as the key word."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Who is eligible for Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["All Etisalat Postpaid customers are eligible for the Deal of the Day.", "Deal of the Day is not available for Business/SMB/Enterprise customers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can the customer subscribe to the Deal of the Day offer?", "answer": ["- Dial *050# or send DEAL to 1204 or through Etisalat UAE Mobile App - by opening the app and shaking the phone. Shake a Deal!\r\n", "\r\n- The customer will receive an SMS (from sender ID 1204), which will carry the offer the customer is eligible for.\r\n", "\r\n- Reply to the message by sending YES to subscribe to the offer. Customer will receive a confirmation message confirming that the offer is activated.\r\n", "\r\n- The customer will receive another message in 10 to 15 minutes of receiving the telecom offer, which will have the Lifestyle offer. To subscribe to the lifestyle offer, the customer has to reply to the message with \u201cbonus\u201d as the key word."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many offers can the customer subscribe to everyday?", "answer": ["The customer can subscribe to two offers daily; one lifestyle offer and one telecom offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I check the balance and/or expiry date of the bonus?", "answer": ["On activation of your offer, you will receive the confirmation message. This message will have the USSD code that you have to dial in order to know the expiry of the free minutes/offers.", "Example - Dear Customer, you have received 30 Local minutes valid for today. To check your minutes balance dial *121*37#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the validity of the special offers that customers receive from Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["The validity of the offers depends on the type of the offer the customer subscribes to. The validity of the offer will be mentioned in the offer SMS.", "Example - Dear Customer, you have received 15 international minutes valid for 7 days. To check your minutes balance dial *121*35#."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there a limit to the number of offers I can subscribe to?", "answer": ["No, there is no limit to the number of offers you can subscribe to, but you will receive and can subscribe to only two offers a day (one telecom related and one lifestyle related). In order to subscribe to another offer, you will need to dial *050# again the next day to get and subscribe to a new offer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Which countries can be called using the International Calling Offers available as the Deal of the Day?", "answer": ["Please refer to the ", " to know about the countries you can call."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, there are no additional charges for this service. You just pay for the applications you choose to buy."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I need a special plan for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, your Data Plan is enough. Your data usage will be deducted from your plan allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am on Etisalat Postpaid, how I will pay for the apps? ", "answer": ["The amount for every application you purchase will be included in your next bill."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am on Wasel. How I will pay for the apps?  ", "answer": ["The amount will be deducted immediately from your credit balance. Make sure that you have enough balance before the purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any limit on my purchase?  ", "answer": ["Below are the limits set for Google Play transactions:\r\n", "\r\n- Per transaction limit AED 100\r\n", "\r\n- Per day transaction limit AED 200\r\n", "\r\n- Per month limit AED 500"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much is the price for each application? ", "answer": ["Each application has price in AED, so you can easily decide to buy or not (no need to do currency conversion)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I use Wi-Fi only?  ", "answer": ["Yes you can."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if the Application does not work on my handset?", "answer": ["- In 1st 15 minutes you can refund the application from the google play store itself.\r\n", "\r\n- After the initial 15 minutes, please contact the developer, email id will be mentioned on the application page on Google Play Store."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, there is no additional charge for this service. You just pay for the applications you purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": " Do I need special data plan for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, your Data Plan is enough. Your data usage will be deducted from your plan allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": " I am on Etisalat Postpaid, how I will pay for the apps? ", "answer": ["The amount for every application you purchase will be included in your next bill."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": " I am on Wassel. How I will pay for the apps?  ", "answer": ["The amount will be deducted immediately from your credit balance. Make sure that you have enough balance before the purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much is the price for each application? ", "answer": ["Each application has price on the store, so you can easily decide to buy or not. No additional charges will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Can I use Wi-Fi only?  ", "answer": ["Yes, enter your mobile number and verification of your mobile number will be done."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if the Application does not work on my handset?", "answer": ["Please contact the Windows Phone support, call the support line or send an email."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I have to pay for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, there are no additional charges for this service. You just pay for the applications you purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I need special data plan for this service?  ", "answer": ["No, your Data Plan is enough. Your data usage will be deducted from your plan allowance."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": " I am on Etisalat Postpaid, how I will pay for the apps? ", "answer": ["The amount for every application you purchase will be included in your next bill."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am on Wasel. How I will pay for the apps?  ", "answer": ["The amount will be deducted immediately from your credit balance. Make sure that you have enough balance before the purchase."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much is the price for each application? ", "answer": ["Each application has price in AED, so you can easily decide to buy or not (no need to do currency conversion). No additional charges will apply."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": " Can I use Wi-Fi only?  ", "answer": ["Yes, verification of your mobile number will be done."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if the Application does not work on my handset?", "answer": ["Please contact the Samsung Apps support, call the support line or send an email."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How can I subscribe to the service? ", "answer": ["You can subscribe to the service by:\r\n", "\r\ni) Simply sending \u201c r greetune\u201d as an SMS to the short code 1010\r\n", "\r\nii) Dial 125 from your Mobile handset"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much will this service cost me? ", "answer": ["There is no connection charge, monthly fee is AED 5."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How much does each Greetune tone cost? ", "answer": ["Each Greetune tone will cost you Dhs 5."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many Greetune can I buy? ", "answer": ["You can buy up to 20 greetune tones."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How do I get charged?", "answer": ["If you are a postpaid customer, a monthly subscription charge of AED 5 will be added to your monthly bill. If you are a Prepaid customer, the monthly fees will be deducted from your account, every month."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is the next step after subscription? How will I know that I have completed the subscription process successfully? ", "answer": ["You will receive an SMS confirming your subscription and a PIN Number with instructions to logon to ", ". Use your mobile number as your User ID and the PIN number to preview/listen, buy and assign tones to your callers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the different options available for setting up my Greetune service profile after subscription? ", "answer": ["The following options are available for setting up / managing the account :", "1. Via Web Page\r\n", "\r\ni) Visit ", "\r\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "\r\nii) Enter your username and password, where the username is your mobile phone number and the password is a unique 6 to 9 digits numeric PIN code received via SMS after successful subscription\r\n", "\r\niii) After entering your account, you may preview the list , pre-listen, buy or personalize any one of the listed tones available on the web page.", "\r\n2. Via SMS\r\n", "\r\nYou may send an SMS to 1100 with one of the following commands to personalize your Greetune account."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if I don\u2019t have enough credit in my account, when the service tries to deduct from my account?", "answer": ["If there is not enough credit, you will be provided a three day grace period, during which time the system will keep trying to deduct the amount from your account. If the system fails to renew the subscription, the service will be disconnected and you will lose the Greetune tones in your album"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Is there any validity period for the Greetune tone? Does it expire?", "answer": ["After you buy the Greetune tone and add it to your album, it will be valid and available for a period of 12 months."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is \u2018Assign Greetune\u2019 to specific number? ", "answer": ["When you assign a Greetune tone to a specific number, the tone can be heard only by that number i.e. If you want 050123457 to hear an Islamic tone with the tone code 100001, you should send \u2018ASSIGN1000010501234567\u2019 to 1100"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Do I pay for each assign/de-assign? ", "answer": ["The assign/de-assign is free of charge, if it is done from the internet and charged like local SMS if the command is sent via SMS."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What is temporary deactivation? ", "answer": ["You can temporarily deactivate the service when you do not want other people to hear your Greetune service, by sending SMS \u201cOFF\u201d to 1100. However, you will not be unsubscribed and you can turn the service back on by simply sending an SMS with the command \u201cON\u201d to 1100."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I temporarily deactivated Etisalat\u2019s Greetune service, will tones be deleted from my album?", "answer": ["No. Your personal tones will not get deleted in this case."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I temporarily deactivated the service, will I still have to pay the monthly fee? ", "answer": ["Yes."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I get a message that my album is full, how can I delete Greetune tones? ", "answer": ["i) Via web : Log on to ", " and delete from your album.\r\n", "\r\nii) Via SMS : To delete certain tones from your album, simply send \u201cDelete XXYYYY\u201d (XXYYYY is the tone ID) to the short code 1100 and it will be deleted."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if Etisalat\u2019s Greetune is active, someone calls me & I am busy on another call? ", "answer": ["The caller hears the normal busy tone, Etisalat\u2019s Greetune will not heard."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if Etisalat\u2019s Greetune is active and someone calls me & I am already on another call with call waiting active? ", "answer": ["The new caller will hear the Greetune tone."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What if the Greetune service is active, someone calls me & my phone is switched off or out of reach? ", "answer": ["The caller hears the usual out of reach announcement and not the Greetune tone."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Will Greetune service work while outside the country and do I have to pay extra charges for that? ", "answer": ["Etisalat\u2019s Greetune service will work when you are roaming with no extra charges"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Who is eligible to use Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["Multi SIM service is applicable for Consumer plans (Postpaid and Prepaid) only. Multi SIM service is not applicable for Business customers."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "If I am a ported-in customer, can I use Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["Yes"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Where can I get the Multi-SIM Service?", "answer": ["Visit any of the "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Does my tariff plan matter?", "answer": ["The subscription to Multi SIM SIMs is independent of the main primary package subscribed by the customer.", "Example: if main SIM is data-only SIM then all cloned SIMs will be data-only as well. If customer has New Postpaid on his main SIM then all minutes, SMS, data packs etc. will also be available on cloned SIMs"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "Does Multi-SIM support all networks?", "answer": ["Multi-SIM works on all types of networks (2G, 3G, and 4G)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What type of SIM cards work with Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["All SIM card types are supported - The customer will have the flexibility of adding/removing SIM cards and changing their type (mini/micro/nano SIM)."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "How many additional SIM cards can I get?", "answer": ["For Postpaid Customers:\r\n", "\r\n- You can get 4 additional SIM cards (all types of SIM cards)", "For Prepaid customers:\r\n", "\r\n- You can get 1 additional SIM card."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What services will work on Multi-SIM?", "answer": ["All services including roaming will be applicable on SIMs (primary + clones):", "a. Voice, data, SMS etc. will be active on all SIMs simultaneously", "b. Excluding receiving voice calls \u2013 it will be enabled only on one SIM at a time", "c. Excluding BlackBerry service \u2013 it will be active only on one SIM at a time"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens if I subscribe to a data package?", "answer": ["If a customer adds a data package to its primary service, then the data will be shared among all the SIMs part of the Multi SIM service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens is I migrate my Main SIM?", "answer": ["If a customer migrates from Post-paid to Prepaid Service or Vice-versa:", "The Multi SIM service will be deactivated when a customer requests for migration of service."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What happens is if want to change my Main SIM package or tariff plan?", "answer": ["If the customer wants to upgrade/downgrade the data package or the primary service, then it does not have any effect on the Multi SIM service.", "For example, if the customer wants to migrate from the 1GB plan to a 5GB plan, then the data + voice as per the new plan that customer migrates to, is shared between all the SIMs subscribed by the customer."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "What are the codes to operate my Multi-SIM Service?", "answer": ["\r\n          ", "\r\n                                    "], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am a postpaid customer, how much will Multi-SIM cost me?", "answer": ["All charges will be added to customer\u2019s bill.", "Monthly rental is applied on pro-rated basis (for example if the customer activates service on 15 April, then the customer needs to pay only for remaining 15 days of April)", "If the customer de-activates the service, there will be no refund for unused time during the month"], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"},
{"question": "I am a prepaid customer, how much will Multi-SIM cost me?", "answer": ["Rental charges are deducted in full from prepaid balance upfront.", "If rental deduction fails, then Multi-SIM service will be suspended. Customer will have to manually re-activate service after toping up account with required amount.", "If Multi-SIM service is suspended, only the clone SIM will be affected.", "If customer de-activates and re-activates his service, he will be charged the monthly rental in full - no pro-rating."], "cat": "mobilenew", "sub_cat": "mobile_postpaid"}
]